Chapter 325: 10 Per Second

At the center of the array, Daoist Xie's entire body was radiating yellow, golden, and purple light. The three types of light weren't conflicting with one another in the slightest. Instead, they were fused together in a harmonious balance.

Countless three-colored spirit patterns were surging incessantly over the surface of its body, occasionally coming together to form a series of arrays, only to then split apart a moment later.

A Golden Immortal Stage aura was also emanating out of the puppet, and unlike in the past, this burst of spiritual pressure was completely smooth and uninhibited.

Han Li was ecstatic, and he bolstered the four-colored light barrier in the room even further to contain this burst of Golden Immortal Stage spiritual pressure.

All of a sudden, Daoist Xie opened its eyes, releasing two bursts of dazzling light out of its pupils.

The two bursts of light shot through the four-colored light barrier with ease to create a pair of large holes, then pierced through the walls of the inn as well before erupting into the heavens, where they disappeared without a trace.

Thankfully, the two bursts of light were traveling diagonally upward and didn't harm anyone.

Han Li was greatly startled by this, and he hurriedly made a hand seal to mend the two holes in the four-colored light barrier.

Meanwhile, the streaks of light flew into the sky above White Jade City before exploding violently, and all of the world's origin qi above the city was swept up into a violently frenzy as gusts of fierce yellow, golden, and purple wind surged through the heavens, releasing a burst of enormous spiritual pressure as they did so.

The three gusts of wind were howling through the air with extraordinary force, and all of the cultivators throughout White Jade City were stunned by what they were seeing.

"There's no way this amount of spiritual pressure can be released by a True Immortal!"

"Could it be that one of the dao lords has arrived in White Jade City?"

Many of the people on the streets outside had erupted into chatter, while Han Li was frantically making hand seals to isolate Daoist Xie's aura, preventing it from leaking any further.

At the same time, he had released his spiritual sense to encompass everything within a radius of several thousand kilometers of the inn so that he would be able to immediately detect any disturbance.

Those two streaks of light had flown out of the city in the blink of an eye, and on top of that, the preaching ceremony was scheduled for this very day, so many of the cultivators in the city had already left.

The small portion of cultivators that remained may not have been able to detect that the aura had come from the inn, and everyone was wary of Golden Immortal cultivators, so even if someone did make the connection, they most likely wouldn't have dared to approach the inn to confirm their suspicions.

The three-colored gale in the sky continued to swirl around for a while before quickly dissipating.

It had created quite a spectacular sight to behold, but it hadn't caused any damage, so the people in the city only discussed the fleeting phenomenon for a short while before quickly dispersing, much to Han Li's relief.

At the center of the array, Daoist Xie rose to its feet, and the light radiating from its body faded alongside the enormous spiritual pressure it was releasing.

"Finally, I've successfully fused with this puppet," Daoist Xie declared.

"Didn't you say that you were fine on your own and didn't require my presence? If I hadn't decided to stay for a moment longer, you would've attracted a great deal of trouble for us," Han Li said in a slightly accusatory manner.

He had spent the entirety of the past three days here, rendering him unable to participate in any of the auctions and exchange events in the city.

At times like this, it was often the case that the most precious treasures would emerge near the end, and if he had been free to shop around these past three days, perhaps he would've been able to gather a few dao pill ingredients.

Daoist Xie could hear the displeasure in Han Li's voice, and it explained, "I failed to anticipate how pure the Lightning Soul Crystal was and how much power it contained."

"So be it. In any case, it's fantastic news that you were able to successfully fuse with this puppet, and I should congratulate you for it," Han Li said as a smile appeared on his face.

"Thank you for acquiring this immortal puppet for me and for looking out for me these past few days. If it wasn't for your help, there's no way I would've been able to complete this process smoothly. I'll remember everything you've done for me," Daoist Xie said as it cupped its fist in a grateful salute.

Han Li merely waved a hand in response. "The power that you inadvertently released just now hasn't exposed us, but even so, we can't stay here any longer. On top of that, the preaching ceremony is about to begin, so let's get out of here."

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then flew into Han Li's storage bracelet as a streak of yellow light.

Han Li swept a hand through the air to release a burst of yellow light to repair the two small holes on the wall, then emerged from his room.

Right as he was about to go downstairs, he suddenly stopped in his tracks, then cast his gaze toward the other direction down the corridor.

After releasing his spiritual sense just now, he had already detected that Gan Jiuzhen was no longer here.

A slightly peculiar look appeared on his face, and he quickly withdrew his gaze before making his way downstairs.

A thought occurred to him as he asked through voice transmission, "By the way, you told me that you were going to tell me the reason why you asked me to sell those Blush Cloud Fire Crystals after you fused with the puppet. Can you tell me the reason now?"

Instead of answering Han Li's question, Daoist Xie raised one of its own. "Fellow Daoist Han, what do you think is used as the power source for this Golden Immortal puppet?"

Han Li was rather taken aback by this question, while Daoist Xie continued, "All immortal puppets run on Immortal Origin Stones, and this one is no exception. On top of that, this puppet possesses Golden Immortal Stage power, and it's extremely costly to use. The number of Immortal Spirit Stones that you previously had on hand was nowhere near enough."

"How many Immortal Origin Stones are required for you to unleash this puppet's full power?" Han Li asked.

"If I were to go all-out, I would have to burn through 10 Immortal Origin Stones per second," Daoist Xie replied.

Han Li was already mentally prepared, but he was still caught off guard. "What? 10 per second!"

"That's not that much. Immortal puppets require an enormous amount of immortal spiritual power for support, and there are some that use up dozens, even hundreds of times as many Immortal Origin Stones per second," Daoist Xie said.

"Have you seen such puppets before, Brother Xie," Han Li asked.

"No, it's just that I've regained some memories as I was fusing with the Lightning Soul Crystal," Daoist Xie explained.

"Oh? Have you recalled anything about your former owner?" Han Li asked with an intrigued look in his eyes.

He was very interested in this person. Daoist Xie had told him in the past that its previous owner was dead, but it was still yet to be seen whether that was actually true.

"I've only recovered some bits and pieces of memories, most of which are related to immortal puppets. As for those Blush Cloud Fire Crystals that you sold, you manage to obtain over 3,000 Immortal Origin Stones for them, and that's enough to call upon my power several times," Daoist Xie said.

"I see. In any case, it's about time that we left," Han Li replied with a nod, then cast his gaze toward the White Jade Peak.

……

It was a bright and sunny day on the White Jade Peak.

There were pristine white clouds drifting over the clear, blue sky, and a rainbow was also hanging in the heavens like a giant bridge that stood above the clouds.

High up in the sky were hundreds of golden chariots that were drawn by winged dragon horses, and upon those carriages stood teams of tall cultivators wielding silver halberds and clad in suits of golden armor, patrolling the sky in a radius of several hundred kilometers.

The entirety of the White Jade Peak was enshrouded under a golden light barrier that acted as a flight restriction, and it wasn't giving off any particularly powerful energy fluctuations.

As long as one was at or above the True Immortal Stage, they would be able to fly into it without being affected, but those who were at or below the Grand Ascension Stage would've been kept out by the light barrier.

Hence, upon reaching the foot of the White Jade Peak, the majority of the Blaze Dragon Dao's disciples were forced to climb the mountain on foot in order to attend the preaching ceremony.

At this moment, the white plaza on the mountain was extremely lively and bustling, with hundreds of thousands of Blaze Dragon Dao disciples and the core elders of many of the Blaze Dragon Dao's subsidiary sects present. Even after all of the cushions had been occupied, there were still more people constantly arriving, and the plaza was quickly becoming extremely packed.

In fact, some people had even begun resorting to sitting down with their legs crossed somewhere halfway up the mountain to await the commencement of the ceremony.

There were countless people gathered at the foot of the White Jade Peak as well, and it was no less crowded than on the plaza on the mountain summit.

However, there was a more diverse range of people gathered at the foot of the mountain, with many cultivators from some other small and medium-sized sects all over the Ancient Cloud Continent interspersed among the Blaze Dragon Dao disciples.

These people had set up a series of stalls along the paths leading up to the White Jade Peak, and these stalls were packed with treasures, pills, and materials that they were selling to passersby.

There were also Blaze Dragon Dao cultivators that were clad in suits of golden armor standing around the stalls at set intervals, patrolling the area to maintain order.

In contrast with the exchange events that Han Li had previously participated in, these stalls were mostly aimed at cultivators at or below the Deity Transformation Stage, and it was much like the Great South Meeting that he had attended back in the Mortal Realm. [1]

At the center of the preaching platform on the summit of the White Jade Peak was a large purple table that didn't have many engravings on its surface, nor did it appear all that beautiful or intricate, but it did have a more antiquated and natural appearance.

Behind the table was a copper cauldron that was around 10 feet tall, plunged into which were several hundred sticks of incense, all of which were lit and producing plumes of faint azure smoke.

On either side of the cauldron were close to 100 round gray cushions placed down in a symmetrical fashion, and at this moment, streaks of light were constantly approaching the scene before sitting down on the normal cushions on the stone staircase around the platform.

The only ones who were granted spots on the stone staircase were inner and outer sect True Immortal Stage elders of the Blaze Dragon Dao, as well as all of the dao lords' core disciples, and given their lofty status, they were naturally far more restrained, so it was a lot less rowdy on the stone staircase than it was on the plaza.

Most of them were meditating with their eyes closed, silently waiting for the ceremony to commence, and only a small portion of them were greeting acquaintances or chatting quietly with one another.

Right at this moment, a streak of azure light flew in from the southwestern direction, then descended onto the preaching platform to reveal none other than Han Li.

He took a glance to find that all of the cushions near the top of the platform had already been taken, but there were still many vacant spots on the lower parts of the staircase.

Han Li made his way up the staircase, and after ascending for around 100 steps, he spotted a familiar figure waving at him to his left.

It was none other than Qi Liang, and Han Li gave him a smile before approaching him and sitting down onto the empty cushion next to him.

[1]. For more information on the Great South Meeting, please refer to RMJI Chapter 128: Great South Meeting.

[Back]

Chapter 326: Gradual Arrivals

"You're a little late, Brother Li! All of the good spots up there have already been taken," Qi Liang said with a smile.

"It's fine. All I need to do is listen and absorb Dao Lord Baili's teachings, why fret over whether I'm close or far away from the platform?" Han Li replied with a nonchalant shake of his head.

"Such a mindset is certainly true to your character, Brother Li. No wonder you've been able to make such rapid progress in your cultivation! If you ask me, once you reach the late-True Immortal Stage in the next 10,000 years, you'll be able to claim a spot among one of the 36 deputy dao lords. Make sure not to forget about me when that happens," Qi Liang chuckled.

"You're far too kind, Brother Qi. Unless I can attain the Great Dao during this very preaching ceremony, there's no way I could make another breakthrough in the next 10,000 years," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

Qi Liang burst into laughter upon hearing this, then changed the subject. "By the way, I haven't seen you at all these past few days. Could it be that you've already obtained the treasures that you're looking for."

"If it were so easy to find what I'm looking for, then I wouldn't have been struggling with the task for so long. There were some unforeseen matters that I had to take care of the past few days, and that's why I came here so late," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"Indeed. I had thought that I would be able to secure some prized treasures during such an auspicious event, but I still wasn't able to find any of the things that I've been searching for," Qi Liang sighed in response.

While Han Li and Qi Liang were chatting with one another, a deafening boom suddenly rang out in the sky, and the two of them hurriedly looked up to see a massive bolt of purple lightning crashing down from the heavens, aimed at a certain spot on the white jade platform.

After the bolt of lightning faded, around a dozen figures emerged, one of which was the purple-robed Ouyang Kuishan, the current managing dao lord of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

As for the dozen or so figures accompanying him, all of them had restrained their own auras, but many of the Blaze Dragon Dao's members had already identified them to have been deputy dao lords of the sect.

Ouyang Kuishan sat on one of the cushions in the first row situated to the left of the cauldron, and only after that did all of the deputy dao lords accompanying him sit down as well.

As soon as this collection of important figures appeared on the platform, all of the Blaze Dragon Dao elders and disciples seated on the surrounding stone staircase instantly sat up straighter, while the chatter around the platform also gradually died down. Even the exchange events taking place at the foot of the mountain had been put on pause, and everyone was looking up at the mountain summit.

In the blink of an eye, the entire area within a radius of hundreds of kilometers of the white jade platform had fallen completely silent.

A few minutes later, a gust of golden wind swept forth from the distant sky, then faded as it neared the platform to reveal seven or eight figures.

The two figures that were leading the way were quite peculiar in appearance.

One of them appeared to have been no different from a normal woman, except she had silver skin and a pair of thin and pointy ears. Standing next to her was a burly man with his face covered in golden fur and scales growing on his eyelids.

The five or six figures behind them clearly also weren't human.

The silver-skinned woman and the golden-furred man each gave a nod to Ouyang Kuishan, then sat down onto the cushions next to him before their entourage sat down as well.

Han Li had never seen these two people before, but it was clear that they were most likely also Golden Immortal Stage dao lords, while those accompanying them had to have been deputy dao lords as well.

Not long after their arrival, a woman in a black dress with a black veil concealing her face arrived atop a giant black crow steed.

In contrast with the previous dao lords to have arrived, she was doing so on her own without an entourage, and she gave Ouyang Kuishan a brief greeting before sitting down on a cushion not far away from him.

Immediately after her came a handsome man with a head of long golden hair, and he was accompanied by 15 or 16 deputy dao lords.

Over the course of the next hour, more and more dao lords and deputy dao lords arrived, and Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni only arrived when there were only two vacant cushions left in the front row to the left of the cauldron.

On this day, not only had Daoist Hu Yan changed into a pristine white robe, his hair was also immaculately groomed, and he was clean shaven as well, indicating that he was taking this event quite seriously.

Yun Ni was walking along beside him with a faint smile on her face, and she was still just as seductive as ever, with many of the dao lords and deputy dao lords unconsciously lowering their heads, not daring to look at her.

Ouyang Kuishan was rather taken aback to see Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni arriving together, and he rose to his feet for the first time after sitting down as he smiled and said, "Welcome, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan, Fellow Daoist Yun. Now that you're here, everyone has arrived."

"Surely we're not late, Dao Lord Baili isn't even here yet," Daoist Hu Yan said as he took a glance at Ouyang Kuishan.

"Indeed, but it's about time for the ceremony to begin, so please take your seats," Ouyang Kuishan said as he took a glance at Yun Ni.

Daoist Hu Yan gave an indifferent nod in response before making his way toward the two vacant cushions with Yun Ni.

Han Li remained seated with his legs crossed as his gaze roamed over all of these figures that he had never seen before. He discovered that aside from the silver-skinned woman and the golden-furred man, there was another demonic man among the 12 dao lords, while the rest were all human. As for the 36 deputy dao lords, the only ones who weren't human were the ones that had accompanied those two demonic dao lords here.

Out of all of these people, he only recognized a few, including Xiong Shan.

These people formed the core of the entire Blaze Dragon Dao, and at this moment, they were all gathered on the summit of the White Jade Peak. Even though they were all restraining their auras, everyone around the platform was still struck by a sense of asphyxiation.

The entire mountain summit had become even more quiet, while the atmosphere was also a little tense.

Around 15 minutes later, a burst of five-colored light suddenly appeared in the distant sky, enveloped within which was a huge five-colored camel, and it was rapidly approaching the scene.

The camel was around 1,000 feet in size with circles of five-colored runes inscribed all over its body, and the two humps on its back resembled a pair of small mountains. Seated atop one of the humps was an elderly man in a colorful robe.

"Yu Yangzi of the Five Light Temple has come to observe the ceremony," the elderly man declared as he approached the platform.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Yu Yangzi. You're still looking as fine as ever! Would you happen to have any surplus Five Light Pills? I've been wanting to get some for a very long time, but they've proved very elusive to find," Ouyang Kuishan greeted with a smile.

"Of course I always have some to spare for you, Fellow Daoist Ouyang! As long as it's not too much, I can certainly spare two or three vials," Yu Yangzi replied with a smile as he descended onto the white jade platform.

"Fantastic! I also have some Dense Summer Earth here. Are you interested, Fellow Daoist?" Ouyang Kuishan asked.

An elated look appeared on Yu Yangzi's face upon hearing this, and he hurriedly replied, "Really? I'm happy to take all of it off your hands, just state your price!"

"There's no hurry, Fellow Daoist Yu Yangzi. Once the ceremony is over, you can come to my cave abode, and we'll discuss the matter over some tea," Ouyang Kuishan said.

"Alright, I'll be sure to come," Yu Yangzi replied with a nod.

The Five Light Temple wasn't quite on the same level as the Blaze Dragon Dao, but it was still a vastly renowned sect in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and that was why he had been arranged a seat in the first row to the right of the cauldron.

Shortly thereafter, a vast expanse of black light swept in from the distant sky, containing a massive black inkstone with intricate floral designs engraved upon it, giving it a gorgeous appearance.

"Layman Mo of the Fleeing Palace has come to attend the preaching ceremony," a low and raspy voice declared from the inkstone.

After that, the inkstone abruptly vanished to reveal a black-skinned elderly man who was no more than five feet tall and was stroking his own thick beard.

"Welcome, Layman Mo," Ouyang Kuishan said as he rose to his feet and cupped his fist in a salute.

Layman Mo merely returned his salute in a half-hearted fashion before walking past him, and Ouyang Kuishan's expression stiffened ever so slightly, but he quickly recovered his composure and sat back down.

Meanwhile, Layman Mo approached Daoist Hu Yan with a wide smile as he asked, "Why haven't you come to my Fleeting Palace these past 10,000 years, you old drunk? Could it be that you've already forgotten this drinking buddy of yours?"

"You're one to talk! You went into seclusion for tens of thousands of years without coming out even once! I visited you so many times, only to be kept out like some unwelcome guest! Having said that, you really did come at the right time, I've saved up quite a bit of fine wine that's not inferior to your Ink Cloud Spirit Wine," Daoist Hu Yan declared with a proud expression.

A furious look immediately appeared on Layman Mo's face upon hearing this. "There's no wine in this world that's more delectable than the Ink Cloud Spirit Wine I've personally brewed! You haven't even had a drink yet, and you're already spouting drunk nonsense! When have you ever been able to acquire a wine that's superior to mine?"

"You can find out if my claims are true or not after the ceremony," Daoist Hu Yan replied, taking a glance at Yun Ni out of the corner of his eye as he spoke.

"Alright, you better not disappoint me."

A wide smile appeared on Layman Mo's face as he made his way over to the right side of the cauldron before taking a seat next to Yu Yangzi.

Before long, around a dozen of the cushions to the right of the cauldron had been occupied, while roughly half of them remained vacant.

This wasn't because there weren't that many people from other sects who wanted to attend the ceremony. On the contrary, the number of sects that wanted to be in attendance far surpassed this, but most of them were rather small and weak, so they had been arranged seats in other parts of the plaza.

The spots on the platform itself were limited, and it would've been rather unsightly for too many people to be crammed onto it.

Chapter 327: Five Decays

All of a sudden, a burst of laughter rang out in the distant sky, and a streak of blue light shot forth from afar, flying into the golden light barrier before hovering in the air outside of the white jade platform.

"Luo Qinghai of the Vast Flow Palace has come to attend the ceremony!"

An enormous blue flower that was around 1,000 feet in size bloomed within the burst of blue light with this declaration, and there were around a dozen figures standing atop the giant flower, all of whom were wearing the same blue robes and giving off formidable auras.

Everyone from the Blaze Dragon Dao instantly erupted into chatter upon seeing this.

Luo Qinghai was the current palace master of the Vast Flow Palace, which ranked alongside the Blaze Dragon Dao as one of the three leading powers of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

Han Li quickly recalled all of the information that he had read about the Vast Flow Palace as he also cast his gaze upward, just like everyone else.

Within the giant blue flower was a large golden throne, upon which sat a tall and thin middle-aged man with hair that was as white as snow.

He had a set of benevolent facial features, and his eyes were as blue as the sea, while his aura was as vast as the ocean, and even from this far away, Han Li still couldn't help but be alarmed by the man's formidable aura.

The dozen or so figures behind Luo Qinghai all appeared to have been very formidable as well.

One of them appeared to have been in his early twenties, and he had a very effeminate appearance with skin that was even fairer than that of a young maiden. If it weren't for the fact that his chest was completely flat, he could've easily been mistaken for a woman.

Even though he was also wearing a blue robe, unlike everyone else in the ground, there were golden waves embroidered onto his collar and sleeves, making his attire more similar in appearance to Luo Qinghai's.

"Welcome, Grand Palace Master Luo. Forgive me for not coming out to welcome you sooner," Ouyang Kuishan said as he rose to his feet and cupped his fist in a salute, while all of the other dao lords and deputy dao lords stood up as well.

"It's a very rare occasion that Fellow Daoist Baili comes out of seclusion, and he always has very unique insights on the five decays. All of his preaching ceremonies are extremely prestigious events in our Northern Glacial Immortal Realm, so I certainly couldn't miss it," Luo Qinghai replied with a smile.

Luo Qinghai and Ouyang Kuishan made some small talk, and instead of descending onto the preaching platform like everyone else, Luo Qinghai remained in the air atop his giant blue flower, hovering at the same height as the preaching platform.

Not long after the arrival of the Vast Flow Palace, a silver chariot that was drawn by eight silver-scaled dragon horses came flying in from afar. There were around seven or eight people on the carriage, and it remained hovering in mid-air on the other side of the platform.

"The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace has come to attend the ceremony," a beautiful woman on the carriage declared.

"This is truly an honor, Deputy Palace Master Xue Ying," Ouyang Kuishan greeted as he rose to his feet, but it was clear that he wasn't particularly fond of the new arrivals.

The other Golden Immortal dao lords also seemed to have been rather disdainful of everyone from the Immortal Palace, merely taking a glance at them before looking away.

The cultivators of the Immortal Palace didn't appear to have been bothered by this, and they extended a greeting toward Luo Qinghai before hovering in the air on the other side of the preaching platform.

Following the arrival of the other two leading powers of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, there were no further new arrivals.

Another 15 minutes or so passed by, and Ouyang Kuishan spoke to several of the dao lords beside him briefly, then rose his feet and swept his gaze across the vast crowds of people gathered around the plaza as he declared, "It's time. Welcome, Dao Lord Baili!"

His voice wasn't very loud, but it was extremely clear, as if he were speaking right beside everyone on the plaza.

In the next instant, everyone rose to their feet, including those on the platform.

"Welcome, Dao Lord Baili!" all of the elders and disciples of the Blaze Dragon Dao yelled in unison, causing the entire plaza to buzz and tremble.

In the next instant, layers of strange ripples suddenly began to appear in the sky, and a crimson fireball slowly emerged, then turned from red to golden in color, glowing as radiantly as the sun.

At the same time, a burst of enormous spiritual pressure erupted out of the ball of fire, and the entirety of the White Jade Peak instantly fell completely silent.

Immediately thereafter, a humanoid figure stepped out of the ball of fire and onto the tall platform.

The man appeared to have been no more than 30 to 40 years of age, and his skin was slightly red in coloration and glowing brightly like a piece of flawless crimson jade.

He stood tall and proud with an authoritative look on his face, and he had a head of long crimson hair that was arranged inside a gold mesh crown. He was also dressed in a fiery red robe that was riddled with draconic embroidery, and it was none other than the number one dao lord of the Blaze Dragon Dao, the man who was said to have only been one step away from the High Zenith Stage, Baili Yan!

"Brother Luo, if I recall correctly, it's been over 100,000 years since we last met in the battle in the Hidden Azure Sea," Baili Yan said with a smile as he cast his gaze toward the Vast Flow Palace camp.

"If you hadn't gone into seclusion so quickly, the two of us could've had plenty of time to meet and chat," Luo Qinghai jibed.

"You're here as well, Deputy Palace Master Xue Ying!" Baili Yan greeted as he turned to the Immortal Palace camp.

"You're looking as handsome as ever, Dao Lord Baili. Now that you've come out of seclusion, I'm sure you're even closer to the High Zenith Stage. Allow me to offer you my congratulations in advance," the woman by the name of Xue Ying replied with a nod.

"I'm afraid your congratulations may be premature, Fellow Daoist Xue Ying. If the High Zenith Stage were that easy to reach, then I wouldn't have gone to the trouble of going into seclusion so many times," Baili Yan chuckled, while Xue Ying merely smiled in response.

"I'm very honored to be hosting all of you here today. During this ceremony, I'm going to be sharing my cultivation experiences and insights in the hope that I can help you all further your own cultivation."

He swept his gaze calmly across the crowd gathered all over the White Jade Peak as he spoke, much like an emperor inspecting his own empire, giving off an unmatched sense of majesty and regal authority.

After that, he turned around and flew onto the platform, taking a seat with his legs crossed behind the purple table at its center.

The dozens of Blaze Dragon Dao dao lords and deputy lords and the cultivators from the Blaze Dragon Dao's allied sects were seated on either side of him, making him resemble a bright moon surrounded by stars.

The sound of a loud gong being struck three times in succession rang out, and a peculiar burst of fluctuations instantly spread over the entire mountain range.

Han Li was immediately instilled with a sense of calmness upon hearing this sound, and what little remained of the background noise quickly died down to result in complete silence.

Baili Yan cast his gaze directly forward as he began to speak, and his voice was surprisingly smooth and mellow.

His voice didn't appear to have been remarkable in any way, and those who were further away from him were initially struggling to hear him, but it didn't take long before his voice began to reverberate around the entire mountain.

His words were echoing incessantly, striking deep into the hearts of the listeners like the tolls of a giant bell, or like the mantric chantings of the Buddha.

Everyone was immersed in this unique sound, and as for exactly what Baili Yan was saying, it was becoming a little indistinct.

However, this immersive atmosphere struck everyone with a sense of comfort both in the body and the soul, and many people could feel their magic power circulation becoming a lot smoother, while certain bottlenecks were beginning to loosen.

However, most of the people experiencing this were at or below the Grand Ascension Stage, while everyone at the True Immortal Stage and above weren't benefitting anywhere near as much.

As for Han Li, he was able to roughly understand what was being preached, but he was not experiencing any profound sensation like everyone else.

The reason for this was his enormous spiritual sense, which was even more formidable than that of the average Golden Immortal. As a result of this, the preaching of a late-Golden Immortal Stage dao lord wasn't enough to place him into an entranced state of immersion.

Furthermore, the preaching of the portly monk on the wall of light manifested by the Eye of Truth and the Heaven Controlling Vial was far more profound, and in comparison, Han Li was left feeling a little disappointed.

However, he didn't outwardly express his disappointment, merely sitting on his cushion with his legs crossed and meditating with his eyes closed.

After all, this was still the preaching of someone on the verge of reaching the High Zenith Stage, so it was still going to be somewhat beneficial to him.

As time passed, noon quickly arrived, and Baili Yan's voice was still reverberating across the entire mountain.

In fact, it was audible even in White Jade City, and everyone in the city had stopped to listen, making the usually lively and bustling city uncharacteristically quiet.

"...Among the five decays, True Immortals must face three without fail, and those trials will either lead to one's demise or rebirth. Only by cultivating arduously can one hope to..."

At this point in Baili Yan's preaching, all of the True Immortals on the platform were leaning forward slightly, listening intently with focused looks on their faces.

Even the Golden Immortals present had sat up a little straighter to listen to what he had to say.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and a hint of befuddlement appeared in his eyes.

He turned to look at Qi Liang to find that he was just focusing just as intently as all of the other True Immortals, seemingly latching onto Baili Yan's every word.

After a brief moment of hesitation, Han Li took advantage of a pause in Baili Yan's preaching to raise a question to Qi Liang through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Qi, may I ask what these three decays and five decays are?"

Qi Liang immediately turned to him with an incredulous expression. "You're unaware of the three decays of the True Immortal Stage?"

"Please enlighten me, Brother Qi," Han Li said.

Chapter 328: Kept in the Dark

"In the eyes of cultivators at or below the Grand Ascension Stage, True Immortals have already reached the end point of cultivation and have ascended to the highest of heights, but as we all know, the True Immortal Stage is only the first step through the door of immortality, and in reality, there are still far loftier heights to be conquered.

“While it's true that we possess limitless lifespans, we are not actually truly immortal, and the reason for that is precisely the tribulation of the three decays," Qi Liang explained to Han Li through voice transmission while also listening to Baili Yan's preaching.

"Oh? Are the three decays similar in nature to the ascension tribulation that Grand Ascension cultivators must transcend? And how do we transcend them?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"The three decays are referred to as tribulations, but they have nothing to do with the ascension tribulation. Instead, they describe the three crises that all True Immortal cultivators will face during the course of their cultivation. The first of those is immortal decay, which results in one's immortal spiritual power seeping away for no discernible reason, thereby damaging one's cultivation base until they fall out of the True Immortal Stage altogether.

“The second decay is bodily decay, which results in the gradual weakening of one's body until it's no longer able to hold immortal spiritual power, thereby resulting in the body's detonation. The third decay is acupoint decay, and it's related to one's immortal acupoints. There are many ways to contend against these three tribulations, but their effects vary from person to person.

“However, one universal way to ward off the decays that works for everyone is to make significant progress in a certain law," Qi Liang explained.

"I see. No wonder all True Immortal cultivators are so desperate to master law powers. Aside from enhancing their own powers, I presume the more urgent priority is actually to combat the three decays. When will the three decays happen? Or do certain conditions need to be met for them to arise?" Han Li asked.

His expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was feeling quite shocked. Perhaps it was due to his prior bout of amnesia, but he wasn't aware of this at all, and only after hearing this explanation from Qi Liang did he come to realize that even True Immortal cultivators couldn't just be content and rest on their laurels.

"The timing of the first two decay tribulations is completely down to the will of the heavens. Some are fortunate enough to avoid them for millions of years, while others could encounter them in less than 100,000 years. I'm sure you still recall Elder Fang Zhuan of the Merit Conveyance Palace, right?

“He was once a mid-True Immortal cultivator and was only one step away from opening up 24 immortal acupoints, but he was blighted by immortal decay and forced all the way back down to the Grand Ascension Stage," Qi Liang revealed.

"Does that mean that if one progresses sufficiently quickly in their cultivation and reaches the Golden Immortal Stage in a very short time, then they'll be able to avoid those two decays?" Han Li asked.

"That is indeed true. If someone can reach the Golden Immortal Stage within 10,000 years, then the chances of them being struck by those two types of decay are naturally extremely slim, but how many people in the Immortal Realm are capable of accomplishing such a feat?

“ It's already extremely remarkable for someone to reach the mid-True Immortal Stage in just 10,000 years. On top of that, even if a True Immortal manages to avoid the first two decays, if they want to reach the Golden Immortal Stage, then they'll have no choice but to face the third decay," Qi Liang said with a wry smile.

"Why is that?" Han Li asked.

"All I know is that all those attempting breakthroughs to the Golden Immortal Stage will inevitably have to undergo the third decay, and that it's no less damning than the first two decays. That's why there are so few Golden Immortal cultivators. As for exactly why this is, that's beyond my knowledge," Qi Liang replied.

"I heard Dao Lord Baili mention just now that there are five decays. What are the other two?" Han Li asked.

"It's said that after becoming a Golden Immortal, one will face two more decays to amount to a total of five. As for exactly what those two decays are, I'm not sure. In any case, the path of cultivation is truly one that is fraught with..."

Before Qi Liang had a chance to finish his sentence, eight of the 12 Blaze Dragon Dao dao lords suddenly sprang up from their cushions before sweeping their sleeves through the air.

The sound of clanging chains interrupted the peace and quiet as the eight dao lords, led by Ouyang Kuishan, released eight golden chains out of their sleeves.

Each chain was around the same thickness as a child's arm, and they were riddled with shimmering golden runes as they flashed through the air like a nest of spirit snakes.

The chains were aimed directly at Baili Yan, whose expression remained unchanged, but his preaching had drawn to an abrupt halt.

All of a sudden, a burst of crimson light rose up from the ground all around him, enveloping his body from all directions like a fiery red light barrier.

The chains scraped against the exterior of the light barrier, raising trails of sparks as they did so, but they were unable to get any closer to Baili Yan's body.

At the same time, Baili Yan stomped a foot down onto the ground, and a burst of crimson light erupted beneath his foot. The entire white jade platform also shuddered violently, yet right as he was about to launch himself up into the heavens, the eight dao lords hurriedly each made a hand seal, upon which the golden chains began to glow brightly while constricting tightly to keep Baili Yan and the crimson light barrier firmly in place.

As a result, Baili Yan was forced back down onto the platform.

A burst of crimson light emerged on his hands as he grabbed toward the surrounding golden chains, only for countless arcs of golden lightning to erupt out of the chains before surging along his arms.

Baili Yan felt a numbing sensation shoot through his arms, and he temporarily lost all feeling in them.

At the same time, the arcs of lightning that were springing out of the golden chains had intertwined to form a square golden cage that trapped him within.

Even though Baili Yan was able to immediately regain use of his arms, due to that split second of delay, it had become far more difficult for him to try and break free.

At this moment, every single golden pillar in the golden cage around him was flashing with lightning, and layers of scale patterns and antiquated runes had appeared on their surface, giving off clear law fluctuations.

These eight golden chains were clearly a set of high-grade immortal treasures that had been prepared specifically to deal with Baili Yan.

All of this had happened in the blink of an eye, unfolding so quickly and abruptly that none of the tens of thousands of cultivators around the plaza had even registered what had just happened.

The 36 deputy dao lords were greatly alarmed to see this, and all of them began to exchange bewildered glances. It was clear that they hadn't been tipped off in advance at all.

On the other side, Yu Yangzi and the others were also very much taken aback by this turn of events, and all of them rose to their feet.

Some of them wanted to ask what was happening, but the atmosphere in the air was rather peculiar, so they ultimately decided to hold their tongues.

Just like everyone else, Han Li was watching the unfolding situation with a perplexed look on his face.

"What's going on?" Qi Liang asked with tightly furrowed brows.

On the white jade platform, Daoist Hu Yan stepped forward with a furious expression, only for two other dao lords to immediately get in his way.

"What are you all doing? Are you betraying the sect?" Daoist Hu Yan asked in a furious voice.

A hint of guilt flashed through the faces of all of the dao lords who had taken action, but none of them said anything, and the two dao lords standing in Daoist Hu Yan's way displayed no intention of backing down.

An alarmed and furious look had also appeared on Yun Ni's face, and she had distanced herself slightly from the dao lords beside her, unsure of who she could trust.

Given the current situation, it appeared that she and Daoist Hu Yan were the only ones who had been kept in the dark.

Inside the cage, Baili Yan slowly swept his gaze across everyone around him, and a burst of crimson light began to emerge on his arms.

A burst of scorching flames then erupted out of his arms to envelop the surrounding golden chains, and under the illumination of the flames, his already smooth and pristine skin was made to appear like crimson jade.

"This Golden Scale Dragon Locking Array won't be able to trap me for long, so if you have anything else to throw at me, you better do it now," Baili Yan said in a cold voice.

However, all of the dao lords remained silent, and it was as if they had agreed in advance not to respond to anything that Baili Yan said.

Up to this point, all of the Blaze Dragon Dao disciples outside the plaza still had no idea what was happening, and they could only watch as the situation unfolded.

As for the elders from other sects who had come to attend the ceremony, they were also oblivious to what had happened, but they could sense that this was no laughing matter, and all of them remained seated, not daring to make any sudden moves.

Atop the giant blue flower that was hovering in the sky next to the white jade platform, Luo Qinghai had already risen to his feet from his golden throne, and he was watching the scenes unfolding on the platform with his brows tightly furrowed.

The effeminate young man behind him approached him, then said, "Palace Master, should we..."

"There's no hurry, let's watch the situation unfold first. If this is an internal affair of the Blaze Dragon Dao, then it would be best for us not to get involved," Luo Qinghai said with a shake of his head.

Right at this moment, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he cast his gaze upward.

As it turned out, a golden line that was several thousand feet in length had suddenly appeared high up in the sky, and it swelled rapidly into a vast expanse of blinding golden light, from within which a group of 20 to 30 figures emerged.

They were led by a tall man with a square face and a thin and long silver mustache. The man was wearing a pristine white robe with golden cloud patterns embroidered upon it, and those patterns were giving off dazzling spiritual light, indicating that this was no ordinary robe.

Hovering in the air behind him were 20 to 30 men and women, most of whom were also wearing white robes, with only very few of them dressed in different attire. However, one thing that was common to all of them was their auras were extremely formidable, and their collective spiritual pressure struck one with a crushing sense of asphyxiation.

All of the cultivators of the Blaze Dragon Dao were already bewildered by everything that they were seeing, and this certainly didn't help to settle their nerves.

Chapter 329: Wanted Fugitive of the Reincarnation Palace

As soon as the man with the silver mustache appeared, the expressions of everyone on the white jade platform instantly changed drastically, with the exception of the 10 dao lords.

As for all of the elders and disciples situated on the plaza and the surrounding stone steps, all of them were rather dazed and confused, clearly having no idea of what this group of white-robed figures were going to do.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and his mind was racing.

He didn't know who these people were, but he could tell that the man with the silver mustache was definitely no ordinary cultivator, and his powers most likely weren't inferior to Baili Yan's.

As for why the 10 dao lords had suddenly decided to betray Baili Yan, that most likely had everything to do with this man, but he couldn't figure out what the motive of Ouyang Kuishan and the others was.

Even though Baili Yan was the Blaze Dragon Dao's first dao lord and its most powerful cultivator, he was constantly in seclusion and barely oversaw any matters in the Blaze Dragon Dao at all, so those who actually controlled the sect and benefited most from its resources were the other dao lords. There was no conflict of interest between the parties, and in fact, the dao lords benefited from the protection that Baili Yan provided to the sect.

While it appeared that he had been trapped for now, he hadn't been injured at all, so given sufficient time, there was a very good chance that he would be able to break free from his bindings, and once that happened, even the 10 dao lords combined definitely wouldn't have been a match for him.

However, the situation had taken a complete turn with the arrival of these white-robed figures, and Han Li could detect the minute changes in the expressions of Ouyang Kuishan and the others.

However, ultimately, none of this had anything to do with him, and he certainly didn't want to be swept up in this mess.

Having said that, he couldn't afford to act reckless given the current circumstances, so he would have to wait and see.

As these thoughts were flashing through his mind, he was sweeping his gaze across the people in the sky, trying to see if he could gather any more visual information about them.

However, right as his gaze fell upon a young man holding a folding fan standing among the people behind the man with the silver mustache, his mind was suddenly struck by a burst of sharp pain.

He couldn't help lower his head while massaging his own temples to try and alleviate the pain.

The young man was very handsome and was wearing a tight-fitting silver robe with intricate designs of flora and fauna embroidered upon it.

He was holding a white jade folding fan with an amicable smile on his face. He casually looked down from above, sweeping his gaze over the crowd down below before directing his gaze to the white jade platform.

After massaging his own temples for a while, Han Li seemed to have regained his composure somewhat, but there was a look of bewilderment in his eyes.

Right at this moment, Xue Ying suddenly extended a respectful curtsey toward the man with the silver mustache as she greeted, "Xue Ying pays her respects to the palace master."

Everyone erupted into chatter upon hearing this.

Xue Ying was the deputy palace master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so the man that she was referring to as palace master naturally had to have been Xiao Jinhan, the current palace master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

Xiao Jinhan gave her a slight nod, then turned his attention to the golden cage down below, where his gaze just so happened to meet Baili Yan's.

A mocking sneer appeared on his face, while a cold look flashed through Baili Yan's eyes.

On the platform, Yu Yangzi and Layman Mo exchanged a glance, and both of them could see their own apprehension mirrored in one another's eyes. Both of them slowly began to move away from the center of the platform for fear of getting swept up in whatever was about to come.

Everyone else at the center of the platform also followed suit to vacate the entire area.

"Prior to this, I saw it as inappropriate for me to get involved in this matter as I thought it was an internal affair of the Blaze Dragon Dao, but it seems like the Northern Glacial Immortal Region is now getting involved. I believe you owe everyone an explanation for this, Palace Master Xiao," Luo Qinghai declared.

"Baili Yan is a wanted fugitive of the Reincarnation Palace being hunted by the Heavenly Court, and I've been ordered to apprehend him. Is that enough of an explanation for you, Fellow Daoist Luo?" Xiao Jinhan replied in a cold voice.

He swept a hand through the air as he spoke, and a streak of golden light that contained a golden scroll flew through the air.

The scroll then unfurled itself in a flash to reveal a passage of golden text, and sure enough, it was a wanted notice directed at Baili Yan.

All of the True Immortals of the Blaze Dragon Dao were rather befuddled by the mention of the Reincarnation Palace, clearly having no idea of what that was supposed to have been. Even Yu Yangzi was rather puzzled by what he was hearing, while only Layman Mo and Luo Qinghai seemed to have been aware of what was being discussed.

The former apologized to Daoist Hu Yan through voice transmission, then flew out of the white jade platform.

At the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon that giant inkstone before flying away atop the treasure, unwilling to stay for even a moment longer.

As for Luo Qinghai, his brows furrowed even tighter upon seeing this, and he took a long glance at Baili Yan as he fell completely silent, but didn't appear to have had any plans of leaving right away.

Yu Yangzi and the others certainly weren't fools, either, and they immediately fled into the distance, knowing that this wasn't something that was wise for them to get involved in.

Only a few of them were unable to suppress their curiosity and only flew several hundred kilometers before stopping and turning around again to observe the unfolding situation from afar, and none of the cultivators from the Northern Glacial Immortal Region raised any objections to this.

Baili Yan withdrew his gaze, then turned to the dao lords who had trapped him as he asked, "Are all of you going to betray me?"

Crimson flames were surging over his body, releasing waves of astonishing heat that were constantly scorching the golden chains, but the chains remained completely still and weren't showing any signs of melting.

However, it was clearly not an easy task for Ouyang Kuishan and the others to keep the chains in place, as evidenced by the sheens of sweat that had appeared on their foreheads. None of them dared to relax in the slightest as they maintained their hand seals, doing everything in their power to stabilize the golden chains.

"Fellow Daoist Baili, our Blaze Dragon Dao is indeed quite a formidable sect, but we can't contend against the Immortal Palace. They have the backing of the Heavenly Court! What do we have? We can't just stand by and watch as the entire Blaze Dragon Dao is destroyed with you," Ouyang Kuishan sighed.

"What about all of you? Do you share the same opinion?" Baili Yan asked as he turned to the 36 deputy dao lords behind him, all of which immediately lowered their heads, unwilling to meet his gaze.

Meanwhile, all of the people on the stone staircase around the platform had been placed in a very awkward situation.

No matter how oblivious they were to the nature of the situation, at this point, it was clear that something was very wrong here.

Many of the people present were considering leaving the White Jade Peak. After all, they certainly didn't want to get swept up in a battle between Golden Immortals. As for the cultivators of the Immortal Palace, they appeared to have been quite calm and collected, but they were constantly watching the people down below with alert looks in their eyes.

Han Li was looking up at the cultivators of the Immortal Palace, just like many of the people around him, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

At this point, Qi Liang had also fallen silent. It was clear that this was not a situation that a True Immortal Stage elder like him could play any meaningful role in.

All of a sudden, the entire platform had become completely silent, and the atmosphere had become extremely tense.

"Ouyang Kuishan, what are you waiting for?" Xiao Jinhan suddenly urged in an authoritative voice.

Ouyang Kuishan and the others offered no response, but all of them immediately sprang into action, making a string of hand seals with one hand while holding onto golden chains with the other.

A burst of formidable energy fluctuations erupted out of their bodies, spreading through the entire surrounding space in a radius of dozens of kilometers. All of the space within this area was visibly rippling, causing the scene to become rather blurry and unclear.

Within the rippling space, the surface of the golden cage was flashing incessantly with golden light. At the same time, thin golden threads were emerging from the cage, piercing toward Baili Yan like a mass of countless feelers.

Right at this moment, a huge snow lotus flower projection abruptly appeared amid a flash of white light behind one of the chain-wielding dao lords.

Ouyang Kuishan spotted this out of the corner of his eye, and he immediately yelled out in alarm, "Yun Ni, stop!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a pristine white hand that was as translucent as jade abruptly extended out of the lotus flower projection before striking the dao lord on the back.

There was a translucent bead situated at the center of the palm, and in the instant that it came into contact with the dao lord's back, it abruptly exploded, releasing a burst of dazzling white light alongside gusts of ferocious wind.

The dao lord in question was focusing most of his attention on the chain in his hand, and everyone else was primarily keeping an eye on Daoist Hu Yan, so no one had anticipated that Yun Ni would suddenly strike.

Thus, the dao lord was caught completely off guard, and he didn't have time to summon any treasures, so he could only release a layer of protective spiritual light before the palm struck him on the back.

A loud thump rang out as the spiritual light around the dao lord's body was dispelled, and he immediately threw up a mouthful of blood as he was launched forward like a kite with a snapped string, crashing into the golden cage around Baili Yan.

He was still gripping tightly onto the golden chain with one hand, but the hand seal he was making with his other hand had already unraveled.

In the next instant, the surface of the golden cage shuddered, and Baili Yan erupted into raucous laughter as two beams of crimson light erupted out of his eyes.

At the same time, his aura also swelled drastically.

High up in the sky, Xiao Jinhan gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a shimmering golden rune, which flew directly toward the golden cage like an arrow while giving off bursts of law fluctuations.

Daoist Hu Yan immediately sprang into action as well upon seeing this, raising a hand to release an azure ball that was riddled with runes. At the same time, he bit through the tip of his own tongue before spitting out a mouthful of blood essence.

Almost at the exact same moment, the dao lord standing in his way raised both hands up into the air, releasing a golden wheel that erupted into the heavens, hurtling directly toward the azure ball, while the other dao lords outside of the eight that were maintaining the golden cage flew toward Yun Ni.

Daoist Hu Yan quickly made a hand seal, and fuelled by his blood essence, a series of golden veins instantly lit up on the azure ball.

Immediately thereafter, it vanished into thin air in a flash, leaving the golden wheel far behind.

In the next instant, the azure ball reappeared near the golden rune, and at the same time, the golden veins on its surface reached the peak of their brightness, following which the azure ball exploded, releasing a vast cloud of azure mist that swept through the air in all directions with tremendous force.

Before the cloud of azure mist had a chance to disperse, a streak of golden light suddenly flashed past beneath it, and the golden rune continued to fly toward the cage, completely unscathed.

Right as it was about to land upon the golden cage, a streak of transparent swordlight that was invisible to the naked eye struck the golden rune with unerring accuracy like a stream of water.

The streak of swordlight dissipated upon making contact with the golden rune, but it was able to knock the rune off its original path.

It was still descending from above, but its trajectory was no longer one that could allow it to land on the cage.

All of this sounded like a long process, but in reality, it had all taken place in the blink of an eye.

Chapter 330: Chaos

The entire scene was completely silent.

Not only were the low-grade cultivators on the plaza stunned beyond belief, all of the Blaze Dragon Dao cultivators situated on the stone steps were also astonished by what they were seeing.

A hint of blue light flashed through Han Li's eyes, and he was able to see everything that had just taken place.

The golden rune released by Xiao Jinhan was very elusive, able to completely ignore that attack from Daoist Hu Yan, but it was nullified by the streak of transparent swordlight released by Luo Qinghai.

Officially speaking, the Immortal Palace was the dominant power in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but it clearly had some differences with the Vast Flow Palace. At the very least, Luo Qinghai didn't seem to have been a fan of Xiao Jinhan.

High up in the sky, Xiao Jinhan took a cold glance at Luo Qinghai, and his expression remained unchanged as he swooped down directly toward the white jade platform from above.

Meanwhile, Luo Qinghai slowly withdrew his right hand, which was concealed up his sleeve,then turned around and sat back down onto his golden throne.

The giant blue flower that he was situated on remained hovering in the sky, and he still wasn't displaying any intention of departing. The dozen or so blue-robed cultivators standing on the giant flower with him also appeared to have been just as calm and collected as he was.

Before Xiao Jinhan was able to descend upon the white jade platform, a draconic roar abruptly rang out, and scorching flames erupted out of Baili Yan's eyes as he curled his fingers up into claws, then abruptly lashed out at the golden cage before him.

Crimson flames rose up from his claws, then rose up to form a peculiar draconic head, which blasted a pillar of fire out of its mouth to strike a certain part of the golden cage.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as one of the pillars of the golden cage was swallowed up by the draconic head's cavernous mouth.

Golden runes were constantly flying out of the scorching flames, while the pillar was warping and twisting until it finally snapped.

The destruction of that one pillar caused a chain reaction, and all of the other golden pillars quickly shattered one after another, causing the entire golden cage to collapse.

A burst of dazzling golden light erupted forth on the white jade platform, following which several dozen draconic head projections flew in all directions, releasing a tremendously powerful aura as they did so.

Specks of golden light arose in the air, and immediately thereafter, the light barrier that enshrouded the entire mountain was completely destroyed amid a resounding boom.

Half of the white jade platform down below was also destroyed, and the eight dao lords who were previously holding the golden cage together hurriedly summoned protective treasures as a defensive measure, but they were still sent flying back involuntarily.

Several of them were struck by the draconic head projections, and the light barriers formed by their protective treasures were instantly destroyed, causing them to tumble down from the platform while throwing up large mouthfuls of blood.

Meanwhile, Daoist Hu Yan arrived by Yun Ni's side in a flash, warding off several oncoming draconic head projections while sweeping her down from the white jade platform with him.

Even though there were around a dozen dao lords acting as a buffer, the 36 deputy dao lords were still sent flying in all directions from the shockwaves of the explosion that had just taken place, but they took advantage of this to fly further away.

All of the cultivators on the stone steps also dispersed in a panic, flying away in all directions as quickly as they could. No one wanted to be the first person to try and flee for fear of being struck down by the Immortal Palace's cultivators, but now that the entire scene had erupted into complete pandemonium, an opportunity had arisen for everyone to get away.

Han Li and Qi Liang also fled the scene in a certain direction with the crowd.

Countless loose rocks were exploding in all directions, much to the alarm of the hundreds of thousands of low-grade cultivators gathered around the plaza, and they also hurriedly summoned their protective treasures while fleeing as quickly as they could.

All of a sudden, countless streaks of light of different colors were flying in all directions from the White Jade Peak, presenting a marvelous spectacle to behold.

In the sky above, Luo Qinghai made a hand seal to conjure up a blue water barrier that encompassed the entire giant blue flower, and the water barrier merely shuddered momentarily in the face of the shockwaves before settling down again.

On the other side, Deputy Palace Master Xue Ying of the Immortal Palace swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a semi-transparent protective barrier around the silver chariot, then cast her gaze toward Luo Qinghai.

However, Luo Qinghai appeared to have been completely oblivious to her scrutiny, looking as calm and collected as ever.

As for Xiao Jinhan, he paid no heed to the oncoming shockwaves at all, and he wasn't slowing down in the slightest as he continued to swoop down from above.

Another loud explosion rang out as a vast expanse of glacial qi erupted out of Xiao Jinhan's body, and a giant white mountain of ice appeared in the sky amid a cloud of white mist, then crashed down onto the white jade platform with devastating might.

Half of the platform had already collapsed, and under the tremendous weight and momentum of the mountain of ice, the rest of the platform also fell away without being able to offer much resistance.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already flown out of the White Jade Peak and was observing the unfolding scene from afar.

Loose rocks and chunks of ice had already piled up into a huge mountain in that direction, presenting a chaotic sight to behold.

Right at this moment, burst of crimson light suddenly appeared beneath the rubble, and immediately thereafter, a sharp clang rang out as a pillar of crimson flames that was around as thick as an adult human arm erupted directly upward from the wreckage before sweeping vertically over the area to slice the mountain of ice and rocks in half down the middle.

A loud roar then rang out as Baili Yan flew out of the mountain of ice with crimson flames surging all over his body, and he was flying directly toward Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

With a flick of his wrist, Xiao Jinhan summoned a translucent longsword, around which was a band of white mist that resembled a coiled snake, and he slashed the sword in Baili Yan's direction.

The cloud up above churned violently as hundreds of giant white pythons formed by glacial qi twisted and writhed, descending upon Baili Yan like a flight of formidable dragons.

Baili Yan let loose another thunderous roar, and he lashed out with a longsword that was enveloped in crimson flames, slashing it horizontally through the air.

A scorching aura swept through the air as hundreds of giant pillars of flames emerged out of thin air to combat the glacial pythons.

A burst of rumbling akin to a dull thunderclap rang out in the sky as snow and ice clashed with devastating force, and each side was taking up half of the sky.

Meanwhile, the plaza had already erupted into complete chaos.

High up in the sky, Xue Ying suddenly asked in an accusatory voice, "Are you trying to stand against our Immortal Palace, Palace Master Mo?"

Only then did Luo Qinghai finally turn to Xue Ying as he replied in a casual voice, "What are you talking about, Celestial Maiden Xue? I'm only spectating with a few of my disciples, and I don't wish to play any part in the conflict between your Immortal Palace and the Blaze Dragon Dao."

Xue Ying offered no response to this, instead turning to a pair of cultivators beside her as she instructed, "Lu Yue, Dong Jie, take everyone and go and keep an eye on Daoist Hu Yan."

The two cultivators immediately heeded the order, setting off with all of the other cultivators situated on the chariot.

"I'll be going ahead, Grand Palace Master Luo," Xue Ying said as she stowed the silver chariot away before flying off in pursuit of Xiao Jinhan and Baili Yan as a streak of white light.

……

At this point, the plaza around the White Jade Peak was already severely ravaged and littered with lifeless bodies.

Daoist Hu Yan was hovering in mid-air with Yun Ni beside him, and both of them were watching the battle taking place between Baili Yan and Xiao Jinhan.

Right at this moment, a huge black ax projection descended out of the sky, releasing a burst of tremendous suction force that caused the surrounding space to twist and warp.

Daoist Hu Yan seemed to have already anticipated this as he took a step forward and dragged Yun Ni closer to his side, evading the attack with ease.

After missing its target, the giant ax projection crashed down onto the ground with an earth-shattering boom, slicing a massive, bottomless trench that was over 10,000 feet in length into the ground on the plaza.

Many of the low-grade cultivators who hadn't been able to get away yet were swept up by the attack, perishing on the spot before they even had a chance to cry out.

Immediately thereafter, the man by the name of Dong Jie raised his enormous mountain-splitting ax with both hands before swinging it down once again.

At the same time, the seven Immortal Palace cultivators, led by Dong Jie, suddenly appeared around the plaza to surround Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

Earlier, they had somehow managed to conceal their cultivation bases, and at this moment, all of them were giving off Golden Immortal Stage spiritual pressure. In particular, Lu Yue and Dong Jie's aura's indicated that they were at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage.

They held no regard for the safety of the people who still hadn't yet managed to escape from the plaza, and they summoned a whole host of formidable treasures to rain down a ferocious barrage of attacks.

The entire space was trembling violently as countless anguished cries rang out from all directions, with deaths and casualties piling up by the second.

A complex look appeared on Ouyang Kuishan's face as he took a glance at the chaotic scene unfolding on the plaza, and he turned to the dao lords beside him as he instructed, "Evacuate our sect's disciples and try to save as many of them as possible."

Even though they had been struck by the shockwaves from when Baili Yan broke free from the cage, they remained largely unscathed, and they immediately dispersed, calling upon some of the deputy dao lords and True Immortal Stage elders who were still on the scene, and together, they began evacuating the Blaze Dragon Dao's low-grade disciples from around the plaza in batches.

At the center of the plaza, Yun Ni conjured up her snow lotus flower projection to encompass both herself and Daoist Hu Yan.

Countless attacks were raining down incessantly upon the snow lotus flower projection, and its petals were constantly trembling, looking as if they weren't going to be able to hold up for much longer.

Meanwhile, Daoist Hu Yan summoned a black pagoda treasure, then tapped a finger against it, instantly conjuring up a black pagoda projection that encompassed the snow lotus flower projection around them.

A string of loud clangs rang out as the oncoming attacks struck the pagoda projection, while Daoist Hu Yan turned to Yun Ni with a pained look in his eyes. "I have my reasons for why I must follow Dao Lord Baili, and that's why I helped him, but you don't know anything about that, and you could've easily chosen to save yourself, so why have you gotten yourself involved in this mess?"

Chapter 331: Slaughter

A faint smile appeared on Yun Ni's face upon hearing this, and she said, "Is it because of the Reincarnation Palace? While it's true that I don't know about all of that, that's not important. As long as I can be with you, that's enough. Thankfully, Suyuan is with Fengyi, so I don't have to worry about her."

Daoist Hu Yan burst into laughter upon hearing this. "Alright, in that case, let's take on these Immortal Palace small fry together!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, an earth-shattering boom rang out from above, and a golden sword projection came plunging straight down from the heavens to strike the black pagoda projection, shattering the roof of the pagoda projection while also causing the entire projection to shudder violently.

At the same time, a crack also appeared on the miniature pagoda treasure in Daoist Hu Yan's hand.

He looked up into the sky to find Lu Yue hovering up above with golden light swirling around his body, and there were several massive sword projections around him that were constantly swinging down upon the black pagoda projection.

Meanwhile, Dong Jie and the other Immortal Palace cultivators were also constantly raining attacks down upon the black pagoda projection, and they were being joined by around a dozen of the Immortal Palace cultivators that had accompanied Xiao Jinhan here. They were led by a woman in a pink palace dress who was also a mid-Golden Immortal cultivator.

Daoist Hu Yan gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, then patted his own waist, and the silver gourd strapped to his belt immediately flew out of the snow lotus flower projection before swelling rapidly to the size of a house as it hovered in mid-air.

Immediately thereafter, Daoist Hu Yan began to chant an incantation, and the spirit patterns on the surface of the giant silver gourd began to flash erratically, while a burst of indistinct white light appeared at its opening.

A stream of black beans came pouring out of the white light, and in the blink of an eye,. the entire sky was filled with black beans that were raining down from the heavens.

Even before landing on the ground, the beans warped and elongated, transforming into a series of Dao Warriors that were at around 10 feet tall, dressed in black clothes and wielding giant black axes.

In the blink of an eye, tens of thousands of these Dao Warriors had taken shape, and they were rushing toward the oncoming Immortal Palace cultivators in a frenzy.

Even though most of the Blaze Dragon Dao disciples had already been evacuated from the plaza, it had suddenly become very crowded once again.

Dong Jie immediately rushed into the fray, swinging his giant ax as he led the charge into the army of Dao Warriors, followed by several other Immortal Palace cultivators.

"I knew he would be a pain to deal with! I'll find a way to keep him occupied, all of you go and assist Elder Lu," the woman in the pink palace dress instructed, then sat down in mid-air with her legs folded over one another in a rather strange posture, following which she conjured up a translucent white guqin in front of herself.

She raised her hands before quickly strumming her fingers over the strings of the guqin, and a string of crisp notes rang out, immediately following which the chests of a group of Dao Warriors several thousand feet away abruptly exploded, rendering them unfit for further battle.

She then turned toward another direction before strumming the strings of her guqin again, and many more Dao Warriors immediately fell to the ground.

The sound of her guqin appeared to have been quite pleasant to the ears, but in reality, it was capable of casting one's blood, energy, and magic power into complete disarray, and even the Dao Warriors weren't impervious to it.

Meanwhile, the dozen or so Immortal Palace cultivators pounced on this opportunity to converge toward Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

Several hundred kilometers away, Han Li and Qi Liang were standing on a mountain summit with several dozen other True Immortal cultivators.

Han Li's eyes were flashing with blue light as he observed Daoist Hu Yan, then shook his head with a forlorn expression.

During the past few centuries that he had spent in the Blaze Dragon Dao, Daoist Hu Yan was the one who had offered him the most assistance, and their relationship had always been quite cordial, so it was not a good feeling to see him in such a dire situation.

However, there was naturally no way that he would try to rush in and save him.

In the face of so many Golden Immortals, his powers were simply insufficient to make any substantial difference, and he would only be giving up his own life for nothing. On top of that, the silver-robed young man that he had noticed earlier was striking him with a strong sense of foreboding, but he couldn't put his finger on exactly why this was the case.

Right at this moment, another resounding boom rang out in the sky above the plaza.

As it turned out, the silver gourd that Daoist Hu Yan was using to hold all of his Dao Warriors had exploded amid a flash of silver light.

All of the Dao Warriors inside, which totaled in excess of 100,000, had already been released, while the broken gourd transformed into a vast expanse of azure spirit liquid that rained down onto the Dao Warriors.

As soon as the Dao Warriors came into contact with the spirit liquid, bright black light erupted out of their bodies, and they swelled to twice their original size as they charged toward the Immortal Palace cultivators.

Unfortunately, in the face of around two dozen Golden Immortals and True Immortals, these Dao Warriors were simply no match, and they were being cut down in swathes like crops in a field, but fortunately, they were able to keep Dong Jie and the others occupied thanks to their vast numbers.

However, with the assistance of the attacks from the guqin of the woman in the pink palace dress, three of them were able to charge into the central area to attack Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni alongside Lu Yue.

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed that one of these three people was the silver-robed young man that he had felt quite apprehensive about.

He was behaving rather strangely in that even though he was also participating in the attack against Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, he didn't seem to have been very invested, merely wandering around the outskirts of the battlefield and very rarely unleashing any attacks, seemingly only there as a formality.

As a result, Han Li was unable to gauge his power or any of his cultivation arts.

After instructing all of the other dao lords to evacuate the Blaze Dragon Dao's low-grade disciples, Ouyang Kuishan remained standing in mid-air not far away from the White Jade Peak, observing the battle from afar.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out as Lu Yue made a hand seal, and a streak of golden swordlight that was over 1,000 feet in length appeared before crashing down upon the black pagoda projection with mountainous force.

The projection instantly collapsed before disintegrating into specks of black light, but the power of the streak of golden swordlight was also exhausted, dissipating before it even had a chance to reach the snow lotus flower projection down below.

Lu Yue's complexion paled as he stumbled in mid-air, then hurriedly summoned a pill that he promptly devoured, clearly having been severely taxed by the attack that he had just unleashed.

The two Immortal Palace cultivators who were participating in the attack immediately stopped what they were doing before positioning themselves in front of Lu Yue to protect him, while the silver-robed young man continued prowling around the area, unleashing attacks upon the snow lotus flower projection.

A series of large cracks had appeared on the black pagoda treasure that Daoist Hu Yan was holding, and even though it hadn't completely shattered, it was clearly no longer fit for use.

"How dare you!" Daoist Hu Yan roared in a furious voice as he stowed the black pagoda away, then pulled out his crimson gourd, grabbing onto the rope tied around the tapered section of the gourd with one hand while making a hand seal with the other before gently patting the gourd.

A sharp clang rang out as a crimson longsword was slowly drawn out of the opening of the gourd.

"I didn't think that my Crimson Luan would ever be unsheathed again! Now that it's seeing the light of day again, I suppose I have no choice but to slaughter these small fry," Daoist Hu Yan chuckled as he took a swig of wine, then turned to Yun Ni as if he were asking for her opinion. [1]

Yun Ni gave him a warm smile and a nod in response.

A solemn look immediately appeared on Daoist Hu Yan's face, and his aura had suddenly become as sharp as the edge of a blade.

Immediately thereafter, he shot out of the snow lotus flower projection, hurtling directly toward Lu Yue.

A layer of hazy light appeared all around him, and a series of fiery red runes lit up on the longsword in his hand. His robes were flapping audibly in the fierce wind, and his aura had swelled drastically.

With the sword in his hand, it was as if he had turned into a completely different person.

The two Immortal Palace late-True Immortal cultivators didn't even get a chance to react before a streak of crimson light flashed past them, and their bodies were sliced into two with stunned looks frozen on their faces. Their nascent souls had only just begun to flee the scene when they abruptly erupted into flames and were incinerated into nothingness in the blink of an eye.

The woman in the palace dress immediately strummed the strings of her guqin upon seeing this, sending a burst of formidable ripples sweeping directly toward him.

Yun Ni raised her hands up into the air in response, and a huge flower petal detached itself from her snow lotus flower projection, then rose straight up into the air, clashing with the wave of ripples to keep it at bay.

"Your opponent is me," Yun Ni said in a cold voice, and the woman in the palace dress gave her a faint smile before beginning to strum the strings of her guqin once again.

The sound of her guqin was like a turbulent river that swept toward Yun Ni in waves.

Meanwhile, after slaying those two late-True Immortal cultivators, Daoist Hu Yan slashed his longsword through the air, and a massive fiery Luan projection instantly appeared behind Lu Yue.

Immediately thereafter he let loose a loud cry that resembled the call of a phoenix, and the fiery Luan projection flew forward with unstoppable might.

At the same time, a burst of crimson flames surged out of Daoist Hu Yan's longsword, and in the instant that it caught up to the fiery Luan projection, the latter immediately transformed into a massive sea of fire that swept directly toward Lu Yue.

In response, Lu Yue raised his sword before slashing it forward, and a burst of dazzling golden light erupted out of the sword before rapidly expanding in mid-air to form a golden wall to keep the sea of fire at bay.

Even though the sea of fire had been stopped in its tracks, it didn't dissipate. Instead, it continued to crash against the golden wall in formidable waves.

The wall was trembling violently, and the golden light that it was radiating quickly faded before it was completely overwhelmed by the sea of fire.

Daoist Hu Yan held his sword in one hand as he strode over to the sea of fire, putting on an extremely graceful and dashing display.

Lu Yue harrumphed coldly as he raised a hand to release a circular golden shield, while flew into the sea of fire while revolving incessantly.

Immediately thereafter, he sprang up and landed on his feet atop the shield, quickly gliding over the sea of fire as he hurtled directly toward Daoist Hu Yan.

Their swords clashed amid a resounding clang, and countless sword projections erupted in all directions.

[1]. The Luan is a mythical bird in East Asian mythology, this is the same Luan as the one in Han Li's Azure Luan true spirit transformation.

[Back]

Chapter 332: Underground Disturbance

While Daoist Hu Yan and Lu Yue were locked in a fierce battle, Yun Ni wasn't doing so well on her end.

At this point, most of the petals of the snow lotus flower projection around her had already wilted, giving it a rather bare and broken appearance.

She was holding a thin green willow branch in one hand, and with each swing of the branch, thousands of willow-leaf-shaped blades of light would be sent sweeping through the air to form a dense net, preventing the woman in the pink palace dress from being able to approach her.

However, right at this moment, a burst of azure light suddenly appeared above her, and it transformed into a massive sword that came piercing down at her head in a nasty sneak attack.

Yun Ni's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and several flower petals immediately closed around her to form a protective barrier.

A loud thump rang out as those flower petals were completely pulverized, and a sword-wielding figure was sent flying back by the resulting shockwaves, hovering in the sky around 1,000 feet away from Yun Ni.

"Do you still remember me, Dao Lord Yun?" the figure asked with a cold smile.

Yun Ni's complexion was rather pale after withstanding that attack, and she cast her gaze toward the sword-wielding figure clad in azure armor to find that it was none other than Gu Jie.

It seemed that in order to exact revenge on Yun Ni, he had refrained from appearing this entire time, and he had only just emerged to unleash that sneak attack.

Daoist Hu Yan had already noticed what had just happened, and he immediately switched to a series of different hand seals. The sea of fire beneath him surged toward Lu Yue at his behest, while he descended out of the heavens to land beside Yun Ni.

"Are you alright?" he asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"I'm fine," Yun Ni replied before summoning a pill and swallowing it.

A cold and furious look appeared on Daoist Hu Yan's face, and he turned to Gu Jie with intense killing intent in his eyes.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Gu Jie's heart upon seeing this, and he gulped nervously.

"I'm going to kill you!" Daoist Hu Yan declared in a frosty voice, then sliced his sword across the palm of his own hand, opening up a gash out of which blood flowed onto his Crimson Luan sword.

Bright crimson light erupted from the sword, and the obscure runes on its surface also lit up.

Daoist Hu Yan then flung his sword through the air, and it instantly vanished amid a flash of crimson light.

Gu Jie's heart jolted slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly conjured up a layer of protective spiritual light while retreating into the distance.

However, he had only just made it several thousand feet when a burst of crimson light abruptly appeared behind him, then pierced through the layer of protective spiritual light around him with ease before plunging straight into his body.

The clear call of a phoenix rang out as the sword pierced through his back before emerging out of the front of his chest as a fiery Luan bird.

In the instant that the sword pierced through his body, several jets of blood instantly shot out of the hole in Gu Jie's chest, and he let loose an agonized howl as his entire body erupted into flames.

After flying out of the front of Gu Jie's chest, the fiery Luan bird immediately swiveled around in mid-air, swooping down with the aim of piercing through Gu Jie's body again.

Enveloped in a layer of crimson flames, Gu Jie let loose a loud roar as he joined his palms in front of his own chest.

A burst of green light immediately appeared over his suit of azure armor, and it flowed like water, enveloping the crimson flames around him.

The crimson Luan bird struck this layer of azure light with tremendous force, but it immediately sank in as if it had struck a wall of cotton before being repelled back and falling away to the side.

Daoist Hu Yan made a beckoning motion, and the fiery Luan bird reverted back into the form of a longsword before returning to his grasp.

Immediately thereafter, plumes of white smoke began to rise up from Gu Jie's body, and all of the crimson flames were quickly snuffed out.

However, at this point, he had already been completely disfigured from burns. His skin and flesh were charred black and riddled with unsightly gashes that glowed crimson, presenting a ghastly sight much like that of glowing molten lava swimming beneath the parched and cracked earth.

All of the Immortal Palace cultivators were greatly startled to see this, and they all turned to Daoist Hu Yan with a hint of wariness in their eyes.

However, Gu Jie suddenly began to cackle in an inexplicable fashion, and at the same time, the layer of green light around his body began to slowly converge and envelop his body tightly like a tight-fitting robe, then fused into his body in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, all of the burns and gashes on his body began to heal at a rapid rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

Daoist Hu Yan gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, but didn't appear to have been all that surprised.

As Golden Immortals, it was not so easy for one's soul and physical body to be destroyed.

"Dao Lord Ouyang, the sooner all of this comes to an end, the less destruction the Blaze Dragon Dao will have to endure," Lu Yue said in a cold voice as he turned to Ouyang Kuishan.

Ouyang Kuishan hesitated slightly upon hearing this, then rose up into the sky as a streak of azure light, quickly appearing on the plaza in a flash.

With his participation, the Dao Warriors were cut down at an even faster rate, and it wasn't going to be long before they were entirely wiped out.

The four Immortal Palace Golden Immortal cultivators were freed up as a result, and they joined forces to set up a lightning array outside of the sea of fire. Dozens of bolts of azure and purple lightning that were as thick as water vats came crashing out of the array, wiping out even more Dao Warriors.

As the number of remaining Dao Warriors rapidly declined, Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni's situation became more and more perilous.

Just like Han Li, complex looks had appeared on the faces of many of the Blaze Dragon Dao cultivators who were watching the unfolding battle, including some dao lords and deputy dao lords.

In their eyes, even though Baili Yan very rarely appeared in the sect, the past eight preaching ceremonies that he had held had benefited a huge number of cultivators, and he was the reason why the Blaze Dragon Dao had been able to remain standing in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region to this day and become a sect that could rank alongside the Vast Flow Palace.

This was an extremely sinister scheme from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace to attack during the preaching ceremony, and Baili Yan had clearly made an effort to avoid harming the spectators present, yet the Immortal Palace cultivators hadn't displayed any aversion to collateral damage.

What was quite saddening to see was that among the 12 Golden Immortal Stage dao lords, only Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni dared to stand against the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, but it was clear that they were fighting a losing battle.

If they were to be defeated, Baili Yan would be completely on his own, and he would surely be overwhelmed by the Immortal Palace cultivators.

Han Li couldn't help but heave an internal sigh upon seeing this.

The power that Daoist Hu Yan had displayed had come as quite a shock to him. He had already guessed that there was more to the sloppy old man than met the eye, but never had he anticipated that he would be capable of keeping close to 10 Immortal Palace Golden Immortals occupied on his own.

Unfortunately, the Blaze Dragon Dao had already fallen apart internally. Otherwise, if all of the dao lords had given Baili Yan their unwavering support, then there was a very good chance that they would've been able to ward off the Immortal Palace attack.

Luo Qinghai had clearly already identified this, and that was most likely why he hadn't gotten involved. Otherwise, if the Blaze Dragon Dao and the Vast Flow Palace were to join forces, then Xiao Jinhan would have no choice but to immediately retreat.

Right at this moment, Han Li noticed that the silver-robed young man had gone missing from the group of Immortal Palace cultivators that were surrounding Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

He quickly swept his gaze across the entire battlefield, but was unable to find the silver-robed young man, and a hint of foreboding welled up in his heart upon seeing this.

……

High up in the sky, Baili Yan's entire body was enveloped in crimson flames, giving him the appearance of a fiery deity.

Outside of the crimson flames were a series of rainbow halos that were giving off astonishing heat, causing the surrounding space to warp and twist.

Facing him from afar was Xiao Jinhan, who was holding a longsword that was riddled with ice spikes, and there was a translucent wheel of ice that was several dozen feet in size hovering behind him, giving off formidable glacial qi.

Outside of that, there were also around a dozen more Immortal Palace cultivators, including Xue Ying, scattered around the area, but they were all keeping their distance from Xiao Jinhan, seemingly unable to bear the glacial aura emanating from his wheel of ice.

"Baili Yan, why do you insist on resisting when your efforts are clearly futile? If you surrender now, perhaps the Heavenly Court would be willing to welcome you with open arms and give you an opportunity to redeem yourself," Xiao Jinhan said in a cold voice.

"Welcome me with open arms? What a joke! When has the Heavenly Court ever been willing to welcome anyone from the Reincarnation Palace? I'd be lucky not to be tormented for the rest of eternity! Let's cut the chit-chat and fight!" Baili Yan replied in a rumbling voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he slashed his fiery longsword through the air, sending a vast wave of fire sweeping toward Xiao Jinhan. At the same time, bright crimson light appeared in his eyes as he began to chant an incantation.

A deafening boom suddenly rang out from beneath the entire Bell Toll Mountain Range, immediately following which the entire landscape within a radius of thousands of kilometers around the White Jade Peak began to tremble violently, causing countless beasts and birds to flee their homes in a panic.

Another peculiar sound rang out, this one even louder than the one before, causing the entire space to shudder and tremble.

All of the Blaze Dragon Dao cultivators at the scene immediately began looking around frantically, trying to figure out what was happening.

Right at this moment, the earth down below suddenly bulged upward, and the massive cracks appeared on the ground, while rivers were severed and countless trees were felled.

In the extremely far distance, around a dozen mountains were rising up at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, rising close to 1,000 feet in a matter of seconds, while countless giant rocks came rolling down the mountains, raising enormous clouds of dust.

Lu Yue and the others immediately turned to Ouyang Kuishan upon seeing this, and Lu Yue asked, "What's going on here, Dao Lord Ouyang?"

However, Ouyang Kuishan merely shook his head in silence, clearly also unsure of what he aws witnessing.

In contrast, a faint smile had appeared on Daoist Hu Yan's face.

Chapter 333: Giant Head

"We can't keep waiting! Set up the Purple Sun Array right away!" Lu Yue immediately instructed upon seeing this.

As soon as this instruction was issued, the four Golden Immortal cultivators around him immediately sprang into action, positioning themselves around Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni before each pulling out a purple talisman before tossing them forward onto the ground.

The four talismans erupted into flames before falling onto the ground in unison, then transformed into four lines of fire that connected together to form a square.

Immediately thereafter, the four of them began to chant an incantation in unison, and the fire on the ground instantly swelled drastically, forming four purple light barriers that erupted into the heavens to surround Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

There were no visible flames on the purple light barriers, but they were giving off extraordinary heat that was even hotter than the flames on Daoist Hu Yan's Crimson Luan sword.

At the same time, the four light barriers began to converge toward the center in unison.

Daoist Hu Yan immediately grabbed onto Yun Ni's hand upon seeing this, and a burst of fire rose up around his body as he prepared to spring up into the heavens.

However, Lu Yue and the others were already prepared for this, and a thick pillar of silver lightning came crashing down from above alongside a massive streak of golden sword light, forcing the two of them back into the Purple Sun Array.

At this point, the array had already constricted drastically, to the point that Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni were forced to press themselves tightly against one another in order to avoid being scorched by the surrounding purple light barriers.

Right at this moment, Daoist Hu Yan suddenly flipped a hand over to produce a translucent snow robe, which he draped over Yun Ni's body, then summoned a small jade bell, which he tossed directly upward.

A massive green bell projection instantly appeared to encompass both of them, keeping the purple light barriers at bay.

Meanwhile, the tremors and rumbling that were running through the earth were only growing more and more powerful, while balls of purple flames had ignited upon the green bell projection, which appeared as if it could shatter at any moment.

"Hurry!" Lu Yue urged, and the four Golden Immortals who had set up the array immediately bit through the tips of their tongues before spitting out mouthfuls of blood essence onto the purple light barriers.

The Purple Sun Array immediately began to glow far brighter than before while also accelerating in its compression, forcing the green bell projection to become smaller and smaller.

Meanwhile, all of the other Immortal Palace cultivators were also attacking incessantly.

Daoist Hu Yan was making a rapid series of hand seals as he injected his immortal spiritual power into the green bell without any reservation, but he was still unable to stop the purple light barriers from continuing to close in around them, and sweat was beginning to bead up on his forehead.

Right as the green bell projection was about to collapse, a resounding boom suddenly rang out from beneath the ground.

This time, it no longer sounded like the toll of a bell. Instead, it was more like the violent and animalistic roar of some type of primordial beast.

The entire earth shuddered violently as huge clouds of dust rose up all around the White Jade Peak, following which the entire mountain abruptly collapsed.

Countless giant rocks came tumbling down amid a thunderous commotion, and it was like doomsday had arrived.

Everyone who remained on the plaza were caught completely off guard, and they plunged down several hundred feet with the collapse of the mountain before hurriedly steadying themselves and rising up into the air.

In contrast, instead of fleeing upward, Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni allowed themselves to plunge straight down to the foot of the White Jade Peak, using the tumbling rocks and cloud of dust as a smokescreen to cover their escape.

"Don't let them get away!" Lu Yue yelled in an urgent voice, then swooped straight down with his sword held in one hand.

Bright golden light emerged over his body, forming a giant golden sword projection that was over 1,000 feet in length, plunging straight down toward what little remained of the White Jade Peak.

The other Immortal Palace cultivators immediately followed along, while Ouyang Kuishan hesitated momentarily before deciding to remain hovering in mid-air.

Right at this moment, around a dozen of the mountains that neighbored the White Jade Peak collapsed one after another, plunging the entire area in a radius of several thousand kilometers into complete disarray.

As soon as Lu Yue and the others rushed into the cloud of dust, they were immediately met with a wave of scorching heat coupled with a terrifying aura that struck them with a sense of asphyxiation.

"Something's not right here! Let's retreat for now!" Lu Yue hurriedly yelled as he stopped cold in his tracks.

Dong Jie and the others immediately stopped as well upon hearing this, then flew back to distance themselves from the already collapsed White Jade Peak.

All of a sudden, a burst of red light appeared within the dust amid the sound of thunderous rumbling, and immediately thereafter, a pillar of molten lava that was over 1,000 feet in width erupted out of the ground like a crimson wyrm, rising up over 10,000 feet into the sky before raining down from the heavens.

Luo Qinghai immediately swept a hand through the air upon seeing this, and the giant blue flower carried himself and all of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators accompanying him away to the north.

High up in the sky thousands of kilometers to the west of the White Jade Peak, around a dozen deputy dao lords were gathered together with grim looks on their faces. Earlier, they had followed Ouyang Kuishan's instructions to evacuate some of the sect's low-grade disciples to safe areas while also evacuating some of the other cultivators attending the preaching ceremony as well.

This was far from a glamorous event for the sect, and they didn't want all of these outsiders to see what was happening before spreading the news to the outside world.

After completing the task assigned to them, they decided to remain here instead of returning to the White Jade Peak in order to avoid unnecessary trouble.

At this moment, all of them were scrutinizing what was once the White Jade Peak with tightly furrowed brows.

……

Meanwhile, on the summit of the Origin View Peak thousands of kilometers to the east of the White Jade Peak.

Han Li and several dozen other True Immortal Stage elders were gathered here, and all of them were also looking in the direction of the White Jade Peak.

"I wonder how Dao Lord Baili is faring..." an elder with a wide forehead and a head of white hair sighed with a concerned expression.

"Regardless of whether Dao Lord Baili can weather this storm, the Blaze Dragon Dao will no longer be the same," another elder sighed.

Another portly elder had a disgruntled look on his face as he grumbled, "The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace has always declared itself to be a just and righteous sect, but how are they any different from a nest of bandits? We may as well..."

Before he had a chance to finish, another elder hurriedly interjected, "Be prudent with your words, Elder Zhu!"

The portly elder fell silent upon hearing this, then heaved a forlorn sigh.

Han Li was planning to sneak away from here, but upon arriving on this mountain summit, he didn't immediately depart. Instead, he was standing on the edge of the plaza on the mountain summit while casting his gaze in the White Jade Peak's direction with blue light flashing in his eyes.

The entire sky in that direction had taken on a bright red hue, and the storm of molten lava had set the nearby forests alight.

The wind fanned the flames, causing them to spread rapidly, and plumes of dense, black smoke immediately began to rise up within a radius of several hundred kilometers. The entire sky was obscured beneath the columns of black smoke, while the ground below was quickly transforming into a sea of fire.

Red and black seemed to have been the only colors left between heaven and earth, presenting a doomsday-like scene to behold.

Right as everyone was looking on in bewilderment, a massive black shadow suddenly rose up from within the cloud and flames around the White Jade Peak.

"What's that?" Qi Liang involuntarily exclaimed upon seeing this.

Everyone else was also astonished by what they were seeing.

Within the sea of fire, an incredibly enormous black bridge had emerged, spanning the length of several mountains, and there were scorching black flames burning all over its surface, presenting a very peculiar sight to behold.

The blue light in Han Li's eyes brightened a little, following which his pupils contracted slightly.

He could clearly see that the surface of the fiery black "bridge" was riddled with countless massive rhomboid scales that were no different from the ones seen on snakes and pythons.

Before he had a chance to process what he was seeing, a resounding boom rang out, and the entire Origin View Peak shuddered violently as if it were also about to collapse.

Many of the cultivators standing atop the mountain had already risen up into the air, anticipating the mountain's collapse, but thankfully, it was able to withstand the violent tremors.

However, the already collapsed White Jade Peak exploded once again, sending countless huge rocks flying in all directions.

Even more molten lava surged out of the ground from the epicenter of the explosion, forming dozens of winding rivers of lava that flowed over the landscape, charring all of the earth in their wake.

Given the current situation, the Immortal Palace cultivators immediately abandoned their attack against Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, flying far away while conjuring up protective light barriers to keep the falling rocks and lava at bay.

It didn't take long before the entire area within a radius of several dozen kilometers of the White Jade Peak had been completely inundated by lava, forming a massive lake of lava with massive bubbles occasionally emerging and popping on its surface.

Lu Yue swept his spiritual sense over the lava for a second, then yelled, "This lava is a little strange. Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni are hiding beneath it. Don't get close, let's stay here and try to force them out."

"I'll do it!" Dong Jie volunteered as he flipped a hand over to produce a shimmering black rock, which he tossed at the lake of lava down below.

He then began to chant an incantation, and a burst of loud buzzing instantly rang out from the black rock, following which it rapidly swelled into a giant mountain that was over 10,000 feet tall, plummeting down toward the center of the lake.

A resounding boom rang out as the bottom half of the mountain instantly plunged into the lake, sending vast volumes of molten lava erupting in all directions to sweep up enormous waves.

However, the lake of lava then quickly settled back down, while the black mountain slowly sank into its depths bit by bit.

Right at this moment, a thunderous roar rang out from within the lake of lava, causing its surface to ripple violently.

In the next instant, the black mountain suddenly flew out of the lake of lava, having been launched into the sky before abruptly exploding.

Immediately thereafter, an enormous black head that was even larger than the mountain emerged from the lake of lava.

Chapter 334: Retaliation of the Trapped Dragon

The giant head reared up along with the enormous body that it was attached to, rising up into the sky like a winding behemoth.

The "bridge" that had emerged earlier also rose up into the heavens along with it.

Only after it had completely ascended into the sky did everyone come to realize that the owner of the giant head was a huge black dragon that was over 100,000 feet in length.

The dragon had a pair of sharp curved horns that were giving off a menacing black gleam, and black smoke was swirling all around its enormous body, which obscured virtually the entire sky, plunging a large area around the White Jade Peak into complete darkness.

What was even more astonishing was that the dragon had a very strange head with a human face that was countless times more massive than a normal human face.

The expressions of all of the dozens of deputy dao lords situated several thousand kilometers to the west immediately changed drastically upon seeing this.

Among them, even those who had stayed in the Blaze Dragon Dao for the shortest amount of time had already been here for over 100,000 years, yet they had never seen or even heard of such a formidable beast lurking under the White Jade Peak.

"Could this be... the Blaze Dragon?" Xiong Shan murmured with an astonished expression.

"Could it be that this is what's been making all those strange sounds under the mountain range?" another deputy dao lord speculated with a bewildered expression.

"That's most likely the case. Many years ago, while venturing deep into the underground fire veins to collect Crimson Fire Essence, I detected an indistinct aura. At the time, I paid it no heed, but thinking back, that aura was virtually identical to the aura of this beast," a thin elderly man said with an enlightened expression.

"But why does its face look like that?"

"Isn't that Dao Lord Baili's face?"

On the Origin View Peak.

Han Li was looking at the enormous beast from afar, and the snippets of information that he had previously read about the primordial beast, the Blaze Dragon, quickly flashed through his mind. Indeed, its physical description was almost a complete match with this gargantuan beast with only some minute differences.

For example, it was described that the face of the Blaze Dragon was only very slightly resembling that of a human, but this Blaze Dragon's face bore a striking resemblance to Baili Yan.

Could it be that this is Dao Lord Baili's true body?

As soon as this thought crossed Han Li's mind, it was immediately dismissed.

This strange Blaze Dragon's eyes were filled entirely with scorching black flames and had no pupils, clearly indicating that it wasn't an intelligent creature. Even if it did have something to do with Baili Yan, it was much more likely that it was an avatar of his.

Furthermore, for some reason, as soon as the giant Blaze Dragon appeared, Han Li immediately felt a strong sense of aversion to it deep within his soul.

He discovered that the black flames burning all over the Blaze Dragon's body seemed to have been imbued with extremely formidable baleful qi, more formidable than any that he had ever felt before.

Meanwhile, on the giant blue flower hovering in the sky several thousand kilometers to the north of the White Jade Peak.

The initially calm and unperturbed Vast Flow Palace cultivators now all had astonished looks on their faces, and they were too stunned to speak.

At this point, Luo Qinghai had also stood up from his golden throne, and he was staring intently at the enormous Blaze Dragon.

Only after a long while did he return to his senses before murmuring to himself, "I had thought that you had only gone into seclusion to delay the onset of the five decays, but never had I anticipated that you would've already overcome the five decays by forging such a unique path. How unfortunate... If you had been given just 10,000 more years, the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace would've been no match for you."

The effeminate man behind him approached him with an uncertain expression, then asked, "Master, what should we do now?"

"All of you, watch carefully! This is an extremely rare opportunity. Even if the Immortal Palace manages to get what they want, it'll almost certainly be at an extremely heavy cost," Luo Qinghai chuckled as he sat back down onto his throne and continued to observe the battle.

Baili Yan's body was enveloped in a layer of rainbow light, and he was holding a crimson immortal sword in one hand and an octagonal fiery red mirror in the other, standing several thousand feet away from Xiao Jinhan.

The entire area within a radius of 20,000 to 30,000 feet around him was enveloped within a near-transparent hemispherical light barrier with white light surging over its surface, and it was also riddled with countless snowflake patterns that were giving off cold glacial qi.

There were around a dozen Immortal Palace cultivators, including Xue Ying, distributed around the light barrier, and each of them was holding a white jade tablet that they were injecting their immortal spiritual power into.

Over half of them were Golden Immortal cultivators, while the rest were all late-True Immortal cultivators, and it appeared that they had trapped Baili Yan here, but they hadn't actually managed to gain the upper hand at all.

"Baili Yan, it's no wonder the Heavenly Court views you as such a potent threat, you are indeed a remarkable man," Xiao Jinhan said as he cast his gaze toward the Blaze Dragon in the distance.

"There are no unremarkable people among those who have reached our cultivation base," Baili Yan replied with a cold smile.

"In any case, we made the right decision to come here today. Otherwise, if we had given you 10,000 more years, you would've been the one actively knocking on our Northern Glacial Immortal Palace's door, and we would've certainly been no match for the High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal that you would've become," Xiao Jinhan

"What makes you think you're a match for me now?" Baili Yan sneered.

……

In the sky above the White Jade Peak.

An earth-shattering roar rang out as the Blaze Dragon twisted its body from side to side, rising up toward Baili Yan.

Right as it was about to pass through the clouds up above, the severely ravaged ground down below abruptly shuddered, following which an enormous array projection appeared before releasing a vast expanse of dazzling golden radiance.

Eight huge golden pillars, each with a golden dragon coiled around them, rose up around the Blaze Dragon, swelling to over 100,000 feet tall in the span of just a few seconds, and the pillars were riddled with runes that were giving off more golden light.

Atop each pillar stood an Immortal Palace Golden Immortal, all of whom were chanting incantations while making hand seals to activate the array.

One of the Golden Immortals standing on the pillars was none other than Gu Jie, and at the same time, the woman in the pink palace dress suddenly appeared in the sky above the Blaze Dragon with her white guqin hovering in front of her.

She stroked her fingers over the strings of the instrument, and a burst of peculiar music suddenly rang out from the eight giant golden pillars, following which the eight massive golden dragons coiled around the pillars abruptly sprang to life.

A collective draconic roar rang out as the eight golden dragons pounced out of the giant pillars, plunging headfirst into the black flames to tear at the Blaze Dragon with their claws and fangs.

Within the black flames, the eight golden dragons wrapped themselves around the Blaze Dragon before opening their cavernous mouths and sinking their fangs into the Blaze Dragon's body, only to find that they were unable to even bite through its scales.

The Blaze Dragon let loose a thunderous roar as it began to thrash around violently in an attempt to shake off the golden dragons.

As a result, it was constantly crashing into the giant golden pillars, causing a massive commotion.

However, the golden pillars remained completely unmoved, and it was as if they were a permanent fixture between heaven and earth.

This array was even more formidable than the Golden Scale Dragon Locking Array, and the Blaze Dragon was unable to break free.

All of a sudden, Lu Yue rose up into the sky as a streak of dazzling golden light, then raised a hand to summon a black ox horn bow.

The bow's design was very simplistic, as if it had been crafted without much care, and there weren't any adornments or even runes on its surface. All it did was give off a faint black sheen, and it had a very antiquated appearance.

Lu Yue cast his gaze toward the thrashing Blaze Dragon, then lunged forward and slowly drew the bow back.

As he did so, the muscles on his arms bulged and trembled incessantly, indicating that he was experiencing a great deal of strain.

The bow was slowly being drawn back, and as the bowstring came into contact with his chin, wisps of silver light began to appear between his hands, then connected together to form a shimmering silver arrow that was aimed straight at the Blaze Dragon's head.

Lu Yue's fingers had been sliced open by the bowstring, and blood was pouring out of the gashes, only to be absorbed by the bow. However, his aura was rather restrained, and he remained completely still, seemingly in no hurry to fire the arrow.

At the same time, a tiny speck of silver light appeared on the tip of the arrow, and initially, it was rather indistinct, but it was becoming more and more substantial and giving off bursts of law fluctuations.

The Blaze Dragon's struggles continued to prove futile, and it was becoming more and more furious by the second.

It twisted around and opened its cavernous mouth to blast forth a stream of ferocious black flames to incinerate, and compared with the black flames on its body, the fire being blasted out of its mouth was even hotter and imbued with more fierce baleful qi.

In mere moments, the eight golden dragons began to wilt under the intense heat, looking as if they were about to melt away.

The eight Golden Immortals standing atop the golden pillars were also feeling the heat, and their blood circulation had sped up by severalfold, while a sense of agitation welled up in their hearts, as if they were being roasted in a fiery pit.

Finally, one of the early-Golden Immortal cultivators was unable to withstand the heat any longer, and he involuntarily threw up a mouthful of blood.

Immediately thereafter, Gu Jie also threw up a mouthful of blood, having already sustained severe injuries from the blow dealt upon him by the Crimson Luan sword.

As a result, the entire array had been destabilized, and it looked as if it could collapse at any moment.

Right as the surrounding golden pillars were about to be toppled, Dong Jie suddenly appeared in the sky in a flash, and through the use of some type of secret technique, he had expanded his own body to over 10,000 feet tall.

He was holding an enormous ax that he swung up into the sky with both hands while leaping into the air, then swung his ax down toward the Blaze Dragon's neck.

Dazzling black light erupted out of the runes engraved onto the blade of the ax, and it began to release formidable tearing force that caused the surrounding space to warp and twist.

Right as the ax was about to tear through the black flames and strike the Blaze Dragon's neck, a burst of crimson light suddenly shot out of the top of the Blaze Dragon's head like lightning, then rapidly expanded while flying through the air, transforming into a giant crimson sword that was several thousand feet in length before striking the sharp edge of the ax.

Chapter 335: Karmic Fire Remission

A resounding boom rang out as a blinding crimson sun exploded in the sky, sending countless bursts of fire hurtling toward the sharp edge of the giant ax.

The ax appeared to have been swinging through the air with unstoppable force, but it was snapped with a resounding crack, while the huge crimson sword pierced straight through Dong Jie's chest.

A huge gash was instantly torn open on his chest, yet before blood had a chance to flow out of the wound, it was evaporated by the scorching flames burning on the giant sword.

Dong Jie swayed a few times before plummeting out of the sky as his body rapidly shrank back down to its original size, while the giant crimson sword flew back to position itself above the Blaze Dragon's head again.

Immediately thereafter, the sword also shrank down rapidly, and Daoist Hu Yan stumbled out of it with an ashen complexion while gasping for air.

Just now, he had drawn upon the blood essence in his own body to fuse as one with his Crimson Luan sword, and only then was he able to severely wound Dong Jie with a single strike.

Despite how severely taxed he was, he didn't immediately swallow any pills to assist in his recovery. Instead, he cast his gaze toward the woman in the pink palace dress.

A burst of indistinct white light abruptly appeared behind her, following which Yun Ni emerged amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, then lashed out toward the woman's back with the green willow branch that she was holding.

Azure light was searching all over the willow branch, and as it was swung through the air, countless willow-leaf-shaped blades of light were instantly released, sweeping directly toward the woman's back.

At this moment, the woman in the pink palace dress had her attention focused entirely on stabilizing the array, which was on the verge of collapse, and by the time she detected what was happening behind her, it was already too late.

The silk streamer that was draped over her shoulders immediately began to glow brightly, then rose up into the air to oppose the willow branch.

At the same time, a streak of light flashed through the air as Ouyang Kuishan rapidly approached the scene from afar with a complex look on his face, holding a golden longsword that he was plunging directly toward Yun Ni's heart.

A hint of finality flashed through Yun Ni's eyes upon seeing this, and she made no effort to take evasive measures, seemingly determined to go through with her attack even at the cost of her own life.

The flurry of willow leaf blades we instantly tore a gash into the silk streamer before crashing heavily into the woman's back, shredding through the protective spiritual light around her as her entire body pitched forward, and she threw up a mouthful of blood that splattered all over her guqin.

At the same time, Ouyang Kuishan had also arrived on the scene, yet right as his sword was about to plunge through Yun Ni's heart, he suddenly twisted his wrist slightly to direct his sword away from its original trajectory, piercing it through Yun Ni's shoulder instead.

"Is it really worth going so far for him?" he asked as a pained look flashed through his eyes.

Yun Ni merely smiled and offered no response as her entire body scattered into countless white flower petals.

In the next instant, she reappeared beside Daoist Hu Yan.

Immediately thereafter, yet another earth-shattering roar rang out, and the black flames over the Blaze Dragon's body reared up significantly as it swiveled around in the sky, thrashing against the array that it was trapped in with ferocious might.

The surrounding golden pillars were already quite unstable, and the entire array began to collapse toward the center in the face of the Blaze Dragon's tremendous power.

As the Blaze Dragon reared up with all its might, the golden dragons coiled around its body were finally snapped into pieces before disintegrating into countless specks of golden light.

Immediately thereafter, the eight golden pillars exploded violently into an enormous arc of golden light that erupted in all directions. The eight Golden Immortals that were overseeing the array were all struck by backlash in the wake of the array's destruction, and they plummeted out of the sky with blood gushing out of their mouths.

Upon breaking free from the array, the Blaze Dragon continued to ascend, flying straight through the clouds before arriving on the other battlefield.

The space there was encompassed within a massive white light barrier, within which gusts of frosty wind that were interspersed with countless snowflakes were howling incessantly, and even the clouds had begun to freeze over, transforming them ice statues of all types of strange shapes and forms, making one feel as if they had suddenly arrived on the Infernal Frost Continent.

"That's Xiao Jinhan's Golden Immortal spirit domain!" Daoist Hu Yan exclaimed.

"There's Dao Lord Baili!" Yun Ni called out as she pointed at the light barrier from afar.

Having already taken a restorative pill, the wound on her chest had already completely healed, but her complexion was still quite pale.

At this point, she was pointing at a massive icy plaque that was hovering at the center of the area encompassed within the light barrier, and it was giving off formidable glacial qi.

Trapped within the giant plaque was none other than Baili Yan, and his body was enveloped within a layer of rainbow light that was flashing incessantly, seemingly desperately trying to keep the surrounding glacial qi at bay.

Upon seeing the approaching Blaze Dragon, a complex look flashed through Baili Yan's eyes.

Meanwhile, Xiao Jinhan was standing atop the giant plaque with his hands resting atop the hilt of his sword.

Hovering in the air behind him was a massive wheel of ice that was giving off radiant silver light while also releasing a constant stream of silver runes.

Whenever a rune came drifting down, it would flow down his longsword and land upon the giant plaque, further reinforcing it while also bolstering the glacial qi within it.

A hint of fury flashed through Xiao Jinhan's eyes at the sight of the approaching Blaze Dragon, and he released the hilt of his sword to make a hand seal before sweeping a hand forward in a forceful fashion.

Dazzling silver light erupted out of the wheel of ice behind him, conjuring up an enormous ice dragon that was over 100,000 feet in length above his head before swooping down toward the Blaze Dragon.

The two massive dragons clashed with an almighty boom, and the ice dragon began to shatter in layers starting from its head, disintegrating into a vast expanse of ice crystals, while the Blaze Dragon continued onward, flying directly toward the white light barrier.

Right as its sharp horns were about to pierce through the light barrier, the sound of an arrow whistling through the air suddenly rang out across the entire sky.

Having accumulated as much power as he could, Lu Yue had finally let loose his arrow.

The silver arrow had a long fiery tail, and it was flying across the sky like a shooting star.

A silver vortex was revolving rapidly on the tip of the arrow, causing all of the space in its wake to shudder violently, while boundless world's origin qi was converging from all directions before surging into the vortex.

The silver arrow rapidly swelled in size as it flew through the air, quickly extending to over 10,000 feet in length from its initial length of three feet, and it punched a massive hole through the clouds before hurtling toward the Blaze Dragon's head from below.

A thunderous boom rang out as a massive hole was shot through the Blaze Dragon's head, extending all the way from the bottom of its chin to the top of its head.

The giant silver vortex remained in its head, causing even more world's origin qi to converge in a frenzy.

The spiritual pressure there was constantly elevating, and it quickly reached an extremely formidable level.

Daoist Hu Yan immediately grabbed onto Yun Ni's hand and flew away into the distance upon seeing this.

He had only flown for just over 10,000 feet when a resounding boom rang out from behind him,. and the silver vortex exploded violently, sending chaotic world's origin qi erupting in all directions, producing shockwaves that encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of hundred os kilometers.

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni felt a vast wave of power sweeping toward them from behind, and both of them threw up a mouthful of blood in unison as they were swept involuntarily away into the distance like a pair of small rafts in an almighty storm.

During the explosion, the silver vortex was constantly expanding to destroy the Blaze Dragon's massive head bit by bit, gradually reducing it to a cloud of dense black mist.

However, instead of dissipating, all of the black mist surged into the white light barrier, then rapidly passed through the vast expanse of snow and ice without any inhibition before converging entirely into the giant ice plaque.

All of a sudden, a black sun exploded violently within the giant plaque, sending formidable shockwaves and countless ice crystals erupting in all directions.

White light flashed over Xiao Jinhan's body as he instantly flew away from the giant plaque, while Xue Ying and the others were sent flying back by the explosion.

Immediately thereafter, the wisps of black mist in the air converged to form Baili Yan, who then slowly descended onto a frozen cloud.

There was black mist surging all around his body, as well as a ball of black flames hovering above each of his shoulders. His red hair had turned completely black, and a small black fire spirit rune had appeared on his glabella, while his eyes had become a darker shade of black than before.

It was as if he had suddenly transformed into a completely different person!

At the same time, his aura had swelled by severalfold, and even the slightest gesture from him was enough to sweep up gusts of fierce wind.

"I went through so much trouble over the course of countless years to expel this karmic fire from my body, yet now, I've been forced into remission. The Heavenly Dao can truly be cruel," Baili Yan mused in an expressionless manner as he cast his gaze toward Xiao Jinhan.

"This is the baleful immortal that's being hunted by the Heavenly Court! Having said that, in order to attain this power, you've doomed yourself to the fifth decay," Xiao Jinhan said with a cold expression.

"So be it. Seeing as things have already come to this point, let the karmic fire burn even brighter!" Baili Yan declared as a fierce look flashed through his eyes.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a constant stream of black mist began to surge out of his body, forming a massive wall of black mist behind him. The wall of mist surged toward Xiao Jinhan, transforming into a black spirit domain that was slowly eating away at the white light barrier in the sky.

At the same time, a cold look appeared in his eyes as he strode over the frozen cloud toward Xiao Jinhan.

The clouds beneath his feet began to shatter amid a string of crisp cracking, while Luo Qinghai heaved a forlorn sigh as he observed the unfolding scene from down below.

"He's been forced into karmic fire remission... Let's go."

With a wave of his hand, the giant blue flower flew away from the scene, carrying with it all of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators.

Thousands of kilometers away, Xiong Shan took one final glance up at the sky, then immediately flew away toward the west without any hesitation, and the other deputy dao lords quickly departed as well, as did many of the True Immortal Stage elders on the Origin View Peak.

The blue light in Han Li's eyes faded, and he turned his gaze toward Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni. Upon noticing that they were also fleeing the scene, he immediately decided to do the same.

"I'll be going ahead, Brother Qi," he said to Qi Liang.

The latter faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "Farewell, Brother Li. I want to stay here for a while longer."

A battle between a pair of cultivators at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage was truly an extremely rare sight, and there were quite a few people like Qi Liang who were willing to take the risk to observe the battle in the hope that they would be able to benefit from it, perhaps even find a catalyst for a breakthrough.

"Take care," Han Li said with a parting nod, then flew away as a streak of azure light.

Chapter 336: Recollection

In the blink of an eye, the streak of azure light that Han Li had transformed into vanished into thin air, and when he reappeared a moment later, he was already hundreds of kilometers away.

As soon as he emerged, he immediately continued onward.

After getting a little further away, he immediately accelerated, covering a distance of tens of thousands of kilometers in the blink of an eye before descending near a secluded mountain.

From there, he turned to take a glance back in the direction of the White Jade Peak before heaving a faint sigh.

Regardless of whether the Blaze Dragon Dao would be able to weather this storm, he couldn't stay here any longer. In the wake of this incident, there would be no end to the troubles awaiting the Blaze Dragon Dao, and he was quite close with Daoist Hu Yan, so there was no telling whether he was going to be targeted as well.

Most importantly, that silver-robed young man had struck him with a very strong sense of foreboding. He couldn't pinpoint why this was the case, but he had an unconscious urge to get as far away from him as possible.

Upon withdrawing his gaze, Han Li made a hand seal, and arcs of golden lightning sprang out of his body to instantly form a lightning array, immediately following which he vanished into thin air.

Not long after Han Li vanished from this spot, several streaks of light came flying over from the White Jade Peak before dispersing in different directions.

All of these people were members of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and there was no lack of True Immortal Stage elders among them.

……

In the sky above a mountain in the Bell Toll Mountain Range, a blurry golden line flashed through the air, hurtling forward at an incredible speed.

The golden line resembled an arc of lightning, and the space in its wake was rippling slightly presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold. This was a movement technique that combined the powers of space and lightning.

Lightning movement techniques allowed one to achieve a level of speed that was close to instantaneous teleportation, but they were two different things in that one was only transforming oneself into a state of lightning in order to enhance their own speed.

All of a sudden, the golden line began to slow down. A burst of invisible force had emerged in the space up ahead to obstruct the golden line, and it was as if it were moving through treacle.

The more the golden line tried to force its way through, the more formidable the obstructive force became, and before long, the golden line had been slowed down significantly.

All of a sudden, the nearby space rippled, and a golden lightning array appeared, following which Han Li emerged at the center of the array amid a rumbling thunderclap.

He swept his gaze forward momentarily, and his expression darkened slightly as he continued onward as a streak of azure light, covering several hundred kilometers in the blink of an eye before drawing to a halt.

Up ahead was an enormous wall of yellow mist that extended straight up into the heavens, and there was no end to it in sight to the left or the right.

The wall of yellow mist was constantly churning, taking on all types of different forms, such as clouds and ferocious beasts.

Rays of yellow light were filtering through the mist, and one could just barely make out countless yellow array patterns shimmering within it. The wall of mist was also giving off an incredibly dense and heavy aura, making one feel as if they were standing before an immovable mountain.

Han Li flew over to the wall of mist, then attempted to release his spiritual sense into the wall, only for it to be instantly repelled upon contact.

His brows furrowed slightly as he began to inspect the wall of mist with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and moments later, the blue light in his eyes faded as well as he murmured to himself, "This is an extremely formidable restriction!"

His lightning teleportation array drew upon the power of space, so ordinary restrictions wouldn't have been able to contain it unless the restriction was also imbued with spatial power.

Through the use of his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, he was able to see some of the finer details of the restriction, and he discovered that it contained a layer of dense and abundant spatial power, clearly indicating that it was a type of extremely formidable spatial restriction.

In addition to that, there were also several other types of restrictions within the wall of mist, and they were combined together using very advanced techniques.

Even for Han Li, breaking this restriction was going to take a very long time.

He took a glance at his surroundings, then released his spiritual sense with all his might, and several moments later, he withdrew his spiritual sense as his expression darkened even further.

The wall of mist was so vast that even with his formidable spiritual sense, he was completely unable to detect where it began and where it concluded.

However, judging from what he had been able to glean thus far, he could tell that his wall of yellow mist was an enormous spherical array that encompassed a huge area around the White Jade Peak.

He had passed through this place on his way to the White Jade Peak, but this restriction definitely hadn't been there at the time.

This must've been set up in advance by the Northern Glacial Immortal Region and those dao lords of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

It was clear that these people had been plotting and preparing extensively for this with the objective of preventing Baili Yan from getting away.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li swept a hand through the air, and 12 streaks of golden light shot out of his body, revealing themselves to be 12 lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood, all of which were riddled with complex lightning runes.

The 12 lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood had been arranged into an array, and as Han Li made a hand seal, all 12 lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood began to radiate dazzling golden light, following which an enormous lightning array was conjured up, within which countless complex lightning runes were flashing incessantly.

Han Li was situated inside the array, and his body began to take on a semi-transparent appearance amid a rumbling thunderclap.

However, in the next instant, the lightning array suddenly began to tremble violently, and lightning was flashing erratically within it in a chaotic and uncontrolled fashion.

A resounding boom rang out as the entire lightning array exploded, and Han Li stumbled out into the open.

After a brief pause, he swept a sleeve through the air to recover the 12 lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood, then cast his gaze toward the wall of yellow mist once again.

Right at this moment, a vast black cloud suddenly appeared above his head, and countless rays of black light shone down from the heavens, raining directly down upon him.

Han Li immediately vanished from the spot amid a flash of azure light, then reappeared tens of thousands of feet away.

The countless rays of black light struck a mountain down below, instantly punching countless holes into it before toppling it entirely.

Han Li raised his head to look up, right as three streaks of light descended out of the sky before fading to reveal a trio of humanoid figures, led by none other than the silver-robed young man.

The two people accompanying him were dressed in black and standing slightly behind him in a respectful manner, seemingly serving as personal guards. One of them was a tall and portly man, while the other was quite short and as thin as a skeleton.

"What is the meaning of this? Your target is Baili Yan. I'm just a minor character, so surely there's no reason for you to go out of your way to come after me," Han Li said.

As he was speaking, he swept his spiritual sense over the trio in the discreet fashion, and his heart immediately sank slightly.

The two guards dressed in black were both at the late-True Immortal Stage, while the silver-robed young man's exact cultivation base was undetectable to him, indicating that he had either cultivated some type of concealment secret technique, or he was a Golden Immortal.

"Well, well, well, color me impressed! Not only have you not died from last time, you've become a late-True Immortal cultivator. I suppose I should congratulate you," the silver-robed young man mused, displaying no intention of answering Han Li's question.

"It sounds like we've met somewhere before?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

The silver-robed young man seemed to have been very amused to hear this, and he erupted into laughter, while Han Li looked on with an uncertain expression.

"There's no way he would remember what happened last time after being struck by your Soul Destroying True Light, Young Master. It's already a massive blessing for him that he hasn't been reduced to a blubbering idiot!" the portly guard chuckled with a fawning smile on his face.

The silver-robed young man's laughter grew even louder upon hearing this.

All of a sudden, Daoist Xie's voice rang out within Han Li's mind. "Fellow Daoist Han, I remember who he is! He's the one who severely wounded you all those years ago and sealed your Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and myself!"

Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this, and he hurriedly asked through voice transmission, "Are you sure?"

"I'm certain. He possesses an array of strange abilities, and he seems to be able to seal away one's memories. I was only able to recover some snippets of memories after fusing with this puppet, but I'm confident that this is the man who came after you all those years ago," Daoist Xie replied.

Han Li offered no response, but a cold look had appeared in his eyes.

"It looks like you've finally remembered something. I've had to spend a great deal of effort looking for you, and I certainly wasn't expecting to find you here," the silver-robed young man said with a faint smile.

"It sounds like we're truly tied together by fate," Han Li said in a cold voice.

"I don't want to waste any time here. Hand over the secret behind how you're able to produce those time law crystals and I can let you live," the silver-robed young man said.

"But I have no plans of letting you live," Han Li retorted with a shake of his head.

"It appears that my kindness is being mistaken for weakness! I'm not going to let you get away again this time."

The smile on the silver-robed young man's face faded as he spoke, and he abruptly swept a hand through the air to release a streak of black light.

As soon as the streak of black light was sent flying through the air, it immediately brightened considerably before abruptly vanishing from the spot.

Han Li immediately dodged to his left while also making a hand seal, and four azure flying swords emerged from his body amid a flash of azure light.

The streak of black light appeared beside Han Li without any warning, but it was kept at bay by one of the flying swords that was revolving around him.

A loud clang rang out as Han Li was sent flying back through the air like a cannonball, only managing to just barely steady himself after flying back for several hundred feet.

Only then did Han Li catch a clear glimpse of the streak of black light, and it contained a small black hammer that was around a foot in size with profound spirit patterns engraved all over its surface, giving off formidable spiritual power fluctuations.

Even though the azure flying sword had managed to ward off the hammer, it was trembling incessantly, clearly having been dealt a heavy blow.

Han Li flicked his fingers through the air, and the three other flying swords quickly shot forth to strike the black hammer, sending it flying back amid a string of three consecutive resounding clangs.

Chapter 337: Integrated Five Extreme Mountains

At the same time, Han Li swept both sleeves through the air to release several dozen azure flying swords, then shot back in retreat without any hesitation.

These flying swords gathered in front of Han Li alongside the four previous flying swords. In the blink of an eye, all 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were assembled, and they immediately unleashed countless identical streaks of azure sword qi that surged toward Han Li's three assailants like a turbulent river, slicing through all of the space in their wake and presenting a formidable sight to behold.

The expressions of the two black-robed guards changed slightly upon seeing this, while the silver-robed young man merely sneered as he withdrew the small black hammer back up his sleeve, immediately following which a silver bell appeared in his hand, and he shook it gently to produce a crisp chime.

Immediately thereafter, waves of silver light erupted from the bell in all directions, instantly encompassing a vast space up ahead.

As soon as the river of azure sword qi surged into the waves of silver light, the former immediately began to warp and twist before silently disintegrating, and the formidable stream of sword qi was nullified with ease.

Soon, only the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords remained, but they were also flying around in a chaotic and haphazard fashion, as if they had lost all sense of direction.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon seeing this, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which bright golden lightning erupted out of the scattered flying swords amid a resounding thunderclap.

As a result, they were able to stabilize themselves within the waves of silver light, following which the arcs of golden lightning erupting out of all of the swords intertwined to form a strange pattern.

Immediately thereafter, all of the flying swords abruptly vanished amid a flash of golden light, then re-emerged as 72 streaks of flying swordlight amid a resounding thunderclap.

Thick arcs of golden lightning sprang forth before connecting with one another to instantly form a lightning array around the trio, and all of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, so the trio didn't have any time to react before they found themselves inside the lightning array.

A burst of formidable restrictive force spread through the array, and the trio immediately felt as if they had been plunged into a swamp, and their immortal spiritual power circulation had also become rather sluggish.

The two black-robed guards were very alarmed, and they immediately conjured up protective light barriers as they attempted to break free from the lightning array, while the silver-robed young man remained completely still as his gaze roamed over the surrounding Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

In the next instant, the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords began to release dazzling radiance as streaks of sword qi that were several times thicker and brighter than before swept toward the trio amid a wave of golden lightning.

"Young Master!" the pair of black-robed guards yelled urgently in unison at the sight of the oncoming barrage of sword qi and lightning.

The silver-robed young man gave a cold harrumph, seemingly completely unaffected by the restrictive effects of the lightning array, then swept a hand through the air to send an incantation seal flying into the bell that he was holding. After that, he shook the bell vigorously, and waves of silver light that were several times denser than before emerged before sweeping through the surrounding area, opening up a silver space that was several hundred feet in size.

The pair of black-robed guard's immediately regained their mobility, and their immortal spiritual power was able to circulate as normal again as well, but at this point, the barrage of sword qi was already no more than 100 feet away.

Right at this moment, the silver-robed young man opened his mouth to release a burst of gray light, which then began to revolve above their heads, releasing a vast expanse of gray light that enveloped all three of them.

In the next instant, the formidable wave of sword qi and golden lightning arrived, forming an enormous ball of azure light that instantly inundated the trio.

Within the ball of light, streaks of sword and arcs of golden lightning were surging through the air in a frenzy, and everything down below was torn to shreds.

Han Li was hovering in mid-air several thousand feet away from the ball of azure light, holding an Immortal Origin Stone that he was using to quickly replenish his immortal spiritual power.

All of a sudden, he raised an eyebrow, and a faint crack rang out from a certain part of the ball of azure light.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of gray light tore through the azure sword qi and golden lightning, seemingly completely unaffected, and it erupted out into the open before fading to reveal the silver-robed young man and his two personal guards.

A small gray mountain was hovering above them while revolving incessantly, releasing a layer of dense gray light that enveloped all three of them.

The pair of black-robed guards were looking a little disheveled, but the silver-robed young man was completely unscathed, and even his robes hadn't been damaged in the slightest.

Meanwhile, Han Li cast his gaze toward the small gray mountain as a complex look appeared in his eyes.

Even though it was a little different from how it had previously looked, he was still able to identify it as one of the treasures that he had lost, the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

"This Acquired Immortal Treasure of yours was not bad, but the refinement method used was far too crude, and the five extreme mountains weren't sufficiently pure, either. I had to expend a great deal of time and effort to refine it to this extent, and it's actually the first time that I'm using it in battle. Let's have you, its former owner, get a taste of its power," the silver-robed young man said in a casual voice as he raised a hand, and the gray mountain instantly swelled drastically in size.

At the same time, the countless profound spirit patterns engraved upon its surface released a layer of gray light as it crashed heavily down upon the ball of azure light below.

Even before the two made contact, the formidable pressure released by the giant mountain was already causing the ball of azure light to ripple and quiver.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he made a hand seal, and he quickly made a hand seal, upon which countless streaks of sword qi immediately converged inward from the surface of the ball of azure light, transforming it into an azure sword lotus flower with thick arcs of lightning flashing over its surface in the blink of an eye.

The azure sword lotus flower spun around on the spot while radiating dazzling azure light, releasing countless streaks of azure swordlight toward the giant gray mountain.

However, at the same time, a burst of gray light swept forth from the underside of the mountain to meet the azure sword lotus flower.

The arcs of golden lightning flashing over the sword lotus flower vanished without a trace within the gray light, following which the sword lotus flower itself crumbled away, reverting back into 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and the spirit patterns on the surfaces of the swords were flashing erratically.

Han Li's brows furrowed even more tightly upon seeing this.

He was naturally aware of the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain's ability to suppress the power of lightning, but the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had absorbed an enormous amount of sword essence and been smelted using a whole host of precious materials, thereby significantly enhancing their power, so he didn't think that it would be so severely affected by the gray light.

It seemed that the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain had also become far more formidable after being refined by the silver-robed young man.

Even as these thoughts were flashing through his mind, Han Li continued to cycle through a series of hand seals, and azure light erupted from the surfaces of the 72 flying swords once again.

At the same time, they released countless azure threads that cleared open an area within the gray light, and before the gray light had a chance to recover, all of the flying swords instantly flew back toward Han Li.

"You sure have quite a few good treasures on you! This set of flying swords is not bad at all. I wanted to take them last time, but I suppose it's still not too late," the silver-robed young man said with a faint smile as he made a hand seal.

All of the runes on the surface of the gray mountain lit up, and waves of gray light that were even denser than before surged forth before spreading downward, immediately enveloping the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which still hadn't had a chance to get very far away.

The spiritual light glowing from all of the flying swords was flashing and quivering incessantly, and they were like fish trapped in a net.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly switched to a different hand seal, but this time, no matter what he tried, the 72 flying swords were unable to break free.

Meanwhile, the silver-robed young man opened his mouth to release a burst of black light, which vanished into the gray mountain in a flash.

The waves of gray light being released by the mountain instantly transformed into countless gray runes, which then turned into countless thin gray threads that wrapped themselves around the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, instantly forming a series of gray cocoons.

The struggles of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords gradually grew weaker and weaker, while the gray light around them stabilized once again.

The silver-robed young man then opened his mouth a second time to produce a slightly viscous-looking ball of black light, within which countless black runes were flashing, giving off a burst of peculiar law fluctuations.

The ball of light then split apart into 72 streaks of black light, each of which fused into an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in the blink of an eye.

The sword qi and lightning being released by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were completely unable to keep the black light at bay, and the spiritual light radiating from them instantly took on a slightly black coloration.

Han Li knew that in order to recover his swords, he would have to directly attack the silver-robed young man, so that was exactly what he did.

The silver-robed young man turned to the oncoming Han Li, only for the portly guard beside him to hurriedly interject, "There's no need for you to personally deal with a mere late-True Immortal cultivator, Young Master. Just leave him to us while you focus on subduing that set of flying swords."

They had just been severely humiliated by Han Li's earlier attack, and if they couldn't prove their usefulness to the silver-robed young man, then they were going to be in a very perilous position.

The thin black-robed guard also immediately nodded in agreement.

"Alright, in that case, I'll leave him to you, but don't kill him. I still have some things that I need to find out from him," the silver-robed young man replied with a nod.

The pair of black-robed guards were ecstatic, and they immediately flew toward Han Li.

Dazzling starlight appeared over the portly guard's body, and his belly abruptly swelled to three times its original size, giving him the appearance of a fat toad.

Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth to release a vast expanse of bright starlight, which swept toward Han Li like a resplendent wave.

Interspersed throughout the wave of starlight were countless glowing grains of sand that were rumbling like lightning, as if they could explode at any moment.

Meanwhile, the thin guard made a rapid string of hand seals, and balls of black flames rose up over his body. Skull projections then emerged within the balls of fire, and they were cackling in a sinister voice as the black fireballs shot forth toward Han Li at the thin guard's behest, transforming into countless harrowing ghostly heads as they flew through the air.

The collective cackling of the ghostly heads was like a wave of countless steel needles threatening to surge into the listener's mind.

Chapter 338: Might of the Treasured Axis

In the face of the pair of oncoming guards, Han Li displayed no intention to take evasive measures. Instead, bright golden light emerged over his entire body as he flew directly toward the horde of ghostly heads.

The portly guard let loose a loud roar as he swept his sleeves through the air, and all of the starry sand converged toward Han Li before exploding violently into huge balls of lightning that inundated the entire sky, presenting a formidable sight to behold.

At the same time, the thin guard pointed a finger in Han Li's direction, and all of the ghostly heads in the sky abruptly swelled drastically in size before opening their mouths to send bursts of black light hurtling directly toward Han Li.

The black light didn't appear to have been all that remarkable, but they were giving off an extremely corrosive aura, and the space in their wake was rippling incessantly, as if the streaks of light were capable of corroding the very air itself.

The golden light radiating from Han Li's body brightened, and he suddenly transformed into a golden blur, accelerating drastically as he flew directly into the oncoming attacks.

Not only had he become extraordinarily fast, he was also displaying immaculate bodily control, weaving back and forth through the lightning and black light, and he was always able to just barely squeeze through right before his body was inundated by the oncoming attacks.

This was all thanks to his Reversal True Axis ability, and the pair of guards hurriedly released their spiritual sense in an attempt to track down Han Li's location, but they were completely unable to keep up with his speed, and it was often the case that as soon as they spotted Han Li, he would already be gone.

The surrounding lightning and black light were all extremely fast and formidable attacks, but he was making them appear downright slow and sluggish, and the pair of guards were astonished to see this.

Before they had a chance to do anything, Han Li had already passed through the vast expanse of lightning and black light, then appeared no more than 1,000 feet in front of them in a wraith-like manner.

At this point, the dazzling golden light radiating from his body had already faded, and only now did the pair of guards manage to react, flying back in retreat with astonishment in their eyes.

However, as late-True Immortal cultivators, they possessed a vast wealth of battle experience, and they immediately devised strategies to counteract Han Li.

The portly guard opened his mouth to release a pair of triangular shields that revolved around him briefly before transforming into a thick light barrier, and at the same time, all of the starlight in the sky transformed into countless starlight rings that swept toward Han Li.

Meanwhile, the thin guard was chanting an incantation, and a string of loud cracks were ringing out from within his body as he rapidly swelled in size while his skin and flesh quickly peeled away, turning him into a massive black skeleton that was over 100 feet tall in the blink of an eye.

The black skeleton was giving off an enormous aura that was close to twice as formidable as before, and red light was flashing within its eye sockets as it spread open its huge hands.

Its fingers resembled giant black swords with black flames surging around them, and it reached out to make a grab for Han Li's head.

It was clear from their immaculate teamwork that these two had been fighting alongside one another for a long time, and weren't giving Han Li any opportunity to strike.

However, right at this moment, dazzling golden light erupted out of Han Li's body again, and a golden wheel appeared behind him before rapidly revolving on the spot.

A layer of golden ripples then surged forth from his body, instantly encompassing the entire surrounding area in a radius of around 10,000 feet.

The two guards were also caught within the golden ripples, and their movements immediately became very slow and sluggish.

Additionally, the starlight rings that were falling out of the sky had also come to a complete standstill, as if they had been frozen in place.

In truth, it wasn't entirely accurate to say that they had been completely stopped in their tracks. Instead, they had actually been slowed down to an extreme extent, to the point that it looked no different from coming to a complete stop.

He's using the laws of time!

The silver-robed young man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately flew toward the pair of black-robed guards, leaving the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords behind as he did so.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already transformed into a giant golden ape that was over 1,000 feet tall, and there were silver patterns all over his massive fists as he swung them viciously at the pair of guards.

In response, the two guards remained completely still, as if they were oblivious to the oncoming attack.

The light barrier around the portly guard's body was completely pulverized by a burst of tremendous force, and the giant fist wasn't slowed down in the slightest as it crashed into his body.

At the same time, the other fist struck the black skeleton that the thin guard had transformed into, and right after the two guards were struck by Han Li's fists, all of the golden ripples in the air receded as the flow of time reverted back to its original speed.

The portly guard's body instantly exploded into countless scraps of mangled flesh, while the black skeleton was also shattered into countless bone shards.

Their two souls had also been restricted by the Mantra Treasured Axis, rendering them completely unable to react, so they were also destroyed alongside their bodies.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the silver-robed young man had only just arrived in the sky above the giant ape with a furious look on his face.

Never had he imagined that Han Li would be able to slay a pair of late-True Immortal cultivators in such devastating fashion in such a brief span of time.

The silver-robed young man swept a hand through the air, and a streak of black light flew toward him, containing a black sword that was similar in shape to a beastly fang. The sword was riddled with countless black runes that were giving off law fluctuations, and it swelled to around 1,000 feet in size in the blink of an eye, following which a black wyrm projection appeared around it as it slashed down upon the giant ape.

All of a sudden, the Mantra Treasured Axis behind the giant ape began to spin in reverse before vanishing into its body in a flash.

In the next instant, the giant ape abruptly vanished from the spot, and the huge black sword struck nothing but empty air.

A trail of golden afterimages appeared in the air as the giant ape flew toward the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain in the distance at an incredible speed.

The silver-robed young man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly flew back as quickly as he could, but he was still far from being able to match the golden ape's speed.

By the time the giant ape arrived in front of the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, the silver-robed young man was only halfway there.

The golden ape immediately opened its mouth to release a ball of blood essence, which was instantly ignited into a burst of crimson flames with countless crimson runes dancing within it as it hurtled toward the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The streak of crimson fire was able to pass through the gray light and gray cocoons without any inhibition before vanishing into the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which immediately began to glow with bright azure light again.

At the same time, they were able to tear through the gray cocoons around them, but it seemed that they still weren't going to be able to break free from the gray light anytime soon.

The silver-robed young man was furious to see this, and he was just about to make a hand seal when the giant ape suddenly turned around with bright golden light radiating from its fists, and its arms flashed through the air in a blur as it unleashed a barrage of countless fist projections.

The barrage of golden fist projections swept toward the silver-robed young man with tremendous force, and even before they descended upon him, a burst of tremendous force had already encompassed the entire space within a radius of about half a kilometer around him, causing him to slow down involuntarily.

The silver-robed young man was unable to evade the attack, so he could only sweep a sleeve through the air to release a black shield, which transformed into a black light barrier in front of him.

Countless fist projections crashed into the black light barrier one after another before exploding violently, but the light barrier remained completely unmoved.

However, the silver-robed young man was also temporarily kept at bay.

Golden light flashed over the giant ape's entire body, and a second pair of arms abruptly emerged from its ribs amid a flash of golden light before quickly making a hand seal.

The 72 flying swords glowed even brighter as they fused as one to form a single giant azure sword with thick arcs of golden lightning flashing over its surface amid rumbling thunderclaps.

The giant azure sword began to shudder violently, then transformed into a streak of azure swordlight that was over 1,000 feet in length before slashing viciously against the surrounding gray light.

A peerlessly sharp aura erupted out of the streak of azure swordlight, causing all of the space in its wake to twist and warp incessantly.

A gash was finally torn into the surrounding gray light, and the streak of azure swordlight instantly shot out from within before returning to the giant ape's side, where it reverted back into a giant azure sword.

Immediately thereafter, the giant ape's body blurred, and it vanished from the spot along with the giant sword.

In the next instant, Han Li re-emerged over 10,000 feet away with arcs of lightning flashing over his entire body, and the giant azure sword was also present beside him, but it had shrunk down to no more than 10 feet in length.

Han Li opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence into the azure sword, and it immediately began to glow a shade of azure that was so bright that its radiance rivaled that of the sun.

The remaining black coloration on the sword was instantly erased, and it let loose an elated ringing sound.

Meanwhile, the silver-robed young man remained still on the spot, watching Han Li with a dark expression as he made a beckoning motion to draw the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain back to himself.

The two stood in mid-air while looking back at one another, and neither of them was in any hurry to attack.

A short while later, the silver-robed young man broke the silence. "Looks like I really did underestimate you."

Han Li paid no heed to him as he began to make a rapid string of hand seals.

The giant azure sword beside him split back up into 72 small swords, then circled around him momentarily before transforming into an azure sword array beneath him.

"I was going to take my time and play around with you a little, but it seems like you're more of a pain to deal with than I expected. In that case, I'll just crush you now, then slowly torture your soul," the silver-robed harrumphed coldly.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of black light, which transformed into a black inkstone treasure.

The inkstone was very antiquated in appearance, and as soon as it appeared, countless tiny golden runes immediately surged out of it in a frenzy.

At the same time, it was giving off a burst of peculiar law fluctuations.

The silver-robed young man's aura also began to swell, and the enormous spiritual pressure that was emanating from his body was causing the nearby space to warp and shudder.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this.

The silver-robed young man was finally displaying his full cultivation base, and just as Han Li anticipated, he was a Golden Immortal cultivator.

However, his aura was still far inferior to the likes of Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, and it was rather unstable, indicating that he had only recently progressed to the Golden Immortal Stage and hadn't had a chance to consolidate his cultivation base yet.

Even so, he was still a Golden Immortal cultivator, which was incomparable relative to a late-True Immortal cultivator.

Chapter 339: Giant Eye

The silver-robed young man began to chant an incantation, and a dense stream of runes surged out of his mouth, then swept toward the black inkstone hovering in the air in front of him before vanishing into it in a flash.

The inkstone immediately began to swell drastically, quickly expanding to over 100 feet in size, and all of the scenery and creatures engraved on its surface took on an extremely life-like quality.

For some reason, a hint of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this.

The silver-robed young man switched to a different hand seal before flicking his fingers consecutively through the air, and the giant black inkstone began to revolve on the spot while releasing a vast expanse of black qi that resembled a puddle of black ink that was swirling around in the air above the inkstone.

The black qi quickly formed a dark cloud that was around 1,000 feet in size, and it encompassed both the silver-robed young man and the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain while continuing to rapidly expand.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which his eyes narrowed slightly as he shot back in retreat without any hesitation while sweeping his spiritual sense through the surrounding area.

However, as soon as his spiritual sense entered the dark cloud, he discovered that it was like a vast expanse of nothingness that he couldn't detect anything from.

Upon making this observation, he immediately raised a hand before pointing a finger forward, and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords around him immediately began to glow brightly before quickly forming an azure sword lotus flower around him.

The lotus flower began to rapidly revolve while releasing countless streaks of azure sword qi, which swept toward the black cloud with tremendous might.

Countless streaks of sword qi tore through the black cloud as balls of azure and golden lightning exploded incessantly, tearing countless holes through the cloud and threatening to scatter it altogether.

However, the black cloud was still constantly expanding, and the holes that had been torn into its surface were quickly filled again, leaving the cloud completely unscathed.

It seemed that the formidable storm of sword qi hadn't affected the black cloud at all, and it was as if the silver-robed young man inside had vanished into thin air.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he was just about to do something else when the black cloud finally ceased in its expansion.

It then began to churn violently while releasing countless black runes that converged toward the center, forming a black ball the size of a house in the blink of an eye.

Han Li observed the scene unfolding before him for a moment, then swept a hand through the air, and the azure sword lotus flower in front of him swelled in size while its petals formed several azure light barriers before him.

All of a sudden, the black ball shuddered, and a red line suddenly appeared on its surface before splitting apart in either direction to reveal a massive vertical eye.

The eye was a pristine white color with an inky black pupil, and it appeared to have been no different from an ordinary eye, but it was giving off a peculiar aura, and as soon as its gaze turned to settle upon Han Li, the sense of foreboding in his heart instantly became compounded even further.

He reflexively rushed away to the side, not willing to be under the direct scrutiny of the giant eye, but the eye was able to track his movements, and its gaze remained firmly fixed upon him.

Han Li was quite alarmed to see this, and azure light emerged over his body alongside arcs of golden lightning as he rapidly flew through the air while constantly changing directions, yet no matter what he did, the giant eye continued to track him without fail.

Furthermore, white light was beginning to gather at the center of the eye's pupil, and it seemed to have been preparing something.

All of a sudden, Han Li harrumphed coldly as he withdrew the azure sword lotus flower in front of him, then flew directly toward the black cloud above the giant eye as a streak of azure light, plunging into the cloud in the blink of an eye.

As soon as he plunged into the dark cloud, Han Li immediately felt his surroundings go dark. He swept a sleeve through the air to release a large body of black liquid, and it was none other than the heavy water that he had accumulated over the past years.

The heavy water circled around him once, instantly forming a massive black spherical barrier that encompassed the entire space within a radius of 100 feet around him to keep the black mist at bay.

After doing all of that, he swept his gaze across his surroundings with blue light flashing in his eyes, but all he could see were layers upon layers of dark clouds, and even with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, visibility was limited to no more than 1,000 feet.

Furthermore, his spiritual sense remained severely restricted, and he was barely able to release it out of his body at all.

His brows furrowed slightly as he slowly flew forward with the heavy water barrier around him, and as he did so, he was doing everything in his power to find the silver-robed young man.

However, even after flying for a long while, his surroundings were still filled with nothing but dark clouds.

Furthermore, the cloud didn't appear to have been all that big from the outside, but after entering it, he felt as if he had entered a boundless independent space.

Moments later, Han Li drew to a halt, then inspected his surroundings momentarily before abruptly sweeping a hand forward through the air.

A dull thump rang out as a thick streak of azure sword qi that was over 1,000 feet in length shot forth before plunging into the black cloud up ahead, instantly piercing through it to open up a passageway that was several thousand feet long.

However, in the next instant, the surrounding black clouds quickly converged from all sides, and the hole was instantly filled again.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he swept a sleeve through the air, and the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were released once again before fusing as one into a single giant azure sword that was several thousand feet in length.

The sword was giving off radiant azure light and incredibly thick arcs of golden lightning, and it was so bright that it was blinding to look at.

A large area was instantly torn into the nearby dark cloud, and Han Li made a hand seal, upon which the giant sword beside him began to glow even more radiantly as it slashed viciously through the space up ahead.

The black cloud up ahead churned violently as a massive gash was sliced into it, and the sword strike was so formidable that it had almost sliced the entire black cloud into two.

The entire space that Han Li was situated in began to tremble violently, yet aside from that, there was no other change, and a few moments later, everything reverted back to its original state, as if that sword strike had never been unleashed at all.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, but right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out.

"I didn't think you would rush in here. That's come as quite a surprise, but don't think that this will allow you to avoid my Soul Destroying True Light."

The voice belonged to none other than the silver-robed young man, and as soon as his voice trailed off, a burst of dazzling white light abruptly appeared in the black cloud up ahead before hurtling rapidly toward Han Li.

Han Li remained still on the spot as the giant azure sword in front of him split up into 72 small swords once again, then came together to form an azure sword lotus flower that began to revolve above his head.

At the same time, the surface of the heavy water protective barrier around him also began to flash and ripple incessantly.

In the blink of an eye, the burst of white light reached no more than several thousand feet away from Han Li before drawing to a halt, revealing itself to have been the same black inkstone from before, except it had become semi-transparent.

The silver-robed young man stood behind the inkstone with his hands clasped behind his back and a cold smile on his face.

"I thought you were too much of a coward to come out," Han Li said with a cold smile as he took a glance at the huge inkstone.

A hint of fury flashed through the silver-robed young man's face upon hearing this, and he harrumphed in a cold voice, "If you're so eager to die, then let me grant you your wish!"

The giant inkstone began to revolve on the spot while giving off rays of dazzling light that were as bright as the sun.

Countless white runes emerged, giving off extremely formidable law fluctuations, and a projection of a giant eye appeared before casting its gaze toward Han Li, just like what had happened outside the black cloud.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately dodged to the side.

However, right at this moment, the black cloud above him suddenly began to churn before abruptly splitting apart, and the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain emerged without any warning.

Countless gray runes were swirling around the mountain, giving off dazzling gray light.

A thick pillar of gray light abruptly came crashing down from the heavens, forming a massive gray space that enveloped Han Li's entire body in the blink of an eye.

Enshrouded within the gray light, the spiritual light emanating from the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords immediately dimmed.

Han Li also felt an immense constrictive force around his body, locking him firmly in place and preventing him from moving.

He let loose a low roar, and bright azure light erupted from his body as he struggled with all his might, but the gray light remained completely resolute, and there was some type of law power surging within it, preventing him from breaking free.

Right at this moment, the giant inkstone up ahead revolved on the spot, following which a thick pillar of white light shot out of the huge eye, hurtling directly toward Han Li.

Even before the pillar of white light arrived, Han Li was struck by a burst of sharp pain directly in his soul, and he felt as if many of his memories were about to be extracted.

Thankfully, his enormous spiritual sense was activated on its own, and the disturbance in his soul was quickly quelled.

Even so, he was still quite alarmed by this turn of events, and the heavy water barrier around him immediately converged to form a wall of heavy water in front of him at his behest, shielding him from the white light.

However, the white light was able to easily pass through the wall of heavy water, and it was completely unobstructed.

In this dire situation, Han Li immediately opened his mouth to release his Heavy Water True Axis, which began to rapidly revolve while drastically expanding in size.

A vast expanse of watery light that was interspersed with countless black runes emerged from the axis to form a barrier in front of him, and the Heavy Water True Axis was able to keep the white light at bay.

However, the white light was able to quickly seep through the watery light barrier released by the Heavy Water True Axis, passing through it after just a few seconds.

However, with this brief window of respite, Han Li was able to catch his breath, and he began to chant an incantation.

Bright golden light radiated from his body as his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him before releasing a vast expanse of golden ripples that gave off formidable time law fluctuations swept forth in all directions.

Perhaps it was due to the surrounding black cloud, but the golden ripples weren't able to spread any further than 1,000 feet.

In the next instant, the pillar of white light entered the area encompassed within the golden ripples, and it immediately came to an abrupt halt.

However, if one were to look closely, they would discover that the pillar of white light was still approaching Han Li, except it had been slowed down by an extreme degree.

The silver-robed young man's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he gave a cold harrumph before beginning to chant an incantation while casting several incantation seals at the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain from afar.

All of the countless runes on the surface of the mountain instantly lit up, and the gray light that it was radiating brightened significantly, while countless gray runes surged forth before fusing into the gray area down below.

The gray space was instantly significantly bolstered, thereby further amplifying the restrictive force acting upon Han Li's body.

A series of gray ripples appeared, giving off incredibly formidable law powers to compress against the golden ripples around Han Li, and the two opposing forces clashed together like powerful waves.

The golden ripples shuddered momentarily before shrinking even further, and the pillar of white light was able to draw closer and closer to Han Li again.

Chapter 340: Luring in the Enemy

900 feet...

800 feet...

700 feet...

Under the pressure exerted by the gray light emanating from the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, the golden ripples being released by the Mantra Treasured Axis were constantly being compressed, while the pillar of white light began to steadily accelerate.

At this rate, it wasn't going to take much longer before the pillar of white light broke through the shackles of time to reach Han Li.

Large droplets of sweat began to bead up on Han Li's forehead, and he could clearly sense the sharp pain in his soul being exacerbated as the white light approached him.

His expression had darkened significantly, and he was constantly injecting more immortal spiritual power into his Mantra Treasured Axis, but that was only slightly slowing down the rate at which the golden ripples were being compressed.

A pleased look appeared in the silver-robed young man's eyes upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release a ball of black light, within which countless black runes were dancing incessantly.

He quickly made a hand seal, and the ball of black light split up into two parts, one of which fused into the giant inkstone, while the other vanished into the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

The inkstone and the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain immediately began to glow even brighter, while the gray space around Han Li had virtually taken on a substantial form.

Countless waves of gray ripples were surging forth incessantly to further compress the golden ripples around Han Li, forcing it down to a radius of less than 500 feet.

The pillar of white light grew even brighter, and countless white runes were dancing around within it. It seemed as if it were about to break free from the golden ripples, and the golden ripples immediately around it were illuminated white as the pillar of white light continued to close in on Han Li at a rate that was discernible to the naked eye.

Han Li's complexion began to pale, and despite his best efforts, the golden ripples around him were constantly being shrunk down by the surrounding gray light.

At this point, the pillar of white light was already no more than 200 feet away from him.

The silver-robed young man could already taste his imminent victory, and he made a hand seal once again, upon which another burst of black light emerged from his body.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out behind him, and a golden crab pincer projection the size of a house emerged. The projection was enveloped in countless arcs of golden lightning and giving off formidable law power fluctuations as it hurtled toward the silver-robed young man at an incredible speed.

The silver-robed young man's expression changed drastically as he hurriedly switched to a different hand seal, and a suit of armor instantly appeared over his body amid a flash of black light.

The suit of armor was of a purplish-black color, and its helmet had been crafted in the shape of a dragon's head, while several spikes could be seen on the knee and shoulder joints. The entire suit of armor was also riddled with black patterns and giving off immense baleful qi.

The golden crab pincer struck the suit of purplish-black armor with an earth-shattering boom, and the silver-robed young man was sent flying, while a series of shallow cracks had also appeared on the surface of the suit of armor.

Even with the suit of armor acting as a buffer, a burst of tremendous force was still transferred into the silver-robed young man's body, churning up his internal organs and causing him to throw up a mouthful of blood.

After he was sent flying, the giant inkstone lost its source of immortal spiritual power, and it finally fizzled out no more than 100 feet away from Han Li.

The Integrated Five Extremes Mountain was still hovering above Han Li's head, but the gray light that it was projecting downward had also become rather unstable.

The gray space around Han Li also rippled slightly, and the restrictive force that it was exerting was significantly diminished.

He immediately pounced on this opportunity, releasing several balls of light out of his body that transformed into a series of true spirit projections.

The projections circled around him momentarily before vanishing into his body, and a layer of purplish-golden light surfaced over his skin as his body swelled drastically, transforming into a purplish-golden giant with three heads and six arms.

At the same time, countless golden scales and silver spirit patterns appeared over his skin, and seven specks of dazzling starlight also emerged on his lower abdomen.

An enormous aura then erupted out of his body, causing the surrounding gray space to shudder violently.

The purplish-golden giant made a grabbing motion with one hand, and a huge azure sword appeared in its grasp before being swung down viciously.

An enormous crescent-shaped streak of azure swordlight swept through the air with thick arcs of golden lightning surging around it before crashing into the gray light barrier.

A resounding crack rang out, and this time, a gash was torn into the gray space, revealing the outside world.

The purplish-golden giant immediately flew out through that opening at an incredible speed, following which a vertical black split open on his glabella.

A pillar of translucent light shot out of the vertical eye, then transformed into an indistinct sword that vanished without a trace in a flash.

In the next instant, the sword appeared behind the silver-robed young man's head without any warning before plunging directly forward.

Even though the silver-robed young man had been injured by the previous blow, his reactions remained quite sharp, and he hurriedly swept a hand through the air to conjure up a black palm projection that grabbed toward the translucent sword.

However, in the instant that the black palm projection closed itself around the sword, the latter abruptly vanished.

The silver-robed young man faltered slightly upon seeing this, and before he had a chance to figure out what had happened, the translucent sword reappeared in his mind before slashing viciously down upon his soul.

"Argh!"

The silver-robed young man let loose a bloodcurdling howl as he threw his hands onto his own head.

Right at this moment, Daoist Xie appeared beside the silver-robed young man before spreading its hands open, and a pair of enormous balls of golden lightning appeared before it, both of which were as massive as mountains.

Thick arcs of golden lightning were flashing incessantly over their surfaces, presenting a formidable sight to behold.

Furthermore, the balls of lightning were releasing countless golden lightning runes, each of which was the size of a table and giving off fierce law fluctuations.

Daoist Xie then joined its palms together, and the two massive balls of lightning fused as one before transforming into a gargantuan golden lightning sword amid a rumbling thunderclap.

Golden halos were proliferating in all directions from the giant sword, and all of the surrounding black mist was instantly scattered.

The entire surrounding space in a radius of several dozen kilometers began to buzz audibly, and countless five-colored balls of light formed by the world's origin qi emerged before converging toward the giant sword in a frenzy.

Five-colored light was also surging over the surface of the giant lightning sword, causing the nearby space to ripple and quiver.

All of a sudden, the entirety of heaven and earth had taken on a completely different complexion, and before the silver-robed young man had a chance to react, the giant sword had already crashed down upon him.

Countless cracks appeared on his suit of purplish-black armor before it exploded amid a resounding boom, and his body was also inundated by a vast expanse of lightning before exploding into countless pieces.

Nearby, Han Li had already reverted back to his original form, and he heaved a faint sigh of relief upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, a tiny burst of black light emerged from the silver-robed young man's torn up remains, and it immediately vanished into thin air.

Blue light flashed within Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and a beam of black light shot out of the vertical eye on his glabella, striking a certain spot in the air in a flash before vanishing into it.

A dull thump rang out as that patch of space shuddered, following which a vast expanse of black light emerged, and a tiny black figure that was only several inches tall stumbled out into the open.

This was none other than the silver-robed young man's nascent soul, and even though it had been forcibly revealed by Han Li's Law Destruction Eye, it hadn't sustained any injuries. However, there was a furious look on its face, and it was just about to make a hand seal when a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted out of the nearby area, following which a translucent chain shot out before wrapping itself around the nascent soul like lightning.

The entire chain was giving off translucent silver light and it had a rather insubstantial appearance.

An alarmed look appeared on the nascent soul's face, and it struggled with all its might to break free, but the chain remained as resolute as ever.

In the next instant, Han Li and Daoist Xie appeared right beside the nascent soul, and the latter was holding a pair of treasures in its hands, namely the black inkstone and the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

Without the support of the silver-robed young man's immortal spiritual power, Daoist Xie was able to seize these two treasures with ease.

The nascent soul seemed to know that it wouldn't have been able to escape no matter what, and it took a glance at Han Li before turning its gaze to Daoist Xie.

"I didn't think that you would have such a trump card up your sleeve. And this chain, if I'm not mistaken this is a spiritual sense chain, so you must've cultivated some type of forbidden technique, right?" the nascent soul asked in a calm voice.

Han Li paid no heed to the nascent soul as he swept a hand through the air to release a burst of azure light, which swept downward before retrieving a pair of storage treasures, the very same ones that the pair of black-robed guards had been carrying.

After that, he released a burst of crimson flames to sweep up silver-robed young man's remains, and after his body had been completely incinerated, the crimson flames surged back, carrying a black ring with it.

Han Li stowed these items away in an unhurried manner, then turned to nascent soul as he asked, "Who are you and why have you repeatedly come after me? If you give me a satisfactory answer, I can grant you a quick and painless death."

"If you're going to kill me, then do it! I'm not going to answer any of your questions!" the nascent soul replied with a cold smile.

Han Li didn't say anything further as he reached out with one hand to grab onto the nascent soul's head, and a burst of black light erupted out of his hand, enveloping the nascent soul before attempting to infiltrate its body.

The nascent soul's face instantly became twisted with pain, but a mocking sneer appeared in its eyes as it spat through gritted teeth, "To think that a mere True Immortal like you would attempt to search a Golden Immortal's soul. What a joke!"

Han Li paid no heed to the nascent soul's mockery as he continued to unleash his soul search technique with all his might.

Waves of black light surged out of the palm of his hand to envelop the nascent soul, but sure enough, his efforts proved to be futile.

"It's no use, Fellow Daoist Han. There is an evolution in one's nascent soul from the True Immortal Stage to the Golden Immortal Stage, so there's no way you'll be able to search his soul. As for me, I'm just a puppet, so I can't use any soul search technique, either," Daoist Xie said.

Han Li slowly released the nascent soul upon hearing this.

The nascent soul heaved a sigh of relief, following which a cold sneer appeared on its face as he said, "If you dare to kill me, then Xiao Jinhan will hunt you down no matter where you go! If you let me go, I can swear a soul vow to settle our differences, and on top of that, I can give you some compensation as well."

Chapter 341: Nascent Soul Refinement

"I don't recall ever saying that I plan to let you live," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

Before the nascent soul had a chance to reply, Han Li opened his mouth to release a burst of silver fire, which instantly enveloped the nascent soul, and it was none other than Han Li's Flame of Essence.

The nascent soul immediately began to howl in agony within the silver flames, but not only was it not displaying any sign of being incinerated, it was no exaggeration to say that its aura hadn't even abated in the slightest.

In a very uncommon turn of events, it seemed that the Flame of Essence was completely ineffective on the nascent soul.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and the silver flames immediately began to swirl around the nascent soul as a tiny fiery vortex at his behest, giving off heat that was several times more intense than before.

"Han Li! The Heavenly Court won't let you get away with this!" the nascent soul howled, and it had taken on a slightly transparent quality within the fiery vortex.

However, the Flame of Essence was unable to affect the nascent soul any further beyond that.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li flicked a finger through the air, releasing a streak of azure sword qi that struck the nascent soul in a flash.

A loud thump rang out as the streak of sword qi exploded, and a faint mark appeared on the nascent soul from its head to its abdomen, but the mark quickly vanished without a trace.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

"Fellow Daoist Han, the nascent souls of Golden Immortal cultivators are extremely resolute and are fundamentally different from True Immortal Stage nascent souls. At this rate, it's going to take at least several years for you to completely destroy it. This battle hasn't gone on for very long, but there's no guarantee that the people at the White Jade Peak haven't noticed his absence," Daoist Xie said.

"What do you suggest I do with this nascent soul then, Brother Xie? If I just let it go free, there will be no end to the troubles to come," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Golden Immortal Stage nascent souls are quite difficult to destroy, but only for a True Immortal. With my current Golden Immortal Stage power, I can destroy this nascent soul for you, as long as you're willing to spend the required Immortal Origin Stones," Daoist Xie replied.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up slightly upon hearing this. "Go ahead, Brother Xie, I'm willing to spend the Immortal Origin Stones."

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then opened his mouth to release a vast expanse of golden lightning, which intertwined briefly in the air to form a dense net of lightning that ensnared the nascent soul.

Arcs of lightning were flashing incessantly over the surface of the lightning net, and it was giving off an astonishingly formidable aura, forming a golden and silver ball of light as it intertwined with the Flame of Essence.

The sound of crackling rang out incessantly as the nascent soul began to spasm violently, and it was becoming transparent at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

Around 15 minutes later, Daoist Xie made a hand seal, and all of the arcs of golden lightning faded to reveal a nascent soul that was enveloped in silver flames.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but then unfurrowed just as quickly.

The body of the nascent soul still remained, but it had already turned completely transparent with only faint traces of golden light left on its surface. Its eyes were completely lifeless, and the spiritual fluctuations that it was giving off were extremely feeble, so it was clear that the spiritual power within it had already been completely destroyed, leaving nothing more than an empty husk behind.

"Why didn't you destroy this nascent soul altogether, Brother Xie? Surely you still have some Immortal Origin Stones leftover from the 500 that I gave you," Han Li asked.

"I have no intention of saving Immortal Origin Stones for you, it's just that I suddenly recalled that Golden Immortal Stage nascent souls are a primary ingredient for refining a pill known as the Golden Soul Pill, so it would be a waste to destroy it. At this point, even if there had been any restrictions planted in the nascent soul, they would've already been completely refined, so you don't have to worry about keeping it by your side," Daoist Xie explained.

"What does this Golden Soul Pill do?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not sure. Recently, I've been recollecting tidbits of memories, and one of those contained information about the Golden Soul Pill. It seems to be quite a rare type of pill, and I'll tell you what it does if I manage to recall," Daoist Xie replied.

"Alright," Han Li replied with a nod, then withdrew his spiritual sense chain.

After that, he pulled out a jade box and placed the nascent soul inside it, then adhered a few sealing talismans to the box before stowing it away.

"Congratulations on recovering a lost treasure, Fellow Daoist Han. This treasure here is also quite a formidable one," Daoist Xie said as it handed over the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain and black inkstone that it was holding.

Han Li accepted the pair of treasures, and an excited gleam appeared in his eyes as his gaze first settled upon the black inkstone.

This was most definitely an Acquired Immortal Treasure of a very high caliber, and the Soul Destroying True Light that it was capable of releasing appeared to have contained some type of law power that could directly harm one's soul. This treasure was most likely the culprit behind his amnesia and subsequent descent into the Spirit Domain Realm.

Aside from that, the black cloud space that it carried was also quite a good trapping device.

However, he had no time to inspect this treasure on an in-depth level for now, and he turned his gaze to the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

He had refined this treasure in preparation for his ascension tribulation transcendence, and he had invested immeasurable time, effort, and resources into the treasure's creation. Now that he had recovered it, he couldn't help but feel a little sentimental.

Just as the silver-robed young man had declared, the current Integrated Five Extremes Mountain was already far different from what it had once been. Its basis was still the five mountains, but each mountain had been infused with many types of spirit materials, and it had also been refined using a more advanced method.

Just the thought of the restrictive ability unleashed by the silver-robed young man using this treasure was enough to get Han Li rather excited.

However, time was of the essence right now, so he didn't have time to closely inspect the pair of treasures, and he quickly stowed them away.

"We should get away from here as soon as possible, Fellow Daoist Han. We need to leave before the battle at the White Jade Peak comes to an end," Daoist Xie warned.

"I want to get out of here as well, but this restriction is quite formidable and not so easy to break through. Do you have any ways to bypass it?" Han Li asked with a wry smile.

Daoist Xie flew over to the wall of yellow mist as he spoke, and he inspected it briefly before suddenly pressing a palm flag against it, following which a layer of yellow light appeared over his hand.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which a hint of intrigue appeared in his eyes.

Ever since it had fully integrated itself with this puppet, Daoist Xie had become much more life-like and bore a much closer resemblance to an actual living cultivator.

Moments later, Daoist Xie withdrew its palm, and Han Li asked, "What do you think?"

"This is a very profound restriction with many interconnected layers. Whoever set up this restriction has to be an exceptional master," Daoist Xie mused.

"Is there a way to break through it?" Han Li asked.

"There is, but it's going to require a large sum of Immortal Origin Stones to activate one of this immortal puppet's abilities," Daoist Xie replied.

"How many will you need?" Han Li asked.

"In addition to what I have left, I'll need... about 300 more," Daoist Xie replied.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, and a wry smile appeared on his face as he said, "That's fine, just do what you need to do."

In order to lure in the silver-robed young man so that Daoist Xie could attack him, he had already placed around 600 to 700 Immortal Origin Stones into Daoist Xie's body, and now that he was having to spend 300 more Immortal Origin Stones, that was already close to a third of his entire wealth.

It seemed that he had to be sparing in his reliance on Daoist Xie unless it was absolutely necessary. He was still hoping to be able to purchase some dao pill ingredients using his Immortal Origin Stones, and that was going to be a significant expenditure.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to produce a storage pouch, which he tossed at Daoist Xie.

Daoist Xie wasted no time in pulling all of the Immortal Origin Stones out of the storage pouch before directly swallowing them, then said, "I'll also require the assistance of your dao warriors."

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, but he duly obliged, handing over his dao warrior gourd to Daoist Xie.

Daoist Xie made a hand seal, and a burst of bright yellow light immediately emerged at the opening of the gourd, following which a series of dark yellow beans came falling out like rain.

Before long, several hundred dao warriors beans had been tipped out, and Daoist Xie began to chant an incantation, upon which the patterns on the surface of the beans lit up in unison.

The beans began to give off a bright yellow glow, but instead of transforming into dao warriors, they expanded slightly before slowly elongating to form what appeared to have been a series of yellow wooden rods.

Bright yellow light was radiating from these wooden rods, and they connected together to form a seemingly haphazard array, but in reality, it was far more profound than it seemed.

Han Li was quite intrigued to see this.

It wasn't a rare occurrence for dao warriors to be used to set up arrays, but Han Li had never seen anyone use dao warriors as array flags as Daoist Xie was doing here, and he couldn't help but wonder if this method of dao warrior usage was something that Daoist Xie had recently recalled.

As Daoist Xie continued to chant its incantation, it released a series of incantation seals out of its hands, every single one of which fell upon the wooden rods with unerring accuracy.

All of the hundreds of wooden rods shuddered in unison, and countless translucent yellow threads rose up from them before intertwining to form a yellow array.

Immediately thereafter, Daoist Xie thrust both palms forward, and all of the wooden rods instantly flew into the wall of yellow mist, which began to churn and produce a layer of yellow light to obstruct the wooden rods.

Daoist Xie was making a rapid string of hand seals, and countless bursts of yellow light were rapidly circulating throughout the yellow array, forcibly nullifying the yellow light being released by the wall of mist as the wooden rods slowly progressed forward.

The section of the wall of mist that was encompassed within the yellow array began to rapidly dissipate, creating a huge indentation.

As the yellow mist scattered, a translucent light barrier with lights of different colors surging over its surface was revealed, and it appeared to have been another profound restriction.

Han Li gave a slight nod at the sight of the array, while Daoist Xie sat down with its legs crossed as it continued to chant its incantation.

All of a sudden, thick arcs of golden lightning emerged over its body, giving off bursts of violent law fluctuations that proliferated in all directions.

All of the world's origin qi in a radius of thousands of kilometers was stirred up, forming balls of purple light that converged toward Daoist Xie.

Chapter 342: Leaving the Sect

A series of dark clouds emerged, and they quickly came together to obscure the entire sky. Arcs of lightning could be seen occasionally flashing within the clouds amid deafening thunderclaps, and boundless lightning-attribute spiritual qi was converging from all directions before fusing into the clouds.

Daoist Xie made a hand seal as it chanted an incantation, and lightning was flashing over its body before spreading outward to form an enormous lightning array that was several dozen acres in area.

The lightning array was rather peculiar in that it was very thin and long, and there were countless lightning runes drifting through the air within it.

All of a sudden, Daoist Xie opened its eyes before casting an incantation seal up toward the heavens, and bolts of lightning began to crash down from the clouds.

All of the lightning was injected into the lightning array around Daoist Xie, causing it to glow radiantly while giving off bursts of thunderous rumbling.

Han Li was standing in mid-air, and he appeared to have been quite calm and composed, but in reality, he was feeling quite tense.

His battle against the silver-robed young man had been quite brief, but it had caused quite a commotion, and this lightning array was giving off extremely formidable energy fluctuations that were definitely detectable to those at the White Jade Peak.

He could only hope that the battle there was still raging so that he would have enough time to make his escape.

Right at this moment, Daoist Xie let loose a low roar, and the lightning array abruptly rose up from the ground, hovering in mid-air while rapidly shrinking down.

Just a few seconds later, it had shrunk down from its original size of several dozen acres down to a ball of lightning that was only around 200 to 300 feet in size, and it was giving off blinding lightning that was too bright to look directly at.

"Go!"

Daoist Xie abruptly rose to its feet as it made a hand seal, and the ball of lightning shot forth as a streak of white light, striking the indentation in the wall of yellow mist at an incredible speed while revolving rapidly.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, and all of the mountains within a radius of several hundred kilometers began to rumble violently. Massive trenches opened up in the earth, and some of the smaller mountains were toppled altogether, presenting a doomsday-like scene to behold.

The yellow mist restriction was also churning violently, and it was as if turbulent waves were rolling over its surface.

Incredibly thick bolts of lightning were erupting out of the ball of lightning before spreading through the yellow mist restriction, peeling it away layer by layer, but at the same time, the surrounding yellow mist was also constantly converging to replenish the mist that was being stripped away, and an impasse had ensued.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I need your help!" Daoist Xie suddenly said.

Han Li immediately sprang up into the air without any hesitation upon hearing this, and after a few flashes of azure light, he appeared no more than 1,000 feet away from the indentation in the yellow mist restriction.

He then swept a sleeve through the air to release 72 streaks of golden light, which circled around him momentarily before instantly forming a giant golden sword that was several hundred feet in length with golden lightning flashing around it.

Han Li made a hand seal, and the giant sword slashed forward at his behest.

All of a sudden, a streak of swordlight that was over 1,000 feet in length with golden lightning flashing over the entirety of its blade struck the indentation in the yellow mist with tremendous might.

A resounding boom rang out, and that sword strike from Han Li proved to be the final straw that broke the camel's back, tearing apart all of the yellow mist that was converging from all directions to significantly slow down the restriction's rate of recovery.

Daoist Xie let loose a loud roar upon seeing this, and the ball of light exploded violently into an incandescent sun as shockwaves that were visible even to the naked eye erupted in all directions. Finally, a huge hole the size of a house had been blown into the yellow mist restriction.

After unleashing that attack, the lightning flashing over Daoist Xie's body quickly faded, and it was looking rather weary.

Han Li immediately swept a hand through the air to cast an incantation seal, and the hundreds of dao warrior beans flew back out of the wall of yellow mist before returning to his gourd. Immediately thereafter, a burst of azure light erupted out of his body, sweeping up both Daoist Xie and the gourd before he flew out of the restriction through the massive hole.

Right after he had flown out through the hole, yellow mist converged from all directions to seal it again in the blink of an eye.

All of the unrest in the wall of yellow mist then quickly subsided, and it was as if nothing had ever happened.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the sky outside, and he heaved a long sigh of relief, feeling as if he had just escaped from the brink of death.

He then turned to Daoist Xie as he asked, "How are you feeling, Brother Xie?"

"The restriction was far more formidable than I anticipated. It's a good thing that you intervened at the perfect time to break the restriction, but I'm going to have to take a long rest after this, Daoist Xie replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then swept a sleeve through the air to release 12 lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood, then began to chant an incantation.

Arcs of lightning emerged over the Lightning Restraining Wood, quickly forming a lightning array with countless lightning runes flashing within it, causing the nearby space to warp and ripple.

Han Li closed his eyes momentarily to sense something, then quickly reopened them before giving a slight nod and withdrawing his hand seal.

The lightning array immediately ceased operating, and countless arcs of lightning flowed back into the lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood before they were stowed away.

The lightning teleportation array was functioning as normal, which meant that there were no further spatial restrictions up ahead.

"Even for the Immortal Palace, setting up this one restriction would've already been quite difficult, so there's no way that there could be a second, even larger restriction outside of it," Daoist Xie remarked.

"That may be the case, but the situation over at the White Jade Peak could take a turn at any moment, so let's get out of here for now," Han Li said as he took a glance back at the yellow mist restriction, then made a hand seal to conjure up a smaller lightning array around himself.

Daoist Xie flew into Han Li's grasp as a streak of golden light, following which both of them were teleported away.

……

Around two hours later.

Arcs of golden lightning sprang out of the space above the Crimson Dawn Peak to form a lightning array, and Han Li emerged inside it, looking a little pale and weary.

He had unleashed his lightning teleportation array consecutively in order to reach the Crimson Dawn Peak as quickly as he could, and even with the support of Immortal Origin Stones, his immortal spiritual power reserves were still severely depleted.

Han Li took a deep breath before descending out of the sky.

All of the servants had already been alerted by the thunderclap that had just rung out, and they hurriedly rushed forward to greet Han Li.

Many of the servants of True Immortal Stage elders had gone to attend the preaching ceremony as well, and at this moment, there were only three servants left on the mountain. After all, the mountain couldn't just be left completely unattended.

The three servants were just about to extend bows to Han Li when he raised a hand and said, "No need for formalities. Wait here for a moment, I have something to speak to all of you about."

After that, Han Li immediately flew into his cave abode in a flash, arriving directly at the spirit medicine garden inside.

He had a habit of carrying important items on his body, but he couldn't constantly carry these spirit medicines with him, and that was why he had taken the risk to come back here despite the urgency of the situation.

He had expended a huge amount of time, energy, and resources gathering these spirit medicines, and he certainly couldn't just leave them behind.

He swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which instantly encompassed the entire spirit medicine garden.

In the next instant, all of the spirit medicines rose up out of the ground alongside the surrounding plots of spirit soil before flying into Han Li's grasp one after another. He then quickly stored them into suitable containers before stowing them away in his storage bracelet.

Moments later, the entire cave abode shuddered as all of the restrictions were removed, and a series of array tools flew out of all parts of the cave abode before also being stowed away.

Outside the cave abode, the three servants were exchanging puzzled glances with one another.

"What's going on?" a square-faced young man murmured in an uncertain voice.

Meng Xiong was one of the three servants, and he shook his head in response. "I don't know, but judging from Elder Li's expression, something very important must've happened. Perhaps it has something to do with those violent tremors we felt earlier."

Right at this moment, Han Li appeared before them in a wraith-like manner amid a flash of azure light, and before the three servants had a chance to do anything, he said, "Time is of the essence, so I'll keep it brief. The sect has encountered a major crisis concerning the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and there will most likely be very far-reaching consequences.

“I'm planning to leave this place right away, and you have two options right now: come with me, or stay here to fend for yourself. You've all been serving me for many years, so even if you choose to stay, I'll leave you with some treasures and resources."

The expressions of the three servants changed drastically upon hearing this.

This was far too abrupt a turn of events, and they had no idea what to do.

"I'll give you 10 seconds to make your decision," Han Li said as he clasped his hands behind his back.

As soon as his voice trailed off, Meng Xiong stepped forward as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

"Elder Li, my aptitude is quite mediocre, and without everything you've given me, there's no way I would've made it to my current cultivation base. I'm willing to continue to follow you."

Han Li nodded in response, then gestured for Meng Xiong to stand beside him.

Immediately thereafter, the square-faced young man also stepped forward, expressing a desire to follow Han Li.

The young man's name was Meng Guang, and he was a man of few words.

The final servant remained standing on the spot with his head lowered, and he wasn't saying anything, but his decision was clear.

Han Li didn't say anything, either, flipping a hand over to produce a storage pouch that he tossed at the servant.

"Thank you, Elder Li," the servant said as he caught the storage pouch before hurriedly extending a respectful bow.

"Let's go," Han Li said, then swept a sleeve through the air without delay, releasing a burst of azure light that swept up Meng Xiong and Meng Guang before flying away.

Shortly thereafter, on a mountaintop not far away from the Crimson Dawn Peak, Han Li's trio was surrounded by a circle of Lightning Restraining Wood.

Han Li made a hand seal, and arcs of golden lightning sprang out of the Lightning Restraining Wood to form a huge lightning array around them.

The surrounding space began to ripple like water, and the ripples spread outward in all directions.

Meng Xiong and Meng Guang were quite alarmed to see this, and both of them reflexively closed their eyes.

Immediately thereafter, the three of them vanished amid a flash of lightning and a rumbling thunderclap.

Chapter 343: Plans

In a certain region of the sea to the west of the Ancient Cloud Continent.

This place was near the Thunderstorm Sea, and the sky was filled with dark clouds with bolts of lightning flashing within them.

However, in contrast with the lightning deep within the Thunderstorm Sea, the lightning here was far less formidable. Occasionally, a bolt of lightning or two would come crashing down out of the sky, but for the average cultivator, as long as they proceeded with caution, they were at no threat of severe bodily harm.

The seawater here was extremely murky, almost like mud, and the entire surface of the sea was enshrouded under a dense blanket of gray mist that seemed to have been infinitely vast, and there were strange gusts of wind howling within the mist that produced a sound resembling human sobbing.

This place was known as the Sobbing Mist Sea, and it was a very renowned area to the west of the Ancient Cloud Continent, but not for good reasons.

Beneath this region of the sea was an enormous gray rock crystal mine, and after it had been completely exhausted of its mineral resources, the seawater had taken on this murky appearance, and this blanket of gray mist had arisen.

The murky seawater and the mist weren't harmful to human cultivators, but the marine demon beasts here seemed to intensely detest this environment, and most of them had moved away. As a result, the cultivator population in the region was also decreasing year after year, making this place more and more barren and desolate.

Deep within the sea of mist was a black island that only had a radius of less than 10 kilometers, and at the center of the island was an extremely desolate black mountain that was several thousand feet tall.

Right at this moment, a burst of golden light flashed within an obscure cave at the foot of the mountain, and the entire mountain shuddered slightly.

The golden light flashed a few times before abruptly brightening significantly, and even the surrounding black mountain face had been illuminated a golden color, while an enormous aura was surging out of the cave.

However, right at this moment, an azure light barrier appeared at the opening of the cave with countless azure runes flashing over its surface, intercepting the aura before it could spread even further.

Even so, the entire island still shuddered violently, while the nearby gray mist was also churned up into a frenzy.

Right at this moment, a loud squawk rang out in the distance, and an azure shadow flew out at an incredible speed before landing near the black island, revealing itself to be an azure bird.

The bird was massive with a wingspan of around 200 to 300 feet, and it had a large head coupled with a thin neck. Its entire body was covered in arrow-like azure feathers, and there was a large fleshy pouch hanging in front of its chest, giving it a rather hideous appearance.

Standing atop the bird's back was none other than the Meng Qianqian, and the bird was naturally Featheryearn.

A hint of elevation appeared in Meng Qianqian's eyes at the sight of the golden lightning flashing in the cave, and all of a sudden, the golden lightning in the cave brightened even further, while thick arcs of golden lightning began to emerge.

The parts of the black rock walls that were struck by the arcs of golden lightning shattered like tofu, and it didn't take long before the entire mountain collapsed violently to reveal a ball of lightning that was several hundred feet in size.

The shadow of a massive lightning array could be seen within the ball of light, and arcs of golden lightning were crashing into the surrounding azure light barrier, causing it to tremble violently, but it remained intact.

All of a sudden, the ball of golden lightning flashed once again, and an incredibly thick pillar of golden light tore through the azure light barrier before erupting into the heavens.

All of the world's origin qi within a radius of hundreds of kilometers churned violently, as did the nearby sea of mist, forming a huge vortex around the pillar of lightning.

The pillar of golden lightning remained for a few seconds before slowly dissipating, and the ball of golden lightning on the island also vanished to reveal Han Li, Meng Xiong, and Meng Guang.

Meng Qianqian immediately flew down from Featheryearn's back with an elated expression, and she was just about to say something when Han Li said, "Now's not the time to talk. Come with me!"

Immediately thereafter, he summoned an azure flying boat amid a flash of azure light, and it instantly swelled to over 100 feet in size.

One either side of the flying boat were two rows of azure spirit wings that were formed by spiritual power.

This Azure Luan Boat was something that he had obtained from a True Immortal while undertaking a mission, and it wasn't a treasure of a particularly high caliber, but it was quite fast, nonetheless.

Han Li flew onto the flying boat, closely followed by Meng Xiong and Meng Guang.

Meng Qianqian faltered slightly before also doing the same, then cast an incantation seal to stow Featheryearn into her spirit beast pouch.

With a flick of his finger, around a dozen thick streaks of azure sword qi were sent flying through the air before striking the black island down below, instantly destroying what remained of it and causing it to completely sink into the sea without a trace.

At the same time, Han Li made a hand seal with his other hand, and the azure flying boat began to glow radiantly as it shot forth into the distance as an azure shadow, vanishing in the blink of an eye.

Not long after their departure, two streaks of light arrived from afar, revealing a pair of humanoid figures, one of which was a middle-aged daoist priest wearing a black hat, while the other was a gray-robed elderly man.

"This is the place! The spiritual qi fluctuations still haven't completely dissipated yet," the daoist priest said with a hint of excitement on his face.

There was an elated look on the gray-robed elderly man's face as well, and he nodded in response. "Indeed, and these are some extremely formidable spiritual qi fluctuations. I spotted a huge pillar of golden light rising up into the air from here. Could it be that some treasure is about to emerge?"

As he was speaking, he had already released his spiritual sense to inspect his surroundings.

"That's definitely a possibility. This region of the sea has always been very unpredictable, so nothing would surprise me," the daoist priest replied, then flipped a hand over to produce a yellow plate treasure with countless runes engraved on its surface.

Bursts of rippling yellow light swept forth from the plate treasures, encompassing the entire surrounding area within a radius of several kilometers.

After scouring the area for a while to no avail, the gray-robed elderly man asked, "Have you found anything, Fellow Daoist Wan?"

The daoist priest remained silent, continuing to use his plate treasure to release halos of rippling yellow light.

Moments later, he withdrew his hand seal, and the gray-robed elderly man hurriedly asked, "How did it go?"

"That pillar of light wasn't a precursor for the emergence of any treasure. Instead, it was a result of someone unleashing some type of ability here," the daoist priest sighed.

The gray-robed elderly man's face fell slightly upon hearing this, and he was still holding onto a shred of hope as he asked, "Are you sure?"

"All nine layers of restrictions in my Precious Domain Plate have been activated, so there's definitely no mistaking it," the daoist priest replied with a roll of his eyes.

The gray-robed elderly man shook his head with a wry smile as he replied, "In that case, it looks like we got excited for nothing. By the way, have you managed to detect that person's cultivation base?"

"Judging from the lingering spiritual qi fluctuations here, they were most likely at or above the Body Integration Stage," the daoist priest replied.

The gray-robed elderly man's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and a hint of lingering fear appeared in his eyes as he said, "In that case, it's a good thing that we arrived late. Otherwise, if we had been any earlier and irked that senior, then we would've been in severe danger."

"In any case, we should leave this place right away to avoid any potential misunderstandings," the daoist priest replied in a calm voice.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Wan," the gray-robed elderly man immediately replied with a nod.

Shortly thereafter, two streaks of light rose up into the sky before flying away into the distance.

……

At this point, Han Li and the others were already hundreds of thousands of kilometers away.

Han Li circled around above the sea for a while, then arrived in another large coastal city in the western region of the Ancient Cloud Continent.

This place was known as Heavenly Cloud City, and it was the capital of the Heavenly Cloud Nation. It was quite a large city that directly neighbored a spirit vein of a decent size, making it a very habitable place.

Not only was the city quite close to the Thunderstorm Sea, its large size meant that many of the cultivators passing through the area would choose to stop here for some rest and to replenish supplies.

Some of the high-grade cultivators returning from adventures in the Thunderstorm Sea would also come to the city to sell or exchange their spoils.

As a result, Heavenly Cloud City was becoming more and more prosperous by the day, and it had already become one of the largest cities within a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers.

Han Li and the others snuck into the city, then chose a secluded medium-sized inn to stay in.

Even the most formidable cultivator stationed in the city was only at the Body Integration Stage, so there was naturally no chance of Han Li being discovered.

That night, in the guest hall.

Han Li was seated on the main chair, while Meng Xiong, Meng Guang, and Meng Qianqian were standing respectfully before him.

After conjuring up a soundproofing restriction, Han Li gave the trio a brief recount of what had taken place in the Blaze Dragon Dao.

At this point, Meng Qianqian possessed the most advanced cultivation base out of all of the servants, but she was quite lacking in life experience, and she was momentarily completely rooted to the spot after hearing such shocking news.

Meng Xiong and Meng Guang were already aware that something had to have happened during the preaching ceremony, but they were still astonished after hearing Han Li's story.

"Qianqian, I'll give you a choice just like I gave the others, and the conditions remain the same. What is your choice?" Han Li asked.

Meng Qianqian remained silent, seemingly still reeling from the bombshell that had just been dropped on her.

"If you need to discuss the matter with Yungui before you make a decision..."

"There's no need for that," Meng Qianqian replied without any hesitation. "I wasn't hesitating, Elder Li, I was just surprised. Regardless of what choice my brother makes, I'm willing to continue to follow you."

Han Li nodded in response, then said, "Right now, I'm no longer an elder of the Blaze Dragon Dao, so you're not to refer to me as such in the future, understood?"

"Yes, Senior Li," the three servants immediately replied in unison.

Han Li didn't say anything further as he rose to his feet, then made his way over to the window, casting his gaze out toward the distant Thunderstorm Sea with a contemplative look in his eyes.

After a long while, Han Li still hadn't said anything, and after a brief hesitation, Meng Qianqian asked in a timid voice, "What are your plans from here, Senior Li?"

Han Li offered no response, seemingly still contemplating something in silence.

Meng Qianqian's trio exchanged a glance with one another, and they naturally didn't dare to disturb him, so they could only wait in silence.

A long while later, Han Li finally declared, "I'm planning to leave the Ancient Cloud Continent for a while."

Chapter 344: Spoils

Meng Qianqian faltered slightly upon hearing this, then hurriedly said, "Brother Li, my brother and Brother Sun still haven't arrived yet, would you be able to wait a bit longer? They're very loyal to you, and I'm sure they'll choose to continue to follow you."

"Your cultivation bases are still quite lacking, so I'll leave all of you here in Heavenly Cloud City. This city has quite a good spirit vein nearby, and it'll be perfect for your cultivation needs," Han Li replied.

Meng Qianqian was rather unwilling to accept this arrangement, but she could tell that Han Li had already made up his mind, so she could only nod in response. "Yes, Senior Li."

"Come with me," Han Li said, then began to make his way outside.

Shortly thereafter, the four of them arrived in a peaceful forest by the name of Moonview Forest in the western part of the city.

The forest was closest to the spirit vein, so the world's origin qi here was very abundant, and there were individual courtyards littered throughout the forest, all of which were enshrouded in restrictions and separated by some bamboo forests and fake mountains.

These were temporary cave abodes constructed by high-grade cultivators who had come from outside the city. After all, some cultivators preferred peace and quiet and didn't want to stay in inns.

At this moment, Han Li and his group were strolling through the forest under the guidance of a white-robed young man.

"All of our cave abodes were designed by master artisans, and the forest is split up into four areas, A, B, C, and D. The cave abodes in Area A have the most abundant spiritual qi, while the ones in Area D have the least spiritual qi.

“Right now, we're in Area D, but even here, the world's origin is far more abundant than other places in the city, and it can accelerate one's rate of cultivation by a quarter, whereas the cave abodes in Area A can enhance one's rate of cultivation by a half," the white-robed young man introduced in an enthusiastic fashion.

"Take us to Area A," Han Li said in an expressionless manner.

The white-robed young man could tell that Han Li was the one calling the shots, and he was ecstatic to hear this. "Please come with me, fellow daoists."

Moments later, the group passed through an archway and arrived in a large bamboo forest, within which some cave abodes could be seen.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this. The world's origin qi here was far more abundant than outside, almost comparable with some of the mountains in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and Meng Xiong and Meng Guang were ecstatic to sense this, while Meng Qianqian was trailing along at the back in silence with a complex look on her face.

"This is Area A. What do you think, fellow daoists?" the white-robed young man asked.

Instead of replying to the question, Han Li asked, "Are there any vacant cave abodes here?"

The white-robed young man's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and he replied, "We do. There are three vacant cave abodes."

"What price can you do for me if I rent them long-term?" Han Li asked.

The white-robed young man took a glance at Han Li, then stated a price.

Han Li turned to inspect his surroundings, refraining from offering a response for now.

"Our cave abodes are the best in Heavenly Cloud City, so the rent is a little more expensive, but you're definitely getting good value for money..."

Han Li waved a hand to cut off the white-robed young man, then pulled out a storage pouch that he tossed at him as he said, "I'll rent all three cave abodes for 300 years for now."

The white-robed young man caught the storage pouch, then inspected its contents briefly with his spiritual sense, and an ecstatic look immediately appeared on his face.

He pulled out three azure badges before handing them to Han Li, then said, "These are the restriction badges for the three cave abodes. Do you need me to take you there?"

"No need, we'll go on our own. You can go now," Han Li replied as he accepted the badges.

The white-robed young man promptly departed, while Han Li pulled out another storage pouch before handing it to the three servants along with the three badges.

"There are some cultivation resources in this storage pouch. Stay here and cultivate, and I've already informed Meng Yungui and Sun Buzheng to come here."

Meng Xiong and Meng Guang both nodded in response.

"How long will you be gone for, Senior Li?" Meng Qianqian suddenly asked.

"At least a few decades, perhaps even over a century. If any of you change your mind during this time, then you're free to leave," Han Li replied in a calm manner, then abruptly vanished from the spot.

Meng Qianqian hurriedly strode forward a few steps, but Han Li was already nowhere to be seen, so she could only heave a forlorn sigh, but a determined look then appeared in her eyes.

Several months later.

A massive black boat was sailing through the waves somewhere on the Thunderstorm Sea.

The seawater around the giant boat was churning incessantly, with waves that were several hundred feet tall occasionally rising up, and the dark clouds in the sky were hanging at a very low altitude with thick bolts of lightning crashing down every once in a while.

The boat was completely unobstructed by the waves and lightning, and it was rapidly advancing over the sea like a giant beast.

The black was a Seafaring Lightning Boat, and it was traveling from the Ancient Cloud Continent to Thunderclap City of the Primordial Wave Continent.

In contrast with the hostile environment outside, everything was very harmonious within the giant boat, with people constantly passing through the corridors, while the restaurants and tea rooms on the top floor of the boat were very lively and bustling.

Some of the cultivators in the boat had even gathered together to hold some small exchange events or to discuss cultivation insights and experiences.

One of the rooms in the boat was completely enshrouded within a soundproofing azure light barrier, and on the bed inside the room sat a man with a dark complexion.

There were seven blue rings hovering around him, and they were drifting up and down incessantly while giving off a faint buzzing sound.

The man's eyes were closed, and he was making a string of hand seals.

Meanwhile, the seven rings were glowing brighter and brighter, and a formidable burst of law power fluctuations was spreading through the air.

A faint smile appeared on the man's face as he made a hand seal, and the seven rings instantly fell into his grasp.

The man was none other than Han Li in disguise, and these seven rings were called the Seven Bright Star Rings, a rare set of immortal treasures that he had found in the portly black-robed guard's storage tool.

It was primarily used to trap enemies, and the law power that it contained was also geared toward trapping.

Han Li had conducted some experiments during the past few days to find that these Seven Bright Star Rings were quite formidable. In particular, when used during clear nights, the rings could resonate with the star power in the night sky to significantly enhance their power.

It was most likely the case that Han Li had struck with such efficiency and brutality that the portly guard didn't even have a chance to summon this treasure before he was killed.

Han Li opened his mouth to produce a burst of azure light that stowed the rings back into his body.

Even though he had already recovered the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, having more trapping treasures was naturally never a bad thing.

During the time that he had spent on the Seafaring Lightning Boat, the rings had already been partially refined, and it wasn't going to take much longer for him to complete the refinement process.

Aside from that, the thin guard also had a formidable immortal treasure called the Asura Heavenly Ghost Flag in his storage tool.

However, this was a ghostly immortal treasure that wasn't very suitable for his cultivation arts, so he only briefly inspected it before returning it to his storage bracelet.

As for the silver-robed young man, he was a Golden Immortal cultivator who clearly had very powerful backers, and he had far more treasures than his two late-True Immortal Stage guards, possessing four immortal treasures.

Aside from the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain and the black inkstone, there was also the silver bell that he had summoned at the beginning of the battle and a black fang-shaped sword.

With that in mind, Han Li opened his mouth to release the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, and it hovered in front of him while revolving on the spot, releasing a vast expanse of gray light that was interspersed with gray runes and was giving off a burst of formidable law power fluctuations.

He had already carefully examined the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain to find that its outward appearance hadn't changed much, but internally, it had changed drastically, with many spirit materials infused into all of the five extreme mountains.

Even though he had refined the five extreme mountains, materials like the Divine Essencefused Mountain and Arctic Origin Crystals had proven extremely difficult to come by, and he had only just barely managed to gather enough to refine the five extreme mountains.

Somehow, the silver-robed young man was able to find a large amount of all five types of materials, enhancing the power of the five extreme mountains by almost twofold. Furthermore, he had also used some type of refinement method to completely fuse the five mountains into one, thereby further significantly bolstering its power.

In particular, the law powers imbued within it had become far more formidable than before.

Various thoughts were flashing through Han Li's mind as he felt the law fluctuations emanating from the small gray mountain.

Back in the Spirit Realm, his cultivation base had been too lowly for him to be able to grasp law powers, so he hadn't paid much heed to the hint of law powers that the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain contained.

However, things were completely different now. Having already reached the late-True Immortal Stage, he had faced many formidable foes and witnessed many types of law powers, thereby granting him better insight into the law fluctuations that the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain was giving off.

This law power was extremely profound, and it seemed to have been related to trapping, but was also completely different from the trapping law powers imbued within the Seven Bright Star Rings.

However, as for how these law powers differed and how he could hope to truly master them, Han Li still had no clue, and he shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought.

Even directly devouring the Heaven Controlling Vial spirit liquid that contained the power of time laws wasn't enough for him to master the laws of time, so it was undoubtedly going to be even more difficult to try and master certain law powers through immortal treasures alone.

Seeing as he couldn't figure it out, then there was no point thinking excessively about it. In any case, adding these formidable treasure to his collection was certainly a good thing.

With that in mind, he opened his mouth to swallow the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain again.

He was the one who had created this treasure, so it wasn't going to take him long to refine it again now that he had recovered it.

Aside from the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, Han Li had recovered another lost treasure from the silver-robed young man's storage tool, namely the Thunderstorm Wings.

This treasure was nowhere near as powerful as the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, but it had been with him ever since his time in the Mortal Realm, so he was naturally very happy to have recovered it.

Perhaps the Thunderstorm Wings hadn't managed to catch the silver-robed young man's eye, but it had never been refined, and it was casually tossed to the bottom of his storage tool, where it had most likely already stayed for many years.

Hence, he was able to easily break the seal and regain control over the Thunderstorm Wings, thereby saving him the trouble of having to refine it.

Chapter 345: Laying Low

At the moment, Han Li was simultaneously refining the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, the Seven Bright Star Rings, and that silver bell in his body all at once.

The bell was an immortal treasure that contained some type of soundwave law powers, and the fact that it was able to scatter the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords with just a single attack was clear testament to its power, and that was why Han Li had decided to work on refining it.

As for the black fang-shaped sword, it was similar to the Asura Heavenly Ghost Flag in that it was also a yin-attribtue treasure, so he had set it aside.

At the moment, his spiritual sense was comparable to that of even early-Golden Immortal cultivators, but refining three immortal treasures at once was still his limit.

As for the black inkstone that was capable of unleashing the Soul Destroying True Light, it contained far more law power than the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, the silver bell, and the other immortal treasures.

Han Li naturally wanted to be able to make the treasure his own, but it seemed to be containing some type of restriction that made it impossible for Han Li to refine it no matter what he tried.

This left Han Li feeling a little frustrated, but he wasn't short on immortal treasures at the moment, and he didn't have that much time on his hands, so he could only set the inkstone aside for now.

Aside from immortal treasures, the trio's storage tools also contained many other treasures, as well as countless pills and precious materials. In particular, the silver-robed young man alone possessed as many as over 10 materials that were imbued with law powers.

Additionally, the three of them had a total of over 10,000 Immortal Origin Stones, and with such a massive haul, Han Li wouldn't have to worry about Immortal Origin Stones for a very long time.

However, the biggest pleasant surprise to Han Li was that he had found a large amount of dao pill ingredients in the silver-robed young man's storage tool.

There were as many as seven of the nine ingredients listed on the dao pill recipe, and all of them were in quite large quantities as well.

Han Li was initially quite shocked by this, but everything immediately made sense to him after he found an identical dao pill recipe to his own.

It seemed that the silver-robed young man also had intentions of refining a dao pill, and given his status and the enormous power of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, that wasn't going to be a difficult objective to accomplish, but now, those ingredients had fallen into Han Li's hands.

At this point, he was only missing two dao pill ingredients, the Heavenmade Ginseng Root and the Dewform Herb, and he was sure that he would be able to acquire them as long as he kept an active eye on the information circulating within the Transient Guild.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized golden badge, which was crafted from some type of special metal, and it was extremely heavy despite its small size.

On one side of the badge was a design of a golden dragon that was roaring to the heavens, giving off a sense of unmatched power and regal authority, while on the other side was a name: Tao Yu.

Above the name was a feather crown design, and Han Li's expression darkened slightly at the sight of the golden badge.

Right at this moment, he suddenly raised an eyebrow as he opened the window of his cabin.

Outside was the turbulent Thunderstorm Sea, but the Seafaring Lightning Boat had restrictions all around it, so the sound of the thunder and the crashing waves was mostly kept out.

A faint glimmer of golden light appeared in the distant sky before vanishing in a flash, and in the next instant, a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted within Han Li's cabin as a lightning array appeared, following which Daoist Xie emerged inside it.

The golden lightning array quickly surged into Daoist Xie's body as arcs of golden lightning, and Han Li took a brief glance at Daoist Xie before remarking, "Looks like you've made a complete recovery."

Daoist Xie nodded in response. "I didn't think the lightning power here would be so abundant. That was really beneficial to my recovery."

Han Li offered no response to this as he stepped aside to allow Daoist Xie into the cabin, then sat back down with his legs crossed.

Daoist Xie had severely exhausted itself from the earlier battle, and after arriving in the Thunderstorm Sea, it had immediately begun absorbing the extremely abundant lightning power here to replenish itself. To Han Li's relief, it was able to make a full recovery in just a few months.

Having a Golden Immortal Stage ally was extremely helpful, so it was very important that Daoist Xie was in good condition.

"It looks like you're still worried about that Tao Yu," Daoist Xie remarked as it caught sight of the golden badge that Han Li was holding.

"I wouldn't exactly say that I'm worried. I already killed him, so there's no point in thinking about it. I'm just wondering if the Immortal Palace has already found out that I'm the one who killed him," Han Li replied.

Previously, he had spent a great deal of Immortal Origin Stones to search for information on this golden badge in the Transient Guild, and his efforts had paid off.

This badge was an elder badge of the Immortal Palace, and Tao Yu was the name of the silver-robed young man. He was also a newly promoted elder of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and on top of that, he wasn't actually from the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. Instead, he had been sent here from some other immortal region over 1,000 years ago to accumulate experience, and he certainly wouldn't have anticipated meeting his demise in this foreign immortal region.

There was no way that the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace would let him get away with this, so at this moment, he was leaving the Ancient Cloud Continent with the intention of returning to the Black Wind Sea, both to check on his Earthly Deity Avatar and to lay low for a while.

The Black Wind Sea was a very secluded place that was virtually completely cut off from the outside world, thereby making it a suitable place for him to hide from the Immortal Palace.

"Given the power of the Immortal Palace, it shouldn't be difficult for them to identify you as the culprit, but you left in a very timely fashion, and thanks to that long-distance lightning teleportation array, even the Immortal Palace shouldn't be able to track you down anytime soon," Daoist Xie said.

"I certainly hope that's the case," Han Li said with a wry smile. "By the way, I didn't think you would be able to master the lightning teleportation array so quickly. That came as quite a surprise to me."

"The array is quite profound and combines both lightning power and spatial power. It's a good thing that I already have innate mastery over lightning power. Otherwise, I wouldn't have been able to grasp it so easily," Daoist Xie replied.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he asked, "Have you noticed anything strange or interesting while cultivating in the Thunderstorm Sea, Brother Xie?"

"Not that I can recall. Are you referring to anything in particular?" Daoist Xie asked.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then told Daoist Xie about the giant eye in the lightning cloud vortex that he had seen during his last trip across the Thunderstorm Sea.

A solemn look appeared on Daoist Xie's face as it exclaimed, "That's very shocking to hear!"

"Does anything in your memories match the description of the eye?" Han Li asked.

"No. This is my first time here in this Thunderstorm Sea. Having said that, I don't think even a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal would be able to severely wound you with just a single glance like that giant eye did," Daoist Xie said.

"Both Xiao Jinhan and Dao Lord Baili were only one step away from reaching the High Zenith Stage, but I feel like even if they were to reach the High Zenith Stage, they still wouldn't have been able to display even a fraction of that eye's power," Han Li agreed with a nod.

"This place is already quite close to the central region of the Thunderstorm Sea, and that's where I encountered that giant eye. Now that you've already fully recovered, I suggest you remain inside the Seafaring Lightning Boat so you don't run the risk of encountering that formidable being," Han Li said.

Furthermore, he had followed his own advice, remaining strictly within the Seafaring Lightning Boat during this entire trip thus far.

"Alright," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

……

Meanwhile.

Ouyang Kuishan and the other dao lords that had turned on the Blaze Dragon Dao were standing in the main hall of the sect, and all of their auras were rather unstable, indicating that they still hadn't recovered from their injuries.

Standing across from them were seven or eight other Golden Immortals from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, while Xiao Jinhan was seated on the main chair in the hall.

All of the dao lords were rather disgruntled to see Xiao Jinhan occupying such an important seat in the sect, and a few of them were glowering at him with outright fury, but Xiao Jinhan paid no heed to them as he asked, "How are things coming along?"

"We've already managed to track down Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni. Both of them fled to the Upper Arr Continent with severe injuries, and Elder Lu Yue has already gone after them with some other elders. I'm sure an outcome will arise there soon. However, Baili Yan remains elusive to this day, and it's unclear how he's managed to do so," an elder of the Immortal Palace reported.

"Very good. Even though Baili Yan is still on the run, he's already been severely wounded, and after his karmic fire remission, his past several million years of cultivation has all gone to waste, so he won't pose a threat to anyone. In fact, he most likely won't even be able to withstand the fifth decay," Xiao Jinhan said with a nod.

It seemed as if he was saying this to all of the Immortal Palace cultivators present, but all of the dao lords were also listening with mixed feelings.

"Dao Lord Ouyang, Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni have committed the cardinal crime of treason by assisting the Reincarnation Palace. According to the rules of the Heavenly Court, all of their relatives and disciples must be apprehended and sent to the Heavenly Court. Have you done this yet?" Xiao Jinhan asked as he turned to Ouyang Kuishan.

"Yes," Ouyang Kuishan replied with his eyelid twitching slightly.

"Very good. You can all go now," Xiao Jinhan said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

All of the Immortal Palace cultivators promptly departed, while the dao lords exchanged a few glances with one another, and only after a subtle gesture was made by Ouyang Kuishan did all of them exit the hall as well.

Moments later, all of the dao lords were gathered outside the hall, and the golden-furred man among them wore a furious expression as he grumbled, "What are the intentions of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, Dao Lord Ouyang? The incident concerning Baili Yan has already come to a conclusion, so why are they still here? Are they trying to take advantage of this opportunity to take over our Blaze Dragon Dao?"

"If I had known this would happen, I wouldn't have helped them target Dao Lord Baili. If Dao Lord Baili were here, Xiao Jinhan definitely wouldn't have dared to be so arrogant," the silver-skinned woman said in a cold voice.

Complex looks appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this, while Ouyang Kuishan remained silent with a wry smile on his face.

The Immortal Palace's intentions were very clear. Following the recently concluded battle, the Blaze Dragon Dao had suffered severe losses, and it was no longer a match for the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace.

At this point, Xiao Jinhan alone would've been sufficient to wipe out the entire Blaze Dragon Dao.

Chapter 346: Wanted Fugitive

While Ouyang Kuishan and the dao lords were lamenting the circumstances, a grim look had also appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face inside the hall.

At this point, he had already stood up from his chair and was pacing back and forth with his brows tightly furrowed.

Moments later, a burst of white light suddenly rose up from his body, then transformed into a white light screen in front of him.

A white humanoid figure appeared on the screen with dazzling white light radiating from their entire body, giving them a rather blurry appearance, and one could only just barely make him out to be a middle-aged man.

Xiao Jinhan immediately ceased in his pacing as he forced a smile onto his own face. "Elder Tao."

"Xiao Jinhan, it's already been several months, have you found out who the killer of my son is?" the white figure asked in a cold voice.

"It was an inner sect elder of the Blaze Dragon Dao by the name of Li Feiyu. He has already fled from the Blaze Dragon Dao, and we've sent out people to apprehend him," Xiao Jinhan immediately replied.

"An inner sect elder? You're telling me a mere inner sect elder was able to kill Yu'er?" the white figure asked as a hint of fury crept into his voice.

"He's no ordinary elder," Xiao Jinhan hurriedly replied. "According to our investigation, he was only in the Blaze Dragon Dao for no more than 1,000 years, and when he first arrived, he was only at the early-True Immortal Stage, but we've since determined his cultivation base to have already reached the late-True Immortal, and he's cultivating the Blaze Dragon Dao's Mantra Axis Scripture. On top of that, he seems to be connected to Baili Yan as well. I have a feeling he most likely has some connection to the Reincarnation Palace."

"I don't care who he is! I entrusted my son to you, and now, he's been killed! Xiao Jinhan, you better provide me with a satisfactory outcome. Otherwise..."

The white figure's voice trailed off there, but the threat that he was making was already very clear.

Xiao Jinhan's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and he lowered his head slightly as he replied, "Rest assured, Elder Tao, I'll be sure to get to the bottom of this."

The white figure gave another cold harrumph before vanishing amid a flash of light, following which Xiao Jinhan raised his head with a steely expression.

He then called out to someone outside the hall, and a golden-robed young man immediately flew in before falling to one knee.

"What are your instructions, Palace Master?"

……

Two years flew by in a flash.

Outside Thunderclap City, a giant boat slowly drew to a halt, and moments later, a series of figures flew out from within before descending onto a huge dock.

Han Li was among them, and a reminiscent look appeared in his eyes at the sight of Thunderclap City.

At this moment, his aura was restrained to the early-Grand Ascension Stage, so he didn't stand out among the cultivators around him.

He took a subtle glance at his surroundings, and upon verifying that there was nothing strange happening on the dock, his expression eased ever so slightly as he quickly made his way into the city.

Thunderclap City hadn't changed much since his last visit. The Urgent Lightning Trees were still as vast as ever, and the streets were just as packed and lively.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li made his way toward a certain direction, and it didn't take long before he arrived at the Thunderclap City Immortal Outlet.

Just like before, the Immortal Outlet was very lively and bustling with many cultivators inside, most of whom were gathered around the missions wall.

Han Li also arrived in front of the missions wall, then cast his gaze upward, and a grim look quickly appeared on his face.

Near the top of the wall was an extremely eye-catching mission that was presented in large golden text: "Apprehend Blaze Dragon Dao Elder Li Feiyu. Reward: 20,000 Immortal Origin Stones. Anyone who provides accurate information on him can also receive a reward of 2,000 Immortal Origin Stones."

After the mission was a portrait of Han Li.

"Looks like things have gotten quite troublesome. These Immortal Outlets are present on all continents, so you're most likely a fugitive all over the entire immortal region at the moment," Daoist Xie mused in Han Li's mind.

"20,000 Immortal Origin Stones, eh? The Immortal Palace sure does think highly of me!" Han Li chuckled coldly internally.

"Who is this Li Feiyu? 20,000 Immortal Origin Stones is a huge reward!"

"Haven't you heard? An internal conflict arose in the Blaze Dragon Dao several years ago, and it's said that their first dao lord was working with an evil organization to try and take over the entire immortal region. Fortunately, Palace Master Xiao of the Immortal Palace discovered the plot in time and put an end to it. I'm assuming this Li Feiyu must be an ally of the Blaze Dragon Dao's first dao lord."

"I see. He must've also committed some heinous crimes!"

"I'm sure he did. Otherwise, there's no way they'd be offering such a huge reward for his capture."

There was a spirited discussion taking place in the nearby crowd, and Han Li inspected the missions wall for a while longer, then walked around the Immortal Outlet for a bit before leaving in an unhurried manner.

Even though he was also confident that there was no way that the Immortal Palace would be able to track him down, he was currently being wanted everywhere, so he had to be careful. Otherwise, a single misstep could lead to his demise.

After leaving the Immortal Outlet, Han Li visited the materials shops in Thunderclap City.

Thunderclap City was an important city that connected the Primordial Wave Continent to the Ancient Cloud Continent, so it had an even more diverse array of materials than some of the large cities on the Ancient Cloud Continent.

After returning to the Black Wind Sea, it would become rather inconvenient to purchase things, and he couldn't make all of his purchases solely through the Transient Guild, so he had to buy some things here first in case certain unprecedented needs arose.

After doing all of that, he left Thunderclap City.

At this point, he had already adopted another disguise, transforming into a fair-skinned scholar, and his cultivation base had also been restrained down to the Body Integration Stage.

He lingered momentarily outside the city, then flew away in an unhurried manner as a mundane streak of azure light.

"Aren't there teleportation arrays in Thunderclap City?" Daoist Xie asked in his mind. "Why didn't you leave using one of them? That would've made things a lot easier."

"Thunderclap City is a very renowned city on the Primordial Wave Continent. If the Immortal Palace is searching for me, this is most likely one of the places that they'll be keeping a close eye on, and there may be some treasures here that can expose my true appearance, so it's better to proceed with caution," Han Li explained.

Not only was he going to refrain from using teleportation arrays in Thunderclap City, he was going to avoid them elsewhere as well.

At his current speed, it would only take him several years to cross the Primordial Wave Continent anyway.

"You sure are as cautious as ever. Even while buying things in the city, you adopted several disguises."

"It can't hurt to be careful."

At this point, Han Li had already flown a sufficient distance out of the city, and after confirming that he wasn't being followed, he immediately accelerated, flying into the distance at a far higher speed than before.

Unbeknownst to Han Li, the extra caution that he was exercising had indeed paid off.

In order to search for him, the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace had invested a huge amount of effort and resources. Not only were they actively scouring the entire immortal region for him, special sensory restrictions had also been set up in the teleportation halls of all of the major cities.

The restriction had been set up in accordance with the aura that Han Li had left behind in the wake of his battle against Tao Yu, and it would raise the alarm if Han Li were in its vicinity.

All True Immortals had some ways through which they could alter their auras, so this was far from a foolproof method, but it was already the best that the Immortal Palace could do.

In order to set up these restrictions, not only had the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace invested a huge amount of Immortal Origin Stones, Xiao Jinhan was forced to give up a massive portion of his personal wealth as well.

As for why these restrictions had been set up in teleportation halls, this was because, generally speaking, one would reflexively activate their cultivation arts to protect oneself in the instant that they were teleported away, and that was the best opportunity for the sensory restrictions to detect Han Li.

The population density near Thunderstorm City was quite high, so Han Li didn't fly at his full speed, only raising his speed to about the same level as the average True Immortal while also taking as secluded a route as possible.

Only after passing the areas of high population density did he gradually begin to accelerate.

The Primordial Wave Continent was a very perilous place, but given his current powers, he would have no trouble traversing through it.

After about three years of travel, he finally arrived at Seaside City.

Instead of entering the city, he hovered in mid-air, looking down at the small city from above.

A short while later, he cast his gaze toward another direction, where the teleportation array that led to the Black Wind Sea was situated.

"I'm finally back," Han Li murmured to himself, then flew in that direction as a faint azure shadow.

Even though many years had already passed by, he naturally hadn't forgotten where the teleportation array was situated, and it didn't take long before he was close to reaching the location.

All of a sudden, he stopped cold in his tracks as his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

As it turned out, the seaside cave had disappeared, and it had been replaced by a city.

The city wasn't very large, only less than 10 kilometers in size, and its walls were constructed from giant white bricks, standing at around 200 to 300 feet tall. The entire city was enshrouded under a dense light barrier that was giving off a gentle white glow, and through the light barrier, one could see a series of tall buildings.

At the center of the city was a white pagoda that was far taller than the surrounding city walls, presenting a magnificent sight to behold.

There was only a single city gate, above which was a plaque that read "Wave View City."

Han Li swept his spiritual sense through the surrounding area momentarily before landing outside the city gate, where there was already a long line of cultivators waiting to enter the city.

At this moment, Han Li had disguised himself into a young man with a yellow complexion, and his cultivation base had also been restrained down to the Body Integration Stage, so he didn't stand out at all.

As soon as Han Li joined the line, the slightly portly young man in front of him turned around with a friendly smile as he said, "I don't recall seeing you around these parts, Fellow Daoist. Is this your first time in Wave View City?"

"That's right," Han Li replied with an indifferent nod.

The young man seemed to have been completely oblivious to Han Li's rather cold demeanor, and his smile remained unchanged as he asked, "Where are you from, Fellow Daoist? Have you also come here because you want to go out to hunt for marine demon beasts?"

Han Li offered no response, merely taking a glance at the young man to discover that he was at the late-Body Integration Stage.

The young man's smile stiffened slightly at the sight of Han Li's slightly hostile gaze, and an awkward look appeared on his face as he said, "Please pardon my rudeness. My name is Qin Zhong, and I have a decent reputation in this city. If you want to form a demon beast hunting team, you can come to me at any time."

Chapter 347: Spot

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he nodded in response. "I see. Greetings, Fellow Daoist Qin, my surname is Liu."

"It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Fellow Daoist Liu," Qin Zhong said with a smile.

He was a very talkative person, and after a brief chat, the tense atmosphere quickly mellowed out.

"Do you know when this city was constructed, Fellow Daoist Qin? I came here once several hundred years ago, and this city didn't exist back then," Han Li asked.

"This city was only constructed just over 100 years ago, and there's a teleportation array in the city leading to the Black Wind Sea, so there are often specialty local products from that region appearing in the city. As a result, it's become more and more renowned and attracted many people, so it's been quite prosperous of late," Qin Zhong explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod, and his heart sank slightly upon hearing this.

This was a sign that the Black Wind Sea's connection with the outside world had improved significantly, which was perhaps a good thing for the Black Wind Sea. After all, the Black Wind Sea had far less abundance in cultivation resources than the rest of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so this was certainly good news for the cultivators in the area.

However, this was certainly not encouraging news for Han Li, who was trying to lay low.

While the two of them were chatting with one another, the line continued to progress onward, and it didn't take long before it was their turn.

After submitting an entrance fee, Han Li was quickly allowed into the city.

Everything in Wave View City gave off a sense of newness. The ground and the streets were virtually completely pristine, as expected of a newly constructed city.

Han Li took a glance at his surroundings, then cast his gaze up toward the pagoda in the distance.

The white pagoda had five floors, and there were five blue jade pillars hovering above it, each of which several dozen feet tall and as thick as a bucket with countless runes inscribed upon them.

The five jade pillars were radiating blue light and bursts of formidable spatial power fluctuations that were resonating with one another.

Qin Zhong could see Han Li looking up at the pagoda, and he asked, "You must be on your way to the Black Wind Sea, right, Fellow Daoist Liu?"

Han Li nodded in response, then asked, "Does the teleportation still happen once per century?"

He didn't bother to try and hide his intentions of going to the Black Wind Sea as many of the people who came to this city were en route to the same destination.

"That's right. You came at a very good time as the next teleportation takes place in less than two years. However, there are many people seeking to go to the Black Wind Sea at the moment, so competition for spots is very fierce, and it most likely won't be easy for you to claim one," Qin Zhong said in a meaningful voice.

"It sounds like you have a way to secure a spot. If that's the case, please enlighten me," Han Li said.

Indeed, judging from how many people were in the city, the teleportation spots most likely were going to be hotly contested.

Of course, if he were to display his true power, then he would be able to secure a spot with ease, but that could expose his identity, so if he could acquire a spot from Qin Zhong instead, he was willing to do so, even at an inflated cost.

"I do indeed have a spot right now, and if you're interested, we can have a more in-depth conversation," Qin Zhong said as he glanced at a nearby restaurant with a mysterious smile on his face.

"Of course," Han Li replied with a nod.

The two of them entered the restaurant, requested a booth, then ordered some food and wine.

"The clear spirit wine of this restaurant is quite exquisite. Have a taste, Fellow Daoist Liu," Qin Zhong said with a smile as he filled Han Li's cup.

The wine was a clear green color with a thin layer of spirit mist drifting on top, giving off an intoxicating aroma.

Han Li took a glance at it, but remained unmoved.

In contrast, Qin Zhong seemed to have been quite an avid drinker, and he downed two cups of wine in a row.

Right as Qin Zhong was about to fill his cup a third time, Han Li finally interjected, "Let's leave the drinking for later, Fellow Daoist Qin. How about we discuss the teleportation spot first?"

"Please pardon me, Fellow Daoist Liu. I no longer have a need for sustenance, but I've never been able to give up good food and wine. Let's cut straight to the chase. I can tell that you're quite a direct and straightforward person, so I won't waste your time."

Qin Zhong set down his cup as he spoke, and a serious look appeared on his face.

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"This is your first time here in Wave View City, so you're probably unfamiliar with the state of affairs here. Right now, there are many people who want to go to the Black Wind Sea, but for some reason, the Black Wind Sea has severely tightened its regulation of teleportation spots, so not just anyone can claim one with Immortal Origin Stones alone.

“On top of that, you need to have some local forces vouch for you, so it's become a lot more difficult for outsiders to enter the Black Wind Sea," Qin Zhong prefaced.

"I've always heard that the Black Wind Sea is different from other places in the immortal realm in that it's a relatively isolated area, and that the majority of its cultivators are descendants of the Earthly Immortals there, so they can't be faulted for trying to mitigate risk. Tell me about the spot that you have, Fellow Daoist Qin," Han Li said.

There didn't appear to have been any urgency in Han Li's demeanor at all, so Qin Zhong could only continue, "My spot doesn't actually belong to me. Instead, it belongs to a good friend of mine. She was originally planning to go to the Black Wind Sea for some business matters, but she just so happened to have reached a critical juncture in her cultivation and requires some pills, and that's why she's trying to sell her spot."

"I see, but if the teleportation spots really are so sought after, then surely she would've been able to sell it long ago instead of holding it to this point, so why does she still have it?" Han Li asked.

"To tell you the truth, this friend of mine is rather short on funds at the moment, so she's asking quite a steep price for this spot," Qin Zhong revealed.

Han Li was actually rather relieved to hear this, and he asked, "How much is she asking for the spot?"

"15 Immortal Origin Stones," Qin Zhong replied after a brief hesitation.

"15? If I recall correctly, each spot used to cost five Immortal Origin Stones," Han Li said as he raised an eyebrow.

"The spots are still selling for five Immortal Origin Stones each, but as you know, demand is quite high right now, and spots have occasionally popped up in the black market for around 10 Immortal Origin Stones each.

“Furthermore, the black market sellers aren't responsible for finding anyone to vouch for you. 15 Immortal Origin Stones is a little steep, but my friend's clan is a very influential one in this area, and they can vouch for you free of charge," Qin Zhong replied.

"I see..."

Han Li stroked his own chin as a contemplative look appeared on his face, seemingly weighing up his options.

"You're probably not aware of this, Fellow Daoist Liu, but at the moment, the Black Wind Sea is increasingly tightening regulations on its teleportation arrays. All those who enter and exit the Black Wind Sea are thoroughly examined, and if anyone causes any trouble in the Black Wind Sea, then the power that vouched for them would receive a very severe punishment.

“Hence, the reputable powers in the city normally aren't willing to vouch for outsiders, and even if you pay someone to do so, five Immortal Origin Stones may not get the job done," Qin Zhong hurriedly added.

"In that case, why are you so certain that your friend's clan would be willing to vouch for me?" Han Li asked.

"My friend has already considered this eventuality, so she requested me to get to know someone before I offer them the teleportation spot. We've only just met, but I can tell through our conversation on the way here that you're not some heinous individual," Qin Zhong explained with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response. "Alright, then I agree to your offer."

A hint of elation flashed through Qin Zhong's eyes upon hearing this, and he hurriedly said, "In that case, I'll notify my friend to come here right away."

"Alright, I'll wait here, please be back soon," Han Li replied with a nod.

Qin Zhong downed his cup of wine, then rose to his feet and cupped his fist toward Han Li in a parting salute before quickly leaving the booth.

Following his departure, Han Li also rose to his feet, then made his way over to the window and cast his gaze toward the white pagoda in the distance with furrowed brows.

It seemed that some significant changes had taken place in the Black Wind Sea since his departure, and he wasn't sure if he had made the right decision in coming back.

An hour passed by in the blink of an eye, and Qin Zhong finally returned with a smile on his face.

Trailing along behind him was a figure dressed in white, wearing a veiled conical hat that obscured her features.

The figure lifted the veil to reveal a set of stunning features, but her skin was abnormally pale, as if there were a layer of frost over her skin, and her entire body was giving off a glacial aura.

"Sorry to keep you waiting for so long, Fellow Daoist Liu," Qin Zhong said in an apologetic manner.

"It's fine," Han Li replied with a nod, then cast an inquisitive gaze toward the woman in white.

"That's right, this is the friend of mine who has the teleportation spot."

Qin Zhong took a glance at the woman as he spoke, and his eyes were filled with affection, clearly indicating that he was head over heels for her.

The woman blushed slightly and glared at Qin Zhong in a shy manner, but there was a hint of affection in her eyes as well.

Both of them had clearly been cultivating for countless years, yet they were acting like a pair of young lovebirds, and Han Li couldn't help but roll his eyes internally upon seeing this.

"My name is Xue Luo, it's a pleasure to meet you, Fellow Daoist Liu," the woman said to Han Li in a slightly shy manner.

"The pleasure is all mine, Celestial Maiden Xue. Would I be able to see the teleportation token?" Han Li asked.

Both Qin Zhong and Xue Luo were at the pinnacle of the Body Integration Stage, and the latter's aura was fluctuating slightly, and that was a precursor for an imminent breakthrough.

"Of course."

Xue Luo pulled out a palm-sized black badge, and on one side was inscribed the words "Black Wind", while "Teleportation" was inscribed on the other.

The badge was identical to the one that Han Li had once received from the master of Black Wind Island, and he inspected it briefly before giving a nod, then swept a sleeve over the table to produce 10 Immortal Origin Stones.

Xue Luo's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and Qin Zhong's face also fell slightly as he said, "Fellow Daoist Liu, we agreed on 15 Immortal Origin Stones!"

Chapter 348: Questions

"Truth be told, I'm a little short on funds at the moment as well, and I only have 10 Immortal Origin Stones. Can I substitute the remaining five Immortal Origin Stones with these?"

Han Li swept a sleeve over the table once again as he spoke, and five fist-sized white crystals appeared, all of which were giving off wisps of glacial qi.

Of course, he didn't care about a mere five Immortal Origin Stones. Instead, the problem was that he was posing as a Body Integration cultivator at the moment, and it would've been far too eye-catching for him to easily produce 15 Immortal Origin Stones.

In the Black Wind Sea, even an early-True Immortal Stage Earthly Immortal wasn't guaranteed to have 15 Immortal Origin Stones in their possession.

"These are Frost Soul Crystals!"

Xue Luo was ecstatic at the sight of the white crystals, and she immediately picked one up for a closer inspection.

Qin Zhong was about to raise some objections, but he immediately decided to hold his tongue upon seeing Xue Luo's reaction.

"I would like to substitute these five Frost Soul Crystals for five Immortal Origin Stones. Will that be alright?" Han Li asked.

"That's perfectly fine," Xue Luo immediately replied with a nod, then immediately stowed the crystals away as if she were afraid that Han Li would change his mind.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he also stowed the badge away in an unhurried manner.

"Fellow Daoist Liu, I'll have to trouble you to come with me to my clan to finalize the vouching proceedings," Xue Luo said.

"That's fine. Thank you, Celestial Maiden Xue," Han Li replied with a nod.

Xue Luo hesitated momentarily, then cast a hopeful gaze toward Han Li as she asked, "Also, would you happen to have more of these Frost Soul Crystals?"

"Why do you ask? Would you like to buy some?" Han Li asked.

Xue Luo exchanged a glance with Qin Zhong, then replied, "These crystals are very useful to me, so if you do have some more, I'm willing to purchase them from you."

"If you have any Frost Soul Crystals to spare, you'll be doing us a huge favor, and if you need any help from me, I'll be sure to heed your call," Qin Zhong immediately chimed in.

Han Li took a glance at the duo, then swept a sleeve over the table to produce a pair of white crystals as he said, "I do actually have two more Frost Soul Crystals."

Each of these two Frost Soul Crystals was around twice the size of each of the previous five, and Xue Luo was ecstatic to see this, but she refrained from immediately reaching out for the crystals.

Instead, she took a deep breath, then asked, "Would you be able to sell them to me, Fellow Daoist Liu? I'll be sure to give you satisfactory compensation."

"I came across these Frost Soul Crystals by chance anyway, so if you want them, I can give them to you free of charge," Han Li said as he pushed the two Frost Soul Crystals toward Xue Luo.

A hint of surprise flashed through Xue Luo's eyes upon hearing this, and she shook her head as she replied, "I can't just accept such a precious gift free of charge! Please state a price, Fellow Daoist."

"In that case, how about this? Seeing as you come from a prominent clan in Wave View City, I'm sure you must have many information sources. Has anything major happened in the Black Wind Sea recently? Also, why has the Black Wind Sea suddenly become so much stricter in its examination of people seeking to enter the region? If you can answer those two questions, I'll give you these two Frost Soul Crystals," Han Li said.

A hint of elation flashed through the eyes of Xue Luo and Qin Zhong upon hearing this, and the former asked, "Is that a serious offer?"

"Most certainly so," Han Li replied without any hesitation.

Xue Luo took a moment to gather her thoughts, then said, "While Wave View City and the Black Wind City are only separated by a single teleportation array, there's not much flow of information between the two places, so we don't know much ourselves.

“When it comes to major events taking place in the Black Wind Sea, all we've heard of is the battle between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island. Recently, the battle has gradually risen to the fore, and it's becoming more and more intense."

"Do you know if other more secluded parts of the Black Wind Sea have also gotten swept up in this conflict?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not sure about that, but I've heard from some people who came from the Black Wind Sea that the battle is still limited to only the central region, while the areas outside of that are still relatively peaceful. That's all I know about the situation," Xue Luo replied.

Han Li nodded in response. Given what he had just heard, Dark Veil Island was most likely still untouched.

"By the way, I heard from a fellow daoist who came from the Black Wind Sea about a decade ago mentioned an event that took place there that had apparently caused quite a stir," Qin Zhong suddenly said.

"Oh? What exactly was this event?" Han Li asked with a hint of intrigue in his eyes.

"I'm not sure about the exact details, but apparently, the Castaway Gale around some parts of the Black Wind Sea had suddenly converged inward, destroying several islands in the process," Qin Zhong replied.

"I heard about that as well. The Castaway Gale is a natural barrier that isolates the Black Wind Sea from the rest of the immortal region, and it's already existed for countless years, but never had anything like that happened before that point," Xue Luo chimed in.

"I see. Would either of you be able to provide an answer to my second question?" Han Li asked.

Xue Luo and Qin Zhong exchanged a glance before both of them shook their heads in response. "Many people in Wave View City have actually been trying to find out why the regulations have suddenly become so strict, but no one has been able to get to the bottom of things so far."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly in contemplation as he replied, "I see. In any case, you've managed to answer one of my questions, so you can have one of these Frost Soul Crystals."

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Liu."

Xue Luo picked up one of the crystals before stowing it away, then cast her gaze toward the other crystal as she asked, "Would you be willing to sell this Frost Soul Crystal for two Immortal Origin Stones?"

Han Li didn't refuse this offer, and the three of them remained in the booth for a while longer before departing.

Han Li made a trip to the Xue Clan with the duo, and it was a large trading house situated in the eastern part of Wave View City.

Xue Luo proved to be quite trustworthy, quickly finalizing the vouching proceedings for Han Li.

With that, both sides had gotten what they wanted, and it was a win-win situation.

Han Li tactfully turned down Xue Luo's offer to stay and enjoy the Xue Clan's hospitality, then promptly departed.

"That went quite smoothly," Daoist Xie remarked in Han Li's mind.

"Indeed," Han Li replied as he flipped a hand over to produce a white badge.

One one side of the badge was engraved the image of a strange white bird with a flat head and an eagle beak, while on the other side was inscribed the character for "Xue".

This was the Xue Clan's token, and it had been given to him by Xue Luo.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he inspected the white badge.

"Is there something wrong with the badge?" Daoist Xie asked.

"No, I just feel like the bird engraved on it is rather interesting," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

He had seen this design in the Black Wind Sea before, and if he recalled correctly, it was the symbol of a large island near Dark Veil Island, an island by the name of Snow Kite Island.

According to the records on Dark Veil Island, everyone on the entirety of Snow Kite Island suddenly vanished tens of thousands of years ago, and that was still an unsolved mystery to date.

Han Li was wondering whether the Xue Clan was somehow tied to Snow Kite Island, but he quickly rid himself of that trivial train of thought and stowed the badge away as a hint of concern appeared on his face.

"Are you still concerned about the changes that have taken place in the Black Wind Sea? Didn't you say that the most formidable cultivator there is the master of Black Wind Sea, and he's only a late-True Immortal Stage Earthly Immortal? If that's the case, surely you have nothing to fear," Daoist Xie said.

"That may be true, but for some reason, I can't shake off this feeling of unease," Han Li replied.

"I think you're getting a little paranoid from constantly having to worry about being apprehended by the Heavenly Court," Daoist Xie said.

"Perhaps so," Han Li replied in a self-deprecating manner, but the concern on his face wasn't eased in the slightest.

As they were speaking with one another, Han Li arrived on a street in the eastern part of the city.

It was noon at the moment, and the street was teeming with people, most of whom possessed lofty cultivation bases.

There was no lack of Spatial Tempering and Body Integration cultivators among them, and they were most likely itinerant cultivators who had come here to purchase different things.

Most of the shops that lined the street were material shops, and all of the spirit plants and demon beast materials sold inside were quite fresh, clearly indicating that they had been recently acquired.

Han Li wanted to take his mind off his current concerns, so he began wandering aimlessly through the shops.

Wave View City wasn't very large, and it didn't have many shops, but there was a high degree of diversity in the wares on offer, and he was able to find some things that he needed, thereby improving his mood.

Shortly thereafter, he drew to a halt in front of one of the larger material shops, then cast his gaze into the shop to find that it was selling a large range of products, all of which had been placed on around a dozen shelves.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he made his way inside, and right at this moment, a white-robed young man just so happened to come out of the shop.

The two of them passed each other by, and Han Li stopped in his tracks before turning to look at the white-robed young man's departing figure with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

The white-robed young man was displaying a late-Body Integration Stage cultivation, but Han Li was immediately able to identify him as an early-True Immortal cultivator.

The aura concealment method that he was using was quite advanced, and Han Li may not have been able to see through his cover had it not been for his immense spiritual sense.

The white-robed young man didn't notice Han Li's gaze, and he quickly vanished into the crowd, while Han Li withdrew his gaze and stepped into the shop.

It was a very normal occurrence for cultivators to conceal their cultivation base. After all, he was doing the exact same thing.

As soon as Han Li entered the shop, he was immediately greeted by the hospitable shopkeeper. "What can I help you with today?"

……

Close to a day later, Han Li had already visited all of the shops in the city, and he had found several good materials, as well as two types of rare spirit plant seeds.

Perhaps it was because this was a newly constructed city in a rather secluded location, but there was no Immortal Outlet here, and that put Han Li slightly more at ease.

At this moment, he was standing in the central area of the city, not far away from the white pagoda.

Under the night sky, the pagoda was giving off a faint white glow that matched the luster of the moon, presenting a marvelous spectacle to behold.

At this moment, the gates of the pagoda were tightly shut, making it impossible for anyone to see inside.

Han Li didn't use his spiritual sense to forcibly inspect the interior of the pagoda, and after staying there for a while longer, he turned to depart, renting a room in a secluded inn to the west of the city before going into seclusion.

Chapter 349: Perplexing

Han Li stayed in the secret chamber in the inn for close to two years.

During this time, he occasionally came out of seclusion a few times in disguise, but only to visit all of the shops in the city, keeping an eye on any news about the Immortal Palace while also checking to see if there were any spirit materials worth buying.

Perhaps it was because the Black Wind Sea was truly too secluded, but even up to this point, the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace still hadn't sent anyone to Wave View City. However, news of what had happened in the Blaze Dragon Dao had still managed to travel here, and it had become the most shocking piece of news in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region in recent years.

Han Li naturally paid some extra attention to this news, and he was quite relieved to hear that Daoist Hu Yan hadn't fallen into the hands of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace. However, at the same time, he was a little perplexed about why Daoist Hu Yan wasn't also a wanted fugitive in the Immortal Outlets.

Aside from that, Baili Yan appeared to have still been alive as well.

Han Li didn't have any ties to him, but he was still happy to see that Baili Yan hadn't met his demise. After all, he was currently wanted by the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, so it definitely wasn't a bad thing that Baili Yan was diverting their attention away from him.

One day, at the center of Wave View City.

A burst of dazzling light erupted out of the five-story white pagoda, and a pillar of blue light rose up from its rooftop straight into the heavens.

At this moment, many of the cultivators in the city were gathered around the pagoda, watching the cultivators entering the pagoda with undisguised envy on their faces.

All those who were entering the pagoda had naturally obtained teleportation spots, and it had been said that many cultivators had reaped benefits from the Black Wind Sea of late. This was the primary reason why Wave View City was already so prosperous despite being such a new city.

In the crowd was a fair-skinned scholar holding a folding fan, and he was staring at the white pagoda in an expressionless manner, making it unclear what he was thinking.

All of a sudden, he emerged from the crowd and stowed his folding fan away as he strode toward the pagoda.

This person was none other than Han Li in disguise.

After entering the pagoda, he passed through a short corridor to arrive in a spacious hall that was over 1,000 feet in size, and on either side of the hall's entrance stood a cultivator wearing Black Wind Island robes.

"Please display your teleportation badge and vouching token," the black-robed cultivator on the left said to Han Li in a calm manner.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce the two requested objects before handing them over.

The black-robed cultivator summoned a white jade tablet, which released a burst of white light that enveloped the two objects, following which a pair of fist-sized golden runes appeared on the tablet before vanishing in a flash.

"Right this way, Fellow Daoist," the black-robed cultivator on the right said as he gestured toward the entrance of the hall.

Han Li gave a slight nod in response, then made his way inside.

The hall was rectangular in shape, and the floor was paved with pristine white jade bricks. There were countless runes engraved upon the surrounding walls, and they were giving off a white glow that illuminated the entire hall.

Aside from several Black Wind Island cultivators, there were already around two dozen cultivators dressed in different attire waiting inside the hall.

The teleportation array was situated at the very back of the hall, and even though it hadn't been activated yet, it was already giving off bursts of faint spatial fluctuations.

Han Li's arrival didn't attract much attention, drawing only a few glances from some of the cultivators, while everyone else paid no heed to him.

He casually swept his gaze across the hall while making his way over to an empty corner of the hall, where he sat down with his legs crossed.

His expression remained unchanged, but he was actually rather intrigued to notice that the white-robed cultivator who had been concealing his own cultivation base that he had encountered upon first entering Wave View City was standing no more than 200 feet away from him.

This wouldn't have been worthy of note on its own. After all, it wasn't a strange occurrence for a True Immortal to travel to the Black Wind Sea.

What had truly caught Han Li's attention was that there were five or six cultivators around the white-robed young man, all of whom were also True Immortals that were only revealing Body Integration Stage cultivation bases. In particular, one of them, a middle-aged man with a square face and thin eyebrows, was at the late-True Immortal Stage, ranking alongside Han Li as the two most formidable cultivators present.

It was rather noteworthy that such a formidable force was collectively traveling to the Black Wind Sea, but as long as they didn't get in his way, Han Li certainly wasn't going to meddle in their business.

Time slowly passed by, and around a dozen more cultivators had arrived in the next two hours.

Right at this moment, a black-robed elderly man emerged as he declared, "Sorry to keep you all waiting, everyone, it's almost time for the teleportation array to be activated."

The declaration immediately caused a stir among the crowd, and all of the cultivators who were meditating had opened their eyes and risen to their feet.

Han Li rose to his feet alongside everyone else, and he discovered that he had met this black-robed elderly man once before; it was the itinerant immortal referred to as Elder Yi. [1]

"I'm sure you're all aware that things are a bit different nowadays than they were before, so prior to entering the Black Wind Sea, I'll have to get all of you to pass through this sensory array," the black-robed elderly man said as he raised a hand and made a hand seal.

Several of the jade bricks on the floor between the elderly man and everyone else abruptly lit up with golden light, following which a series of golden runes flew out from within, quickly intertwining in mid-air to form a ring of golden light that was around 10 feet in size.

Inside the golden ring, balls of golden light of different sizes were whizzing incessantly through the air.

A hint of blue light flashed through Han Li's eyes, and he discovered that every single one of these balls of light was formed by countless golden seal text runes. His expression remained unchanged, but his heart sank slightly upon seeing this.

Most of the cultivators present seemed to have already been aware that this was going to happen, and aside from a few who displayed surprised reactions, the rest began to pass through the ring of light one after another.

Whenever someone passed through the rings of light, the balls of golden light around it would shudder slightly and display some minute changes.

Meanwhile, Elder Yi's gaze remained fixed firmly on the ring of light this entire time, seemingly observing something.

Before long, around a dozen people had already passed through the ring of life and entered the teleportation array. Even the white-robed cultivator that Han Li had noticed earlier had already passed through the ring of light, and up to this point, no abnormalities had been displayed.

Instead of immediately approaching the ring of light, Han Li made his way over to a purple-haired Body Integration Stage young woman beside him as he said, "Greetings, Fellow Daoist, I am Luo Feng of Dark Veil Island. I had to leave the Black Wind Sea due to clan matters several hundred years ago, and at the time, this procedure hadn't been implemented. Could it be that something's recently happened in the Black Wind Sea?"

Judging from her attire, she seemed to have been a cultivator from Cedar Gift Island, which Han Li recalled was affiliated with Black Wind Island.

The purple-haired woman was just about to make her way toward the ring of light when she stopped in her tracks, then turned to Han Li as she explained, "If you've been away for several centuries, then it's no surprise that you don't know about this. This is a new rule established by Island Master Lu a century ago, and I don't know the exact reasons why, but it seems to have something to do with a certain evil cultivator."

"I see. Thank you for enlightening me, Fellow Daoist," Han Li replied with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute.

The purple-haired young woman waved a casual hand before making her way forward.

Meanwhile, Han Li's mind was racing as he cast his gaze toward the ring of golden light once again.

His first thought upon hearing mention of an evil cultivator was that it had to have been himself. After all, he had killed Tao Yu, who was clearly a very important figure, and it would've only made sense for him to have been deemed an evil cultivator by the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace.

However, he then quickly decided that this most likely wasn't the case.

Not only had he not heard of any ties between Black Wind Island and the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace prior to this, the fact that this restriction had already been set up for a century indicated that it clearly had nothing to do with him. After all, back then, he was still in the Blaze Dragon Dao and hadn't done anything out of line.

Aside from that, the white-robed cultivator hadn't triggered any reaction from the restriction, so it seemed that this restriction didn't pay any heed to one's true cultivation base.

As these thoughts were flashing through Han Li's mind, more cultivators continued to pass through the golden array. At this point, there was barely anyone left around him, and the other True Immortals that had concealed their true cultivation bases had also stepped into the teleportation array.

Thus, he took a deep breath before stepping into the ring of golden light.

The surrounding balls of golden light shuddered in unison, following which a burst of gentle force instantly enveloped his entire body, flowing over him like trickling water.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he continued.

One step!

Two steps!

Three steps!

All the while, Elder Yi continued to scrutinize the golden array with his hands clasped behind his back.

The ring of golden light didn't encompass a very large area, and Han Li was able to pass through it in just a few steps without any mishaps, much to his relief.

Shortly thereafter, the remaining few cultivators also passed through the sensory restriction without any incident.

Only then did Elder Yi give a slight nod before sweeping a sleeve through the air to wave away the restriction. At the same time, streaks of blue light shot out of his other sleeve before landing upon Han Li and the others, revealing a series of blue talismans.

In the next instant, the teleportation array lit up with dazzling radiance, and Han Li's entire field of view was completely filled with white light.

A long while later, the scene around him stabilized once again, and he found himself situated within a circular hall.

This was the interior of Black Wind Island's Heavenly Star Pagoda, so Han Li had some recollection of this place.

A hunch-backed elderly woman wearing a black robe was standing in front of the array, and she smiled as she declared, "Welcome to the Black Wind Sea, fellow daoists!"

Everyone cupped their fists in a collective salute toward the elderly woman before stepping out of the array and making their way toward a nearby archway.

Han Li was walking slowly among the crowd, and all of a sudden, he slowed down slightly, seemingly having noticed something.

Just now, he had noticed out of the corner of his eye that the white-robed cultivator wasn't following the crowd. Instead, he had stopped in the hall after stepping out of the teleportation array, and the same applied to all of the other concealed True Immortals as well.

The hunch-backed elderly woman didn't raise any objections to this, and Han Li became even more curious about who these people were.

[1]. This guy showed up once back in Chapter 156: The Perilous Path of Cultivation, he's not an important character, so don't worry if you don't remember him.

[Back]

Chapter 350: Lockdown

After leaving the Heavenly Star Pagoda, Han Li made his way along the white stone plaza toward a nearby street, just like everyone else, and it wasn't long before he entered the city.

Black Wind City was the most prosperous city in the entire Black Wind Sea, and this was the most prosperous area in the entire city.

The city remained largely unchanged since Han Li's last visit, except several extremely opulent shops had opened up on the most lively and bustling crossroads in the area. Business was booming for these shops, and countless cultivators were constantly entering and exiting the establishments.

Han Li maintained a casual façade as he made his way onto a nearby street, one that was lined with materials shops, and he turned back to take a glance at the Heavenly Star Pagoda before stepping into one of the shops.

The shop wasn't very large, and there weren't many customers inside.

Han Li was immediately greeted by an enthusiastic employee, who asked, "What can I help you with today?"

Han Li began to engage in a casual conversation with the employee, but his peripheral vision was still focused on the Heavenly Star Pagoda.

An entire hour passed by, and nothing happened on the plaza outside the pagoda.

All of a sudden, a group of cultivators appeared on an obscure corner of the plaza, and they were none other than the hunch-backed elderly woman and the group of concealed True Immortals, with the late-True Immortal Stage middle-aged man bringing up the rear.

As soon as the group appeared on the plaza, they immediately rose up into the air and flew away in a certain direction, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's suspicions were confirmed upon seeing this.

If he recalled correctly, that direction was where the island master's manor was situated.

After purchasing a few materials to keep up appearances, Han Li left the shop, then cast his gaze toward the direction that the group had flown away in with a slightly hesitant look in his eyes.

However, he then shook his head and departed in another direction.

Regardless of how these people were related to the master of Black Wind Island or what their intentions were, they most likely had nothing to do with him, so it was best for him to avoid attracting unnecessary trouble.

With that in mind, Han Li passed through several more streets, and as he emerged from a secluded alley, he had adopted another disguise, transforming into a yellow-skinned man.

With the Transient Guild mask, adopting disguises was very easy, so he took on a new appearance in virtually every single place that he passed through.

After that, he began to explore Black Wind City while replenishing some supplies.

Perhaps it was because the Black Wind Sea's ties with the outside world had been strengthened, but the city really had become a lot more prosperous than before, and various types of materials and pills that had been quite rare in the past could now be found in all of the shops.

Close to half a day later, Han Li rose up into the air as a streak of azure light before flying away into the distance.

Shortly thereafter, he descended onto the plaza in front of the island master's manor.

At a rough glance, this place hadn't changed much, either, except the manor was currently enshrouded under layers of light barriers of different colors, and there were also some cultivators patrolling nearby, indicating that security had become a lot tighter than before.

Han Li didn't linger for very long here before making his way toward the Talisman Letter Palace where missions were released.

There were many more cultivators gathered in the palace than during his last visit, and the number of missions on the stone wall inside had also increased significantly.

Furthermore, the contents of the missions had also changed drastically, and there were many more missions

There were even missions that offered rewards for killing certain Azure Feather Island cultivators, each one with its own corresponding reward.

Han Li quickly read through all of the missions on the stone wall, but he was unable to find any related to himself or even the Blaze Dragon Dao.

However, he still wasn't completely reassured.

He strolled around the hall for a while to strike up some conversations with other cultivators who were also looking at missions, and only after confirming that there were no signs of the Immortal Palace coming after him here was he finally able to heave an internal sigh of relief.

However, prior to leaving, he took on a mission to acquire a certain demon beast material in order to avoid suspicion.

After leaving the Talisman Letter Palace, Han Li took another glance at the island master's manor before flying toward the city gate as a streak of azure light.

However, halfway to the city gate, a burst of dull rumbling suddenly rang out from all over the island, accompanied by the sound of splashing waves.

Han Li hurriedly stopped in his tracks, then looked around to find that pillars of blue light had erupted into the heavens around Black Wind City, forming a fence-like structure around the entire city.

Formidable energy fluctuations were emanating from the pillars of light, causing the surrounding space to tremble and quiver.

Waves of watery light then began to surge out of the pillars of blue light, causing them to bend and converge toward the center, quickly fusing together to become interconnected.

Before long, a thick blue light barrier had taken shape, encompassing the entire city within it.

Countless ripples were surging over the light barrier, and it was clear that this was a very intricate array.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he continued onward, quickly reaching the city gate.

There were many people gathered at the city gate, causing quite a commotion.

Han Li descended discreetly by the edge of the crowd, then made his way into the throngs of people.

At this moment, the group of cultivators at the front of the line were communicating to a black-robed city guard.

"What's going on? Why has the protective array suddenly been activated?"

"We urgently need to leave the city, would you be able to make an exception and let us through?"

"Island Master Lu has ordered for the protective array to be activated as we've just received news that some cultivators from Azure Feather Island intend to attack Black Wind City. This is just a safety precaution, and as soon as the threat is alleviated, we'll immediately deactivate the array," the leader of the guards declared to everyone as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this.

He had already heard that the conflict between Black Wind City and Azure Feather Island was worsening by the day, but he didn't think that things were already this severe.

Judging from everyone's reactions, it seemed that they weren't overly surprised by this explanation.

Han Li pondered the situation momentarily, then turned to a red-robed elderly man beside him as he asked, "Fellow Daoist, could it be that the city's protective array is activated quite often?"

The red-robed elderly raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and he asked, "Are you not from the Black Wind Sea?"

"I only just arrived on Black Wind Island through the teleportation array, so I'm not very familiar with the state of affairs here," Han Li replied in a polite manner.

"I see. The conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island has been getting more and more intense. Black Wind City is the stronghold of Black Wind Island, but it's still not all that safe, and the city's protective array has already been activated many times in recent years," the red-robed elderly man explained.

"Which side has the upper hand in the conflict?" Han Li asked.

"Overall, Black Wind Island is more powerful than Azure Feather Island, but recently, Azure Feather Island has managed to recruit many islands as allies, so they're now able to stand toe to toe against Black Wind Island. I wonder when this war is going to come to an end," the red-robed elderly man sighed.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Right as the crowd was abuzz with conversation, a Grand Ascension Stage middle-aged man emerged from the crowd, then asked, "May I ask when the array will be deactivated? You can't just expect all of us to wait indefinitely."

"I'm afraid I can't give you a precise answer. Perhaps it'll only be two or three days, perhaps it could be up to 10 days or half a month. If you need to leave the city for some urgent reason, you can go the island master's manor to request an audience with Island Master Lu. If you can acquire an exit token from Island Master Lu, then you'll be free to go," the leader of the guards replied.

The man's brows furrowed tightly upon hearing this, but he didn't say anything further.

Many others were also reluctant to accept this arrangement, but they clearly didn't dare to oppose the authority of the island master's manor. As for applying for an exit token, none of them actually had to leave the city that urgently, so after some more discussion, all of the cultivators gathered at the city gate quickly dispersed.

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed as he heaved an internal sigh.

It seemed that his luck was rather bad. If he had set off just a little earlier, perhaps he would've already been out of the city by now.

He took a glance up at the blue light barrier in the sky, then bade farewell to the red-robed elderly man before returning the same way that he had come.

The activation of the protective array had caused a stir in the city, but it quickly subsided. After all, this was a fairly regular occurrence, so everyone quickly continued with what they were doing.

Before long, Han Li arrived in an inn in a secluded part of the city, where he rented a room.

Night soon arrived, and inside the secret chamber, Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open as he rose to his feet, then swept a sleeve through the air to release around a dozen streaks of azure light that descended all around the room to form a restriction.

Immediately thereafter, he made a hand seal, and arcs of golden lightning appeared over his body before quickly spreading outward to form a golden lightning array.

The lightning array then flashed with golden light, and he abruptly vanished from the spot.

The remaining traces of golden lightning lingered momentarily in the room before completely fading away.

Meanwhile, in a secret chamber deep beneath the island master's manor.

It was quite a dimly lit room that was surrounded by rippling black light.

At the center of the secret chamber was a large blue jade platform, above which were hovering a series of blue array flags, of which there were at least 10,000.

Dazzling blue light was radiating from these array flags, forming a hemispherical blue light barrier that enshrouded the blue jade platform down below.

Engraved onto the platform was an image of a city, and upon close inspection, one would quickly be able to tell that it was none other than Black Wind City.

Chapter 351: Encountering a Conflict

At this moment, a black-robed elderly man was seated with his legs crossed beside the blue jade platform with dozens of blue jade plates hovering around him.

All of a sudden, one of the jade plates shuddered as a bright gleam flashed over its surface, and the elderly man immediately opened his eyes and cast his gaze toward that jade plate.

"What's wrong, Elder Chu?"

A voice rang out as a black-robed figure emerged out of the darkness, and it was none other than the master of Black Wind Island, Lu Jun.

There hadn't been much change to his physical appearance, and he still appeared as authoritative as ever.

"Someone has just passed through the city's protective array," the black-robed elderly man replied with furrowed brows.

"Passed through? As in someone managed to unravel the array?" Lu Jun asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"No, they've simply passed through it using some type of special movement technique," the black-robed elderly man explained.

"How did they do that?" Lu Jun asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"They must've used some type of spatial secret technique. The city's protective array can't be bypassed through normal movement techniques, but it has no spatial restrictions, so it's not completely foolproof."

Another voice rang out as a third figure emerged from the darkness, and it was none other than the late-True Immortal Stage middle-aged man that Han Li had seen earlier.

The authoritative look on Lu Jun's face was instantly replaced with a respectful expression at the sight of the middle-aged man, and he said, "I've never encountered such a situation before. Perhaps it's because the Black Wind Sea is too secluded and my knowledge is lacking."

"This type of secret technique isn't all that common on the outside, either, so I also wasn't expecting to see one here," the middle-aged man replied.

"Could it be someone from Azure Feather Island?" the black-robed elderly man asked.

"Most likely not. I've had numerous battles with Daoist Master Azure Feather in the past, and even he doesn't possess such an ability. Otherwise, things wouldn't have been so peaceful all this time. I'm presuming it's one of the cultivators who were teleported into the city earlier today," Lu Jun mused.

"We can only hope that this person doesn't have anything to do with Azure Feather Island," the black-robed elderly man said.

"In any case, they're definitely not one of our people, and it's certainly not a good thing that there exists someone who can pass through our city's protective restrictions as they please," Lu Jun said with slightly furrowed brows.

"There's no need to be overly concerned, Island Master Lu. I just so happen to have a restriction here that contains spatial power, and Fellow Daoist Chu can simply add it to the city's protective array," the middle-aged man said as he flipped a hand over to produce a stack of shimmering silver array tools, which he handed to the black-robed elderly man.

The black-robed elderly man's eyes lit up as he felt the faint spatial power fluctuations emanating from the array tools, and he hurriedly accepted them before giving them a close inspection.

Lu Jun was also quite elated to see this, and he cupped his fist in a grateful salute as he said, "You have our thanks, Fellow Daoist Feng."

"Don't worry about it. How are you going with the task that I assigned you?" the middle-aged man asked, abruptly changing the subject.

"After receiving your instructions, I immediately sent people to reinforce the defenses, and we'll be sure to keep out all of the Azure Feather Island cultivators," Lu Jun replied in a serious voice.

"The cultivators of Azure Feather Island aren't worthy of concern, the key is the Reincarnation Palace. If Azure Feather Island is being supported in secret by the Reincarnation Palace, then things will be very troublesome, so we can't afford to grow complacent," the middle-aged man said with a serious expression.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Feng," Lu Jun replied with a nod.

The middle-aged man also nodded in response before departing, and even though he was speaking in a rather haughty manner, neither Lu Jun nor the black-robed elderly man displayed any displeasure, as if this were a normal occurrence.

"I can take care of everything on my own here, Island Master. You should go back to rest," the black-robed elderly man said.

Lu Jun shook his head in response as he cast a concerned gaze toward the blue jade platform.

"Are you still worried about Young Mistress Yuqing?" the black-robed elderly man asked.

"I can't help but be concerned for her," Lu Jun sighed.

"Young Mistress Yuqing is only trying to share your burden. Besides, Waveflow Island isn't far away from Black Wind Island, and she's made significant strides in her cultivation base of late, so she'll definitely be fine," the black-robed elderly man reassured with a smile.

Lu Jun seemed to have been slightly reassured upon hearing this.

……

Close to 100,000 kilometers away from Black Wind Island, arcs of golden lightning suddenly erupted out of thin air, forming a golden lightning array above the sea.

Han Li appeared at the center of the array, and his expression eased slightly as he inhaled the slightly damp and salty sea breeze blowing toward him.

After taking a moment to gather his bearings, he flipped a hand over to produce the jade slip that contained the map of the Black Wind Sea that he had previously purchased, then pressed it against his own forehead.

Moments later, he stowed the jade slip away, then flew away into the distance.

According to what he had learned thus far, the area around Black Wind Island wasn't all that peaceful at the moment. Given his current cultivation base, he naturally had nothing to worry about, but he was still going to keep as low a profile as possible, and he was flying carefully at a low speed while taking care to conceal himself.

The night passed by quickly, and as the sun began to rise in the east, it was as if countless shimmering golden scales had appeared on the surface of the sea, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

The Black Wind Sea was the first place Han Li had settled at upon his return to the Immortal Realm, so he harbored some special emotions for this place. This was like his hometown in the Immortal Realm, and that made him particularly partial to the scenery here.

However, right at this moment, he suddenly cast his gaze toward a certain direction with a hint of surprise in his eyes, then immediately stopped in his tracks.

He had just detected some violent spiritual qi fluctuations several thousand kilometers away in that direction, and it seemed that a fierce battle was taking place.

After a brief hesitation, he began to fly in that direction, but as he did so, his body slowly became transparent, and the azure light that he was giving off also faded, turning him into an invisible shadow.

At this current speed, he was able to cover several thousand kilometers to arrive at the scene of the battle in mere moments, and he concealed himself within a cloud in the sky before casting his gaze downward.

Enormous waves were rising up into the heavens alongside streaks of spiritual light of different colors, and resounding booms were also ringing out incessantly.

Out of the two opposing groups of cultivators, one of them consisted of five Black Wind Island cultivators, two of whom were at the Grand Ascension Stage, while the other three were at the Body Integration Stage.

One of the Grand Ascension cultivators was a young woman who appeared to have been in her twenties, and she was wielding an azure feather fan, which conjured up gusts of fierce azure wind with each sweep.

The other Grand Ascension cultivator was a thin yellow-aged man with a rather yellow complexion, and there was a blue mirror hovering above his head that was occasionally shooting forth thick pillars of blue light.

As for the three Body Integration cultivators, they were gathered around the young woman while controlling their own treasures, seemingly intentionally protecting her.

They were facing a pair of Azure Feather Island cultivators, and even though the Black Wind Island cultivators had the numbers advantage, they were in a terrible situation as one of the two Azure Feather Island cultivators, a bald man with a fleshy growth on his head, was at the True Immortal Stage.

At this moment, there was a large black flag hovering in front of the bald man, and the image of the black deity on the flag bore a close resemblance to the lightning god of legends.

As he made a string of hand seals, bolts of black lightning erupted out of the black flag in all directions to form a sea of black lightning.

Thick bolts of lightning shot out of the sea of lightning, vanquishing the attacks from the Black Wind Island cultivators with ease while also forcing them back into constant retreat.

Beside him was an elderly man with a goatee, and he was giving off a Grand Ascension Stage aura.

The elderly man was wielding a pair of yellow spear treasures, which had transformed into a pair of earthy yellow dragons that were blasting millstone-sized balls of yellow light out of their mouths to assist the bald man.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes at the sight of the young man as it was none other than the daughter of Island Master Lu Jun, Lu Yuqing.

"I didn't think you would dare to leave Black Wind Island when you're the sole heir to the island. I wonder if I should call you brave or foolish," the bald man chuckled coldly as he made a hand seal, and thick bolts of lightning erupted out of the sea of lightning, then rapidly intertwined to form five giant lightning serpents that pounced at the five Black Wind Island cultivators.

A grim look appeared on Lu Yuqing's face upon seeing this, and she swept her feather fan through the air, unleashing a gust of ferocious azure wind that enveloped the five huge lightning serpents at once.

Countless threads of azure light could be seen within the gust of wind, and the giant lightning serpents were slowed down significantly.

Meanwhile, the middle-aged man beside her made a rapid string of hand seals, and the blue mirror in front of him abruptly swelled to several hundred feet in size.

An incredibly thick pillar of blue light then shot out of the mirror to encompass the five lightning serpents while releasing vast glacial qi, immediately following which the pillar of light transformed into a massive blue ice mountain, freezing the five lightning serpents inside.

"Go, Young Mistress Yuqing! We'll hold off these two!" the man yelled while making a string of hand seals, sending thick pillars of blue light erupting out of his mirror toward the pair of opposing cultivators.

The other three Body Integration cultivators also braced themselves to make a final stand as they began bombarding the two Azure Feather Island cultivators with attacks.

A conflicted look appeared in Lu Yuqing's eyes, but she then gritted her teeth and fled toward the distance as a streak of azure light.

"You're not getting away!" the bald man declared with a cold smile as he switched to a different hand seal, and the five lightning serpents exploded violently into thick arcs of lightning that tore the blue ice mountain apart with ease.

Immediately thereafter, the arcs of lightning intertwined to form a huge lightning net that swept toward the group of Black Wind Island cultivators at an incredible speed, and it instantly fell upon the middle-aged man and the others, quickly charring their entire bodies black.

Meanwhile, the elderly man with the goatee sped away as a streak of yellow light in pursuit of Lu Yuqing.

Chapter 352: Identity Exposed

The other four Black Wind Island cultivators were struggling with all their might under the lightning net, but they were like insects trapped in a cobweb, unable to break free no matter how hard they tried.

A sinister grin appeared on the bald man's face as he pointed a finger forward, and four thick bolts pillars of lightning instantly erupted out of the black flag above his head before striking the four cultivators in a flash.

The protective treasures around the three Body Integration cultivators were torn apart without being able to put up any resistance, and their bodies were reduced to ashes before they even had a chance to cry out.

The middle-aged man possessed a far superior cultivation base to those three, but a pillar of lightning was still able to pierce straight through him, splitting his body into two with explosive force.

However, he was able to take advantage of this opportunity to struggle free from the lightning net, and a vast expanse of crimson light emerged to envelop the two halves of his body before speeding away in a certain direction as a ball of crimson light.

The bald man immediately switched to a different hand seal upon seeing this, and black lightning flashed over the surface of his black flag, following which it swelled drastically in size before flying away in pursuit of the ball of crimson light, intercepting it in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, the black flag wrapped itself around the ball of crimson light before releasing a vast expanse of black lightning, and an agonized howl rang out as the ball of crimson light was incinerated into ashes.

All of this had taken place in the span of just a few seconds, and the bald man made a beckoning motion, following which the black flag quickly flew back to his side, reverting back to its original size as it did so.

At the same time, he cast his gaze toward the direction that Lu Yuqing had fled in.

Lu Yuqing hadn't been able to get very far in such a short time, but the elderly man was still unable to catch up to her.

The bald man immediately sped off in that direction as an arc of black lightning, and as a Grand Ascension cultivator, there was naturally no way that Lu Yuqing could outrun a True Immoratl, so the arc of black lightning was quickly able to catch up to her.

"Did you really think you could get away from me? What a joke!"

A cold voice rang out within the black lightning, immediately following which a massive black hand that was around an acre in size and formed entirely from lightning emerged out of thin air before grabbing toward Lu Yuqing.

Even before the giant hand had fully descended upon her, she was already struck by an enormous burst of pressure that swept up gusts of fierce wind, causing her to lose control in her flight and swirl around in the air like a helpless leaf.

A panicked look appeared on her face, and the feather fan in her hand lit up as it swelled to around twice its original size, following which she swept it upward with all her might.

A thick pillar of azure wind shot forth, and it was giving off an astonishing howling sound alongside faint spatial fluctuations, allowing it to keep the giant lightning palm at bay.

"That's... a Profound Heavenly Treasure!"

The bald man reappeared in mid-air with a surprised look on his face, following which he gave a cold harrumph as he thrust his palm forward once again.

The giant black lightning palm instantly swelled further by about twofold in size, and countless black lightning runes emerged around it as it also began to emanate bursts of law power fluctuations.

The pillar of azure wind was instantly crushed, while the giant lightning palm continued to descend, and all of the air beneath it seemed to have congealed.

Lu Yuqing felt the surrounding space constrict around her, rendering her completely unable to move, and a hint of despair appeared in her eyes.

Right as the giant palm was about to descend upon her, a burst of spatial fluctuations suddenly erupted beside it, immediately following which an azure shadow flashed past in a wraith-like fashion.

The giant lightning palm was instantly stopped cold in its tracks without any warning, then exploded violently into countless arcs of lightning that quickly dissipated.

As a result, Lu Yuqing was freed, and she was both stunned and elated as she immediately flew through the air, covering a distance of tens of thousands of feet in a flash.

However, instead of fleeing the scene, she began to inspect her surroundings with wide eyes.

"Who's there?" the bald man roared in a furious voice as he also began scouring the surrounding area.

Meanwhile, an alarmed look appeared on the elderly man's face, and he hurriedly flew back to the bald man's side before releasing his spiritual sense to sweep through the air, yet neither of them were able to detect anything.

"You have to be a True Immortal to have dispelled my attack so easily, so why are you sneaking around like a cowardly rat?" the bald man goaded in a mocking voice.

"I have no intention of getting involved in the conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island. It's just that I have some ties with this woman, so it would be much appreciated if you could let her go."

An indifferent voice reverberated through the air in response, but neither the bald man nor his companion were to ascertain where it was coming from.

"You want me to let her go? Why don't you make me?"

The bald man abruptly turned around and cast his gaze toward what appeared to have been nothing but empty air, following which an incredibly thick pillar of lightning erupted out of his black flag to strike the precise spot that he was looking at.

A vast expanse of dazzling lightning exploded with an earth-shattering boom, causing that stretch of space to shudder violently.

The lightning quickly dissipated, but there was still no one there.

An astonished look appeared on the bald man's face upon seeing this, and right at this moment, a faint sigh rang out beside his ears, followed by an authoritative declaration.

"Let there be wind!"

As soon as the voice trailed off, the bald man's surroundings instantly changed drastically, and he was suddenly transported from the sea to a vast yellow desert.

Gusts of fierce wind were howling around him, and the desert stretched as far as the eyes could see with countless tornadoes raging on the horizon.

The bald man was astonished to see this, but he then immediately realized the situation that he was in.

"This is an illusion!"

Right at this moment, a streak of azure light pierced through his dantian. It was an azure flying sword, and there was a nascent soul pinned through its tip.

The bald man looked down with wide and incredulous eyes at the sight of the flying sword protruding out of his lower abdomen, and in the next instant, the azure flying sword destroyed the nascent soul before vanishing in a flash.

The surrounding desert faded away, and the sea was revealed again.

At this point, the bald man's body was completely limp and lifeless, and a large hole had been pierced through his lower abdomen as he plunged down toward the sea like a dead weight.

Right at this moment, a streak of silver fire suddenly emerged to strike the body, immediately setting it alight and incinerating it into ashes.

The elderly man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he frantically looked around with a horrified expression.

Whoever the concealed enemy was, they were able to slay a True Immortal cultivator in an instant, so he was naturally no match for them.

With that in mind, the elderly man began to tremble with fear as he fell to his knees and implored, "Please spare me, Senior..."

However, right at this moment, a streak of azure swordlight flew out of thin air, then flew in a circle around the elderly man's body at an incredible speed.

The elderly man's expression instantly stiffened, immediately following which several gashes appeared all over his body, splitting it into pieces.

At the same time, his nascent soul had also been destroyed, and the chunks of his body plummeted into the sea down below.

The streak of azure swordlight vanished once again, and peace and quiet was restored.

Lu Yuqing was relatively calm in the wake of this turn of events, and after returning to her senses, she immediately extended a curtsey as she said, "Lu Yuqing of Black Wind Island sincerely thanks you for saving her life, Senior. Would you be able to show yourself?"

Concealed within the cloud in the sky, Han Li made a beckoning motion to recover an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, which was carrying a pair of storage tools and a small black flag.

He flipped a hand over to stow these items away, then prepared to leave, displaying no intention of revealing himself.

All of a sudden, Lu Yuqing's ecstatic voice rang out. "Brother Liu!"

Han Li was quite alarmed to hear this, and he immediately stopped cold in his tracks before turning back to look at Lu Yuqing.

At this moment, there was a layer of rippling black light within her eyes, and she was looking directly at him.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. Under the scrutiny of her strange eyes, it felt as if he were entirely laid bare to her.

If she had been a cultivator of the same caliber as him, then he wouldn't have been overly surprised, but it was very remarkable that a Grand Ascension cultivator like her possessed such an uncanny ocular ability.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li decided to reveal himself, descending not far away in front of Lu Yuqing.

Lu Yuqing faltered slightly at the sight of him, and Han Li was rather puzzled by her reaction, but didn't say anything.

A slightly sulky look appeared on her face as she said, "You didn't look like this back when we last met. Are you in disguise now or were you in disguise back then? Or perhaps you've never revealed your appearance to me?"

"If you're unable to see through my disguise, then how did you recognize me?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Lu Yuqing hesitated momentarily, then smiled as she replied, "I was born with a pair of Illusory Ghost Eyes that can see straight through the souls of others, thereby allowing me to identify them."

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, he was quite surprised that such an innate ocular ability existed.

Transient Guild masks could only alter one's appearance and aura, but not one's soul, so it was no wonder that she was able to identify him, and that left Han Li with a rather difficult predicament.

He had saved Lu Yuqing as they were acquaintances, and he had thought that he could simply save her and leave without being detected or recognized, but his plans had been foiled.

However, he couldn't just kill her in order to silence her. He simply wasn't such a cold and callous individual that he could do such a cold-blooded thing to an innocent woman.

Chapter 353: Returning to Dark Veil Island

Lu Yuqing seemed to have identified Han Li's concerns, and she promised in a solemn voice, "Rest assured, Brother Liu, I won't tell anyone about this, including my father."

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response. "You have my thanks. I'm just an itinerant cultivator, and I really don't want to get involved in the conflict between your Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island."

"I should be the one thanking you, Brother Liu! You just saved my life!" Lu Yuqing chuckled.

Han Li merely responded with a faint smile.

After considering the situation, he had realized that it wasn't much of a problem even if his identity were exposed.

All Lu Yuqing knew was that he was an itinerant cultivator by the name of Liu Shi, and he had altered his appearance back when he first arrived on Black Wind Island, so there was very little chance that they would be able to make the connection that he was Liu Shi of Dark Veil Island. After all, there were countless cultivators in the Black Wind Sea, and it wouldn't have been uncommon to see people with the same name.

With that in mind, he felt even more reassured.

"Having said that, the conflict between our Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island will most likely only increase in scope, and it's only a matter of time before the entire Black Wind Sea is swept up in the conflict, so it won't be easy to remain uninvolved. You've saved my life twice, and I'm extremely grateful to you.

“My father also has a very high opinion of you, so if you're willing to come to our Black Wind Island, you'll definitely be given very favorable treatment. Our Black Wind Island has always been very kind to its elders," Lu Yuqing said.

Han Li merely smiled in response, silently turning down her offer.

A hint of disappointment flashed through Lu Yuqing's eyes upon seeing this, but she then pulled out a black badge before offering it to Han Li.

"I can see that you've already made up your mind, so I won't try to persuade you any further. This is my personal badge. If you ever need to go to Black Wind Island for whatever reason, you'll be able to come and go as you please with this badge."

Han Li accepted the badge, then took a brief glance at it before stowing it away.

"I still have some matters to attend to, so I'll be taking my leave. I suggest you return to Black Wind Island as quickly as possible, Fellow Daoist Lu. This is not a safe place," Han Li said, then sped away as a streak of azure light, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Lu Yuqing looked on at his departing figure with a slightly forlorn expression, then quickly flew back toward Black Wind Island as well.

After flying for some time, Han Li suddenly changed directions in his flight, and around half a day later, he had finally left the area in which the conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island was taking place.

From there, Han Li immediately accelerated, hurtling through the air like a bolt of azure lightning.

After flying for about half a month, he had reached a very secluded area in the Black Wind Sea, and there were barely any islands to be seen.

All of a sudden, he stopped in his tracks, then released his spiritual sense throughout the surrounding area.

In the next instant, he abruptly swooped downward and plunged into the sea.

After roaming over the seabed for a moment, he arrived at a deepsea chasm, and he flew to the bottom of the chasm without any hesitation.

There, he found a patch of flat ground before summoning a stack of array tools, which he set down one after another.

This was a rather complex array, and it took Han Li over two hours to set it up to completion.

After that, he chanted an incantation, and a blue light barrier emerged, instantly encompassing the surrounding area in a radius of several hundred feet.

The blue light barrier was very faint in color, and it was even more difficult to catch sight of in the sea. Furthermore, it wasn't giving off any magic power fluctuations, so even if one were situated very close to it, they could still easily miss it.

After doing all of this, a pleased look appeared in Han Li's eyes, and he swept a hand through the water to release around a dozen lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood, all of which were engraved with countless runes.

This was none other than his long-distance lightning teleportation array.

Even though Lu Yuqing had promised not to expose him, he didn't dare to grow complacent.

After a day and a night, he was finally able to complete the lightning array.

He then cast an incantation seal through the water, and a burst of golden lightning instantly emerged within the lightning teleportation array as it began to operate.

However, the aura of the array was completely isolated within the blue restriction, so it was completely undetectable outside.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, and after taking some more time to examine the array to ensure that there weren't any issues, he promptly departed.

A month later.

The sun gradually rose up over the horizon, but the entirety of Dark Veil Island was still enshrouded in a murky veil of mist.

The mist slowly began to dissipate as gusts of sea breeze blew over the island, and the branches of the trees all over the island were rustling incessantly. Smoke from stove fires was rising up from all of the mortal settlements on the island, and everything appeared serene and peaceful.

All of a sudden, Han Li appeared in the sky above the island amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

At this moment, his entire body was enveloped within a faint watery light barrier, giving him the appearance of an indistinct shadow that could vanish at any moment.

His expression eased slightly at the sight of the serene scenes down below.

In the current Black Wind Sea, only secluded islands like Dark Veil Island could still enjoy this level of peace and serenity.

He cast his gaze downward, and a hint of a surprise suddenly appeared on his face.

The island remained virtually unchanged, except the village-like settlement of the Luo Clan had been completely replaced with a stretch of luxurious palaces complete with exquisite pagodas and pavilions, as well as some lotus flower ponds, resembling a glorious immortal abode.

Streaks of light were flying over the palaces, and all of them were members of the Luo Clan.

There were far more of them than before, and their cultivation bases had also improved significantly on average. It seemed that Dark Veil Island had been thriving since he was last here, and some of the mortal cities all over the island had also enjoyed large population spikes.

A pleased look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and abruptly vanished into thin air, then reappeared in front of a certain place down below.

Inside the palace was a huge altar, upon which stood a deity statue of none other than Han Li.

At this moment, two people were kowtowing and praying to the deity statue.

Both of them were at the Grand Ascension Stage, and bursts of formidable power of faith were converging toward the statue.

Moments later, the two of them rose to their feet, then raised their heads to look up at the statue.

One of these two people was Luo Feng, and he had made significant strides in his cultivation base.

The other person was a middle-aged man with large eyes and bushy brows, and Han Li recalled that he was a Body Integration Stage elder by the name of Luo Ming, but he had also progressed to the Grand Ascension Stage during the past few centuries.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps rang out from outside the palace, and a young man who was also dressed in Luo Clan attire arrived.

Instead of entering the palace, he extended a respectful curtsey while standing outside as he declared, "Clan Head, Grand Elder, the preparations for the ceremony are complete."

"Good. Have all of the island masters arrived?" Luo Feng asked as he rose to his feet.

"Island Master Tie Yan and Island Master Chen Zhong have already arrived. Island Master Ling Yun says that he has some matters to attend to on Dusk Cloud Island, so he'll be coming a little later, but he definitely won't delay the ceremony tomorrow," the young man replied in a respectful manner.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

Tie Yan and Chen Zhong were a pair of itinerant cultivators who had pledged their subordination to Dark Veil Island in the wake of Han L's slaying of Han Qiu and Mistress Gu Gu, and they had been sent by him to oversee those two islands.

As for Dusk Cloud Island, that was a nearby island, and judging from what the young man had just said, it seemed to have pledged its subordination to Dark Veil Island as well.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon hearing this.

It seemed that Luo Feng and the others had done quite well, and at this point, Dark Veil Island was most likely one of the most powerful islands in this area.

As for the ceremony, this was an event that was held on Dark Veil Island once every 50 years.

"Alright, you can go now. Proceed according to the plan, and do not gloss over any details," Luo Feng instructed with a dismissive wave of his hand.

"Yes, Clan Head," the young man replied with a respectful bow before departing.

Following the young man's departure,Luo Ming asked,"Clan Head, will Master Liu Shi be attending this ceremony?"

He then hesitated momentarily before continuing, "Master Liu Shi has already been in seclusion for several centuries. Is it possible that something's gone wrong with his cultivation?"

"Cease your baseless speculation! Master Liu Shi's powers are unfathomable, how could any problem have possibly arisen in his cultivation? At his cultivation base, it's very common to go into seclusion for hundreds or even thousands of years, so don't say anything like that ever again," Luo Feng scolded with a stern expression.

"I naturally also attribute no weight to these baseless claims, but after the disappearance of Ancestral God Luo Meng in the past, even though our island has been peaceful these past few centuries, many of our people are still quite anxious about the possibility of the ancestral god disappearing again.

“On top of that, with all the conflict taking place in the Black Wind Sea, those concerns have only been heightened, and to further compound these woes, Master Liu Shi hasn't made an appearance in several centuries. Tie Yan, Ling Yun, and the others appear quite respectful and obedient on the surface, but if Master Liu Shi continues to remain in seclusion, there's no telling whether they could hatch some nefarious plans," Luo Ming said.

Luo Feng's brows also furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"Clan Head, I suggest you go and see Master Liu Shi and implore him to make an appearance at this ceremony, even if it's just this once," Luo Ming advised.

"Alright, I'll put that on my agenda," Luo Feng replied with a nod.

After that, the two of them began to discuss some finer details pertaining to the ceremony, and Han Li discreetly departed.

He had come to see whether Luo Feng had been acting according to his instructions these past few centuries, and he was quite reassured to see that Luo Feng was still performing his duties and obligations.

After leaving Dark Veil Island, Han Li arrived at a nearby region of the sea, where there was a vast vortex that was swirling incessantly.

Han Li flew into the water in a flash, quickly reaching the seabed.

There was a hemispherical blue light barrier that was around an acre in size overlooking the seabed, and layers of rippling blue light were flashing over its surface.

Seawater was able to pass through the light barrier without any impediment, and Han Li cast an incantation seal through the water, upon which an opening immediately appeared on the light barrier, allowing him to fly through.

At this moment, his Earthly Deity Avatar was seated with its legs crossed on the seabed with a thread of blue light hovering above its head. This was a water law thread, and it was far thicker than when Han Li last saw it, with countless tiny runes flashing within it.

The avatar was enshrouded within a thick layer of blue light that was rippling incessantly, and all of the surrounding seawater was swirling around it.

Judging from the formidable spiritual pressure that it was giving off, the Earthly Deity Avatar had already reached the mid-True Immortal Stage, and it was approaching the pinnacle of that stage, so it wasn't far away from the late-True Immortal Stage.

Chapter 354: Site Selection

Han Li wasn't all that surprised to see this.

This avatar had been constantly cultivating by manifesting heavy water using the time crystals, and even though there had been some occasional interruptions, its rate of progression wasn't much slower than Han Li's, so it was no surprise that it had reached the mid-True Immortal Stage.

Right at this moment, the blue light radiating from the avatar's body faded, and it rose to its feet, while the vortex in the sea slowly subsided.

"Thanks for your hard work," Han Li said.

"We are one and the same, so there's no need to thank me. Here's the heavy water I've derived these past years," the Earthly Deity Avatar replied as it flipped its hand over to produce a black pouch, then offered it to Han Li.

Han Li reached out to grab the pouch, but the Earthly Deity Avatar didn't let go right away. Instead, he cautioned, "Be careful, it's very heavy."

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he braced himself, but in the instant that the Earthly Deity Avatar released the pouch, his arm was still abruptly dragged downward, and his entire body was almost thrown forward by the enormous weight of the pouch.

He let loose a low roar as the muscles on his arm bulged, while a layer of golden light appeared over his body, and only then was he able to arrest the pouch's downward momentum.

A hint of surprise flashed through his eyes upon seeing this.

Heavy water had to be refined before he could manipulate it at will, but the fact that he was struggling to hold up such a small pouch even with his current tremendous strength indicated that it had to be containing an enormous volume of heavy water.

With that in mind, he injected his spiritual sense into the pouch, upon which he was once again rather surprised by what he saw.

This was a Heavenly Water Pouch that he had purchased from the Transient Guild for a high price, and it was able to store an entire large lake's worth of water, yet it had almost been completely filled.

"Impressive!" Han Li remarked with a pleased nod.

"After I reached the mid-True Immortal Stage and the fourth level of the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome, my rate of heavy water derivation sped up significantly. This pouch of heavy water is almost enough to be refined into a small creek's worth of level four heavy water," the Earthly Deity Avatar explained.

Han Li nodded in response, and he stowed the Heavenly Water Pouch away before producing two identical empty pouches that he handed to his avatar. "Keep cultivating, and I'll try to supply you with as many time crystals as possible."

The Earthly Deity Avatar accepted the pair of porches without a word, then sat back down with his legs crossed.

Immediately thereafter, blue light re-emerged over his body, while the law thread above his head gave off dazzling blue light, forming a tiny blue vortex.

The surrounding seawater was churned up into a huge vortex once again around Earthly Deity Avatar, and a tiny speck of heavy water was slowly gradually taking shape between the palms of the avatar's hands, and it was expanding at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, and he immediately urged, "Hold on a second!"

The blue light radiating from the Earthly Deity Avatar's body instantly faded, and it rose to its feet once again.

"Did you just say that upon reaching the fourth level of the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome, your rate of heavy water derivation has significantly increased?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

The avatar nodded in response. "It increased by about threefold."

Han Li was quite stunned to hear this, and he immediately asked, "Threefold! Has the same thing been happening with each level that you've progressed in the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome?"

"For the first three levels, the rate has also been increasing, but not by much. However, upon reaching the fourth level, the rate suddenly increased drastically," the avatar replied.

A hint of excitement flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

Progress was extremely slow in the early stages of the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome, and he certainly wasn't expecting something like this to happen.

The Earthly Immortal who had created the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome had only just reached the third level before he gave up on the cultivation art, unable to bear its agonizingly slow rate of progression any longer, and he most likely hadn't anticipated this, either.

At this point, Han Li was seriously beginning to doubt that the Earthly Immortal was actually the creator of the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome.

If he really had created the cultivation art, then this shouldn't have been something that he had failed to anticipate. It was very likely that someone else had created the cultivation art, and he had only obtained it from somewhere before declaring that he was the creator.

"Alright, you can keep cultivating," Han Li said with a contemplative look in his eyes.

He was really eager to find out whether there would be another significant jump in the rate of heavy water derivation upon reaching the fifth stage of the cultivation art.

If so, then with the assistance of the time crystals, the rate of heavy water derivation would reach an incredible level, and even deriving level eight and level nine heavy water at some point in the future wouldn't have been unrealistic.

The Earthly Deity Avatar sat back down with its legs crossed to resume its cultivation, while Han Li observed it with a contemplative look in his eyes.

All of a sudden, he cast his gaze up toward the surface of the sea.

A streak of light had just flown over from afar and stopped outside the blue light barrier. It was none other than Luo Feng, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he greeted, "Luo Feng pays his respects to Master Liu Shi."

On the seabed, Han Li replied, "What is it, Luo Feng?"

Luo Feng faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which an ecstatic look appeared on his face as he hurriedly explained, "Master Liu Shi, our Dark Veil Island's bicentennial ceremony will be taking place tomorrow. Would you be able to make an appearance during the event?"

He had visited Liu Shi several times in the past without receiving a response, so he was fully prepared to be disappointed again, and he was ecstatic that he had received a response for once.

The vortex in the sea continued to churn and swirl, and there was no response.

A sense of urgency welled up in Luo Feng's heart, and he said, "I don't wish to disturb your cultivation, Master Liu Shi, but there's recently been a lot of unrest in the Black Wind Sea. The conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island is becoming more and more intense, and many of our island's people are growing quite concerned. If you can make an appearance tomorrow, that would surely be a very reassuring sight for everyone..."

"Alright, I'll make an appearance during the ceremony tomorrow."

Han Li's voice rang out from the seabed to cut off Luo Feng.

"Thank you, Master Liu Shi! I'll be taking my leave now!"

Luo Feng was ecstatic, and he extended a respectful bow toward the seabed before flying back to Dark Veil Island.

……

Inside the light barrier, Han Li withdrew his gaze.

His Earthly Deity Avatar was going to make an appearance during the ceremony in his stead.

Given its current mid-True Immortal Stage power, it was more than enough to intimidate those early-True Immortal Stage itinerant cultivators.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to produce the jade seal that contained the map of the Black Wind Sea, then pressed it against his own forehead.

Now that everything had already been settled, it was time to find a place to go into seclusion.

Dark Veil Island was relatively safe and peaceful, but it wasn't actually an ideal place for him to go into seclusion.

While it was unlikely for his identity as Liu Shi to be exposed, there were no guarantees in the matter, and he didn't want to risk the prospect of having the identity of Liu Shi traced back to him.

Around an hour later, a barely visible streak of azure light flew out of the sea and into the distance.

Only after three days and three nights did Han Li draw to a halt, and he had arrived in an area of the Black Wind Sea that was even more secluded than Dark Veil Island, with nothing but ocean and small deserted islands as far as the eyes could see.

The islands were completely uninhabited by humans, but there were many demon beasts on both the islands and the nearby sea, with no lack of Body Integration and even Grand Ascension Stage demon beasts among them.

Han Li looked around to find that the spirit veins on these islands were decent, not quite on the same level as Dark Veil Island, but there was still a relative abundance of spiritual qi in the area.

This place was already extremely far away from Dark Veil Island, and virtually no cultivators ever came here, making it an ideal location for seclusion.

As for the demon beasts in the area, those naturally posed no threat to him.

With that in mind, he spread his enormous spiritual sense throughout the area, and a short while later, he descended onto a small island down below.

The island wasn't very large, only several dozen kilometers in diameter.

The environment on the island was rather complex, with a volcano that was around 1,000 feet tall situated at its center, and due to the frequent volcanic eruptions, there was no plant life around, only crimson rocks littered all over the landscape.

However, a bit further away from the volcano was a lush forest, and even further away were a series of ponds and swamps, as well as a vibrant grassland.

It was a place that was full of vitality, and there were even some spirit plants and spirit flowers growing here.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this.

The island wasn't very large, but its spirit vein was the best one in the nearby area.

He arrived at an obscure little canyon on the island, then swept a hand through the air to release a streak of azure sword qi, which sliced through a mountain face like tofu, and before long, a cave abode had taken shape.

Han Li didn't put too much effort into refining the cave abode, only paying a little extra attention when carving out the spirit medicine garden. After that, he pulled out a stack of array flags and array plates before setting them up near the new cave abode.

With the restrictions activated, a burst of gentle azure light appeared, following which the cave abode abruptly vanished, transforming into a lush forest that blended in with the nearby environment.

This restriction was the same as the one he had set up earlier on the seabed in that it wasn't giving off any aura, so even if a True Immortal were to scour the area with their spiritual sense, they weren't likely to discover it.

After that, Han Li summoned several more stacks of array tools that had been previously used to set up restrictions around his cave abode back on the Crimson Dawn Peak, and before long, the new cave abode resembled an impregnable fortress.

He had even pulled out another array and set it up around the entire island, but he refrained from activating those restrictions right away, saving them for potential future enemy attacks instead.

After doing all of that, he strode into his cave abode and arrived at the medicine garden.

He had made sure to carve out a large area for the garden, even more so than the one back in his cave abode on the Crimson Dawn Peak.

After standing on the spot for a while, he swept a sleeve several times in succession through the air, summoning clumps of spirit soil of different colors that descended into the medicine garden.

Some of these things had been prepared by him in advance, while others had been purchased on the way back to the Black Wind Sea.

Chapter 355: Sealing the Island

After that, Han Li pulled out various types of spirit liquid and began to mix batches of spirit soil while also setting up restrictions throughout the medicine garden to split it up into different sections.

Only after doing all of that did he pull out all of the spirit medicines in his storage pouch before carefully transferring them to this new medicine garden.

While Han Li was arranging his medicine garden, the ceremony on Dark Veil Island had also commenced.

At this moment, the entire sky above the island was enshrouded in a layer of vibrant crimson light, and black wooden pillars with lit braziers on top of them had also appeared all over the island, giving the event a sense of prestige and occasion.

On a giant plaza stood three huge lit wooden pyres, each of which was several hundred feet tall, and at the center of the pyres was a massive altar.

Atop the altar was a deity statue that was over 100 feet tall, and many people were gathered at the foot of the altar, including all of the cultivators of the Luo Clan.

Aside from them, there were also cultivators in alternative attire, and they were from Dark Veil Island's three subsidiary islands.

In front of the crowd stood four figures. The one on the very left was Luo Feng, and he was joined by a fair-skinned young man, a middle-aged scholarly man with a black mole on his face, and a beautiful woman wearing a long green dress that exposed a sliver of her fair and voluptuous cleavage.

At this moment, everyone was worshiping the altar, and these four were no exception.

Luo Feng wore a solemn expression and was impeccable in every single one of his movements, while the other three had hints of disdain on their faces and were clearly just going through the motions.

They were all True Immortal cultivators, so they were naturally quite reluctant to be worshiping a statue of another True Immortal.

As time passed, the ceremony quickly approached its conclusion.

At this point, Luo Feng and the other three figures beside him had already departed from the front of the crowd and sat down on some nearby chairs.

"Clan Head Luo, today's ceremony is an important occasion for Dark Veil Island. Is Fellow Daoist Liu Shi still not going to make an appearance?" the fair-skinned young man suddenly asked.

"Come to think of it, I only ever met Fellow Daoist Liu Shi once several centuries ago, and he's been in seclusion ever since then. Is he cultivating some type of ability or secret technique?" the scholarly man asked.

The young woman was also looking at Luo Feng, and even though she wasn't saying anything, the inquisitive look in her eyes was very apparent.

Luo Feng took a glance at the trio, then smiled as he replied, "I already met with Master Liu Shi yesterday, and he'll be making an appearance today."

The expressions of the trio instantly changed slightly upon hearing this.

"Is that true?"

"Of course," Luo Feng replied with a smile.

The fair-skinned young man exchanged a glance with the other two True Immortals, then nodded as he said, "It would be great if Fellow Daoist Liu could make an appearance. At the moment, the Black Wind Sea is a state of widespread turmoil, and we'll need him to make decisions on how our Dark Veil Island is to proceed from here onward."

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Tie Yan. All of the major powers across the entire Black Wind Sea are keenly observing the unfolding situation. Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island are far too formidable for a small island like ours to compare with, so we have to make sure that we don't make any missteps. Otherwise, the consequences could be catastrophic," the scholarly man chimed in.

The fair-skinned young man's name was Tie Yan, while the scholarly man's name was Chen Zhong.

A grim look appeared on Luo Feng's face upon hearing this, and he offered no response.

"There's no need to be so pessimistic, everyone. With us and Fellow Daoist Liu joining forces, we're certainly nothing to be scoffed at, and we should be more than enough to protect these few islands," the young woman suddenly said.

"You sure are optimistic, Fellow Daoist Ling Yun," Tie Yan replied with a faint smile, but it was clear that he wasn't convinced.

The ceremony continued, yet even as it was about to reach a conclusion, Han Li still hadn't made an appearance.

Luo Feng was still seated on his chair, but a hint of anxiety had crept into his eyes, he was occasionally darting glances in the direction where Han Li was in seclusion, while the expressions of Tie Yan's trio were also becoming more skeptical by the minute.

"It looks like Fellow Daoist Liu may be busy and can't make an appearance today, after all," Tie Yan remarked.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a speck of blue light suddenly appeared on the distant horizon before rapidly expanding as it approached from afar.

A burst of rumbling that resembled the sound of countless thundering horse hooves rang out, and all of the world's origin qi in the surrounding area surged violently, forming streaks of blue light that converged from all directions, basking everything near the altar in a blue glow.

At the same time, a burst of tremendous spiritual pressure descended upon everyone down below from the blue light, and everyone was instantly rooted to the spot.

The expressions of Tie Yan's trio changed drastically as they looked up into the sky, and Chen Zhong gulped nervously as he exclaimed to himself in a feeble voice, "He's reached the mid-True Immortal Stage!"

Tie Yan and Ling Yun were just as astonished, and a hint of fear and alarm had surfaced in their eyes.

All of a sudden, all of the blue light faded, and a blue figure slowly descended onto the altar before withdrawing their immense spiritual pressure.

The figure was completely enshrouded in a layer of blue light that gave them an indistinct appearance, and one could only barely make out the outlines of a man standing with his hands clasped behind his back.

Luo Feng was ecstatic, and he immediately extended a respectful salute. "Ancestral God Liu Shi!"

All of the Luo Clan's cultivators were also relieved and elated to see Han Li's arrival, and they hurriedly extended respectful salutes as well.

Everyone else from the other islands quickly followed suit, as did Tie Yan's trio.

"No need for formalities," the blue figure said, and his voice wasn't very loud, but it was clearly audible to everyone present.

Everyone immediately reverted to their original standing postures as they cast their eyes toward the blue figure.

All of the Luo Clan's cultivators were looking at him with fervent elation, but the same didn't apply to some of the cultivators from the other three islands.

"While it's true that I've been in cultivation for the entirety of the past few centuries, I've been keeping tabs on everything that's been happening on the islands and in the Black Wind Sea," the blue figure declared.

The expressions of Tie Yan's trio instantly stiffened slightly upon hearing this.

"Luo Feng, you've managed the islands quite well these past few centuries. Here is a vial of Profound Moon Pills as a reward for your efforts," the blue figure said as he swept a hand through the air to send a burst of blue light flying toward Luo Feng, and the blue light quickly faded to reveal a white jade vial.

An ecstatic look appeared on Luo Feng's face as he hurriedly extended a grateful bow. "Thank you, Ancestral God Liu Shi!"

A hint of admiration flashed through the eyes of Tie Yan's trio upon seeing this.

Profound Moon Pills were extremely renowned pills that had a substantial cultivation enhancement effect even on True Immortal cultivators. However, they were extremely rare, and Black Wind Island was perhaps the only place where they could be purchased in the entire Black Wind Sea.

"Keep working hard in your cultivation and strive to reach the True Immortal Stage as soon as possible," the blue figure instructed.

"I won't disappoint you, Ancestral God Liu Shi!" Luo Feng vowed with a firm nod.

"Tie Yan, Chen Zhong, Ling Yun, the three of you have also worked hard. You can have these three spirit treasures," the blue figure continued as he swept his sleeve through the air once again, releasing three streaks of light that descended in front of the trio before revealing a set of treasures, namely a green jade scepter, a white bead, and a small yellow flag.

All three treasures were premium spirit treasures that were giving off extremely formidable magic power fluctuations and were only one step away from immortal treasures.

Tie Yan's trio was ecstatic, and they split the treasures among themselves before also extending grateful bows.

The blue figure swept a sleeve through the air a third time, this time sending a storage tool flying toward Luo Feng.

"Luo Feng, there are some pills and cultivation resources in there for you to distribute as you see fit and maximize the power of our Dark Veil Island," the blue figure said.

Luo Feng immediately gave an affirmative response.

"As for the ongoing conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island, that has nothing to do with our Dark Veil Island, so in order to avoid getting swept up in the conflict, from this day forth, everyone is strictly forbidden from leaving the island, and all islands will enter a period of lockdown," the blue figure declared.

This wasn't a surprising decision from Han Li, and no one raised any objections.

The blue figure swept his gaze over everyone present as he declared, "Rest assured, everyone. So long as you remain loyal to Dark Veil Island, I will ensure your safety."

Everyone was instilled with a sense of warmth and reassurance upon hearing this, and they extended another collective grateful bow.

After that, the blue figure didn't linger any longer, promptly departing into the distance as a streak of blue light.

Tie Yan's trio watched as the blue figure departed, then exchanged a few glances, and all of the skepticism they previously harbored had been completely erased, replaced with nothing but awe and veneration.

……

Several days later.

On a small island a vast distance away, Han Li was in a state of seated meditation when he suddenly opened his eyes as a faint smile appeared on his face.

His Earthly Deity Avatar had already informed him that Dark Veil Island and its three subsidiary islands had all activated their protective arrays, cutting the islands off from all external contact.

This was naturally something that he had planned in advance.

By sealing the islands, he could minimize his chances of being swept up in the conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island, thereby mitigating the risk of his identity being exposed as much as possible.

With that matter settled, he rose to his feet and arrived at his spirit medicine garden.

The garden had a radius of close to 1,000 feet, and it had already been split up into several dozen different sections through the use of light barriers of different colors. The environment in each section was different, allowing for different spirit medicines to thrive.

Some sections were hot, some sections were cold, and some were completely shielded from all light, giving them a perpetual night-like environment.

The spirit medicines had become a little wilted after being stored in Han Li's storage pouch for some time, but now that they had been replanted, they were quickly recovering their vitality.

Aside from that, Han Li had also planted some of the spirit medicine seeds that he had recently acquired, as well as his other primary bean.

At the moment, he simply didn't have a sufficient number of Dao Warriors at his disposal to serve any substantial purpose, so he had to grow some more.

Among these spirit medicines, Han Li was naturally particularly invested in the primary ingredients required to refine the Myriad Axis Pill, namely the Myriad Axis Fruit, the Herofall Flower, and the Blood Crystal Lotus Root. He had planted them in the best locations in the garden and also used the best spirit soil as well.

In particular, he had spent a great deal of time and effort crafting a spirit pond for the length of Blood Crystal Lotus Root that he had purchased during that auction.

He had already gathered a sufficient quantity of all of the Myriad Axis Pill's supplementary ingredients, so once these three primary ingredients were ready, he would be able to commence the pill refinement process.

Chapter 356: Myriad Axis Pill

After carefully examining these three spirit medicines and instructing his giant ape puppet to water them with the Heaven Controlling Vial's spirit liquid in a timely fashion, Han Li departed from the medicine garden and returned to his secret chamber before sitting down with his legs crossed.

At this point, it wouldn't be long before all of the ingredients required to refine the Myriad Axis Pill were ready.

Hence, his current priority was acquiring the two remaining ingredients required for dao pill refinement, namely the Heavenmade Ginseng Root and the Dewform Herb.

With that in mind, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce his Transient Guild mask before putting it on.

He then began to read through the missions in a well-rehearsed fashion, yet there were still no responses to the missions that he had released to acquire those two spirit ingredients.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he erased the previous missions before releasing them again, except the rewards were tripled this time.

With such substantial rewards on offer, he was confident that it was only a matter of time before he received some responses.

After doing all of that, he stowed his Transient Guild mask away, then pulled out a pair of storage tools, which he had obtained from the pair of Azure Feather Island cultivators.

After briefly inspecting their contents with his spiritual sense, he couldn't help but shake his head in dismay.

The cultivators of the Black Wind Sea were downright impoverished compared with their counterparts in the outside world, and their storage tools contained nothing of sufficient value to catch his eye.

All of a sudden, he raised an eyebrow as he flipped a hand over to produce an azure badge.

This was an item in the bald man's storage tool, and it had been crafted from some type of azure spirit jade. On one side was engraved the image of a phoenix-like azure spirit bird, while on the other side was inscribed the character for "Feather".

This must be some type of badge from Azure Feather Island.

The badge didn't appear to contain any information on the bald man, which set it apart from the average identification badge, and that left Han Li feeling a little perplexed.

He inspected the badge a moment longer before stowing it away. After all, he had no interest in native powers of the Black Wind Island like Azure Feather Island anyway, so he naturally didn't want to waste any time or effort studying the badge.

After closing his eyes for a moment to prime himself into optimal condition, he began to examine the third level of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

Even though he had already reached the late-True Immortal Stage, he still hadn't truly begun cultivating the third level of the Mantra Axis Scripture as it was far more difficult to understand than the previous two levels, and he was still yet to completely grasp it.

He was waiting for the three primary ingredients for the Myriad Axis Pill to mature anyway, so this was a good opportunity to study the cultivation art.

Over 30 years passed by in the blink of an eye.

Throughout this entire time, the gate of Han Li's cave abode hadn't been opened even once, and it was already covered in a thick layer of dust.

Of course, no one had come to visit him during this time, either.

At this moment, Han Li was standing in his medicine garden, and he was in the process of carefully picking three golden spirit fruits from a golden spirit tree that was around 10 feet tall. These were none other than Myriad Axis Fruits.

He gave a pleased nod at the sight of the fruits in his hands, and he stowed them away in his storage bracelet before leaving his medicine garden to make his way to the pill refinement chamber.

On the way, he stopped in his tracks and took a glance at another secret chamber.

This was where Daoist Xie was staying in seclusion. Around a decade ago, Daoist Xie had suddenly requested Han Li to arrange a secret chamber for it, and Han Li naturally wasn't going to refuse such a request.

However, up to this point, nothing seemed to have happened in the secret chamber, and Han Li had no idea what Daoist Xie was doing in there.

Daoist Xie was only becoming more and more mysterious in his eyes, and he couldn't help but feel as if it were harboring some type of obscure secret.

However, as long as Daoist Xie wasn't doing anything to his detriment, he naturally wasn't going to meddle in its business. After all, he had far too much on his plate already.

With that in mind, he made his way into his pill refinement chamber, then activated all of the surrounding restrictions before sitting down with his legs crossed.

During these past few decades, the vast majority of the spirit liquid that had been manifested by the Heaven Controlling Vial had been used to mature the Myriad Axis Fruit, the Herofall Flower, and the Blood Crystal Lotus Root.

At this point, he had finally matured sufficient ingredients to refine 30 batches of pills, and he could begin attempting to refine Myriad Axis Pills.

He meditated for half a day to prime himself into the best possible condition, then swept both sleeves through the air to summon that silver cauldron, as well as the fiery silver figure, which fell under the cauldron.

The fiery silver figure sat down with its legs crossed, then made a hand seal, and the silver flames on its body instantly reared up before splitting up into nine identical bursts of flames that enveloped the underside of the cauldron in an extremely even fashion.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air once again, and 30 batches of Myriad Axis Pill refinement ingredients emerged, laid out beside him in an orderly fashion.

He had already thought about the refinement method for the Myriad Axis Pill countless times these past years, so he couldn't have been more familiar with it.

He opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light that flew into the cauldron, and its lid instantly flew off on its own.

Han Li picked up a Myriad Axis Fruit, then flicked a finger through the air, and several streaks of azure swordlight shot forth, shredding the fruit into a clump of golden puree in the blink of an eye.

The core of the fruit had been set aside, and he carefully guided the puree into the cauldron, which was quickly heating up thanks to the silver flames.

The Myriad Axis Fruit puree quickly melted into a ball of golden liquid, following which Han Li picked up a white gel ingredient that he also guided into the cauldron.

Han Li proceeded to remain in the pill refinement chamber for three whole years.

On this day, the door of the pill refinement chamber abruptly swung open, and Han Li emerged from inside with an excited gleam in his eyes, indicating that he was in quite a good mood.

He flipped a hand over to produce a longan-sized pill amid a flash of golden light, and the pill was golden in color, giving off a gentle golden glow.

Upon closer inspection, one would discover that this layer of golden light was formed by layers of thin golden patterns, presenting a profound sight to behold.

This was none other than a Myriad Axis Pill.

Despite the tiny size of the pill, there were over 10,000 layers of these golden patterns on its surface, and that was most likely where it had gotten its name from.

As a pill that could enhance even a late-True Immortal cultivator's cultivation base, not only had it been very difficult to acquire all of the ingredients required to refine it, the refinement process itself was also the most complex out of any pill that Han Li had attempted to refine thus far.

Even though he was already a pill refinement master and had the assistance of the Mantra Treasured Axis, which could slow time down to a crawl, he was still only able to successfully refine half a batch of pills after going through 10 batches of ingredients in the first year.

However, he had learned a great deal from these failures, and as a result, his success rate had steadily risen. In the end, he managed to successfully refine five and a half batches of pills in the past three years using the 30 batches of ingredients, amounting to a total of 55 pills.

For the ordinary Earthly Pill Master, even 10 batches of Myriad Axis Pill ingredients would've been impossible to gather in a short time, let alone 30. Furthermore, a success rate of just under 20% didn't seem to have been particularly impressive, but if Ping Yaozi were to learn about this in the afterlife, he would be so shocked that his jaw would drop straight to the floor.

Even for the likes of Xiong Shan, Myriad Axis Pills were worth fighting over, even at the risk of his life, and even if he were to obtain a Myriad Axis Pill, he would most likely choose to save it for an important breakthrough in his cultivation, rather than consume it right away.

After all, even in the context of the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region, there were only several types of pills that could advance the cultivation bases of late-True Immortal cultivators, and even a formidable sect like the Blaze Dragon Dao didn't have many of these pills at its disposal. Otherwise, Golden Immortal cultivators wouldn't have been so rare.

However, this wasn't a problem for Han Li. In fact, he could refine even more Myriad Axis Pills in the future so that he would never have to stop taking them during his cultivation.

At this moment, Han Li was in quite a good mood, but not because of the number of Myriad Axis Pills that he had managed to refine. More importantly, he discovered that his pill refinement mastery had improved rapidly over the course of the past three years, and it reached a certain bottleneck.

He had a feeling that if he could progress through this bottleneck, then his pill refinement skills would reach a whole new level.

With that in mind, he took a deep breath and stowed the Myriad Axis Pills away, then emerged from the pill refinement chamber.

Before long, he had arrived at his medicine garden once again, and he stopped at the spot where the primary bean had been planted.

Under his instructions, the giant ape puppet would water it with a drop of spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial every once in a while, yet the primary bean still showed no signs of sprouting.

However, given his past experience, Han Li knew what to expect, so he wasn't bothered or agitated in the slightest as he made his way over to a white spirit pond.

The pond was roughly 70 to 80 feet in size with a layer of faint white mist over its surface.

Several crimson lotus flowers were floating on its surface, and wisps of crimson mist could be seen drifting out of its stamen, releasing an extremely rich aroma of sweetness.

One of the lotus flowers was particularly large, comparable to the size of a washbasin, while the other ones were all far smaller.

Han Li looked beneath that lotus flower to find a huge lotus root that was as thick as a bucket extending into the soil at the bottom of the spirit pond from the underside of the flower. The root was around 10 feet in length, and it was very translucent, giving off a layer of dense crimson light.

There were several smaller roots branching off from the main lotus root, but they were far lacking in both thickness and coloration compared with the main root.

On the main root was a fist-sized gray mark that was very dark in coloration, resembling a smudge of ink.

This lotus root was the very same one that Han Li had purchased from the auction, and he was using it to breed more Blood Crystal Lotus Roots in order to support his Myriad Axis Pill refinement.

At this point, the lotus root had already been matured to at least 200,000 to 300,000 years old.

The older the main ingredient, the higher the success rate of Myriad Axis Pill refinement, and the more efficacious the pills were going to be.

During the lotus root's growth, the bonded mark on its surface had also changed slightly in appearance. Not only had it grown larger and darker, certain patterns had emerged within it, resembling the veins of a leaf.

Furthermore, Han Li could sense law power fluctuations emanating from the mark, albeit only very faint ones.

However, it wasn't time law fluctuations. Instead, it was some other type of unknown law power.

This was quite a surprise to Han Li as he definitely hadn't sensed any law power fluctuations from the bonded mark before this, and they had most likely arisen due to the watering from the Heaven Controlling Vial spirit liquid.

In the wake of this discovery, he couldn't help but feel a little intrigued by this bonded mark, and he was eager to see how it was going to change in the future.

Chapter 357: The Final Step

Han Li stayed beside the white spirit pond for a while longer before leaving the medicine garden, then returned to his bedroom before immediately falling asleep.

These past three years, he had been refining Myriad Axis Pills without rest, and the entire pill refinement process was one that required his full attention. At the same time, he had to calculate the timing of his usage of the Mantra Treasured Axis, and even with his late-True Immortal Stage cultivation base and spiritual sense, he was feeling quite exhausted.

Prior to commencing his cultivation, he had to take some time to recover so that he could prime his body, mind, and magic power into the best possible condition.

He slept for three days and three nights, and upon awakening, he was once again raring to go, arriving in his secret chamber before sitting down with his legs crossed and summoning an azure jade vial.

He tipped the vial over slightly to produce a Myriad Axis Pill, and after holding it between his fingers and inspecting it for a while, he promptly swallowed the pill.

The pill quickly melted in his stomach before surging throughout all of his meridians as a powerful flow of warmth.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and he felt as if this surge of warmth were like a pack of galloping wild horses that were flowing faster and faster through his meridians while gradually forming a series of vortexes, resulting in a painful and swollen sensation in those meridians.

Moments later, Han Li's brows gradually unfurrowed as an elated look appeared on his face.

The Myriad Axis Pill was even more efficacious than he had anticipated.

He gently exhaled as he focused his attention on his Mantra Axis Scripture, commencing a process of immersive cultivation.

A layer of gentle golden light rose up to envelop his entire body, and the years slowly passed.

The dust that was accumulating outside the gate of the cave abode was becoming thicker and thicker, and at this point, it was virtually impossible to tell that there was still a gate on the mountain face.

500 years was an extremely long time for mortals. During this time, entire empires could rise up and collapse, yet for cultivators, it was nothing more than one bout of seclusion.

On this day, countless dark clouds suddenly converged in the sky above the island, and arcs of lightning were flashing incessantly within the clouds.

All of the world's origin qi in a radius of thousands of kilometers churned violently to form an enormous spiritual energy vortex that was slowly revolving in the sky.

Countless balls of spiritual qi appeared in the sky, and they converged toward the island, drawn there by the revolving vortex.

Several dozen kilometers away from the island was a fiery red island that was only around a half a kilometer in radius, and it was a coral island that was extremely beautiful and resplendent under the light of the sun.

All of a sudden, a crimson demon beast emerged from the water near the island with a splash.

The demon beast was over 100 feet in length and resembled a boar with steely crimson fur. There was also a pair of white tusks protruding out of its mouth, giving off a metallic gleam.

What was more remarkable about this creature was that it had six legs.

Its facial features were quite menacing, but its body was as round and rotund as a watermelon, so it appeared far more comical than it did threatening.

If any cultivators familiar with the Black Wind Sea were present, they would've been able to identify this demon beast as a Pig Dolphin Beast, a very common low-grade demon beast in this region, except this one was already at the late-Nascent Soul Stage.

The beast's rotund body abruptly swelled up, and it opened its mouth up wide to produce a burst of powerful suction force, allowing it to gobble up some of the balls of spiritual qi in the air.

A layer of red light then began to flash over its body, and the phenomenon lasted for about two hours before the balls of spiritual qi in the air faded away.

The Pig Dolphin Beast closed its mouth, and the red light radiating from its body was looking a little brighter than before.

The beast cast its gaze toward the island in the distance, then oinked a few times as if it were asking for more.

It had already been residing here for a very long time, and several centuries ago, an extremely powerful human cultivator had arrived on that island, leading to all of the formidable demon beasts nearby moving away.

However, at the time, it had just attained a basic level of intelligence and was still rather ignorant, so it didn't leave.

The human cultivator had remained in his cave abode this entire time, and he hadn't attacked any of the nearby demon beasts.

Due to the fact that all of the more formidable demon beasts in the area had moved away, the Pig Dolphin Beast had been able to enjoy a very safe and comfortable life, and even though its intelligence had developed further since then, it had still decided not to leave.

As for why it had decided to stay, that was because during the past few centuries, that enormous spiritual qi vortex would appear every once in a while, and it had already appeared 11 times up to this point.

Whenever this happened, the Pig Dolphin Beast would use its innate ability to absorb some of the spiritual qi in the air, and that was how it had rapidly progressed from the Qi Refinement Stage to its current cultivation base in just a few centuries.

The Pig Dolphin Beast took a few more glances at the island in the distance.

Its cultivation base was already approaching the pinnacle of the Nascent Soul Stage, and if that phenomenon had lasted a while longer, perhaps it would've already reached the Deity Transformation Stage.

Looks like I'll have to wait for next time... the Pig Dolphin Beast thought to itself, then swam back into the sea.

Inside the cave abode, Han Li's entire body was radiating dazzling golden light while also giving off a burst of tremendous spiritual pressure.

As many as 35 specks of golden light had appeared over his body, and as the golden radiance slowly faded, he opened his eyes to reveal a hint of excitement within them.

He had been making rapid progress in his cultivation, opening 11 immortal acupoints in less than 600 years.

If anyone else were to hear about this rate of progress, they would be stunned beyond belief, and if they were to hear that he had a virtually limitless supply of Myriad Axis Pills at his disposal, even a Golden Immortal would be so envious that they would be coughing up blood!

Even Han Li himself hadn't anticipated that he would be able to open 11 immortal acupoints in just 500 years.

According to his original estimates, it would've taken him at least 1,000 years to reach this stage, but in reality, he had gotten there far faster.

Aside from that, there was something that was rather perplexing to Han Li about the Myriad Axis Pill, and that was the issue of resistance.

Even though he had been taking Myriad Axis Pills throughout the past 500 years, his body hadn't developed any resistance to it, thereby making it less efficacious.

He had spent some time trying to uncover the reasons for this, but his experiments hadn't yielded any conclusive results, so he ultimately set the matter aside. After all, it wasn't a bad thing, so there was no reason to dwell on it.

He shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, following which a contemplative look appeared on his face.

With 35 immortal acupoints opened, he only had one more left to reach the Golden Immortal Stage.

It was only a single step, but the difference was like that between night and day, and the degree of difficulty of making the breakthrough was comparable to a Grand Ascension cultivator ascending to immortality in the Spirit Realm.

In order to break through this bottleneck, not only did he have to open up 36 immortal acupoints, the most difficult part was overcoming the final one of the three decays, namely the acupoint decay.

Up to this point, Han Li still hadn't experienced any of the decays in his cultivation, but he had heard many stories about how damning these decays could be, so even with his current powers and abilities, he didn't dare to grow complacent.

The best way to ward off the three decays was to truly master a law power.

He was cultivating the laws of time, one of the three paramount laws, and if he could truly master it, even a little bit, then that would most likely be extremely effective for warding off the three decays.

However, up to this point, he had exhausted all of his other options without any success, and his only hope left was to refine a dao pill.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he rose to his feet and left his secret chamber before arriving in a section of his medicine garden.

There was a patch of black spirit soil here, and the air was very cool and moist.

Planted in the spirit soil was a white spirit ginseng root that was quite transparent in appearance, looking as if it had been carved out of white jade.

This was none other than one of the dao pill's primary ingredients, the Heavenmade Ginseng Root.

Finally, his persistent efforts had paid off, and he had managed to purchase a young Heavenmade Ginseng Root from the Transient Guild at a high price.

Han Li gave a pleased nod at the sight of the ginseng root.

After obtaining the ginseng root, he had immediately instructed the giant ape puppet to water it with the Heaven Controlling Vial spirit liquid, and at this point, it was already over 100,000 years of age, making it fit for pill refinement.

At this point, all that he was missing was the Dewform Herb, but there was still no news on it.

This was almost entirely up to luck anyway, and given that he was currently in the Black Wind Sea, all he could do was rely on the Transient Guild.

With that in mind, he heaved a faint sigh and returned to his secret chamber before sitting down with his legs crossed.

Even though he was still unable to refine any dao pills for now, he naturally didn't want to just sit around and do nothing. Instead, he was going to attempt to open up his 36th immortal acupoint, and at the very least, he was going to open it up most of the way to reach the pinnacle of the late-True Immortal Stage.

With that in mind, Han Li consumed another Myriad Axis Pill before closing his eyes to cultivate.

This area of the Black Wind Sea was virtually completely untouched, and it seemed to never display any changes, giving one the impression that time stood still here.

Another 50 to 60 years passed by in the blink of an eye, and once again, the Pig Dolphin Beast appeared on the nearby coral island before casting its gaze toward the island that Han Li was situated on.

According to its past experience, the spiritual qi vortex was about to appear.

During these past few years, it came out virtually every single day to check, for fear of missing out.

However, close to 10 years had already passed since the date that it had predicted, yet the spiritual qi vortex still hadn't appeared.

Not only that, but the island was completely silent, and some of the spiritual power fluctuations that had previously occasionally emanated from it had also ceased to appear.

A slightly agitated look appeared in the Pig Dolphin Beast's eyes as it continued to stare at the island in the distance.

Could it be that the human cultivator had already left?

After some further hesitation, it turned and began to swim toward the island.

Chapter 358: A Gift from the Pig Dolphin Beast

For a late-Nascent Soul Stage Pig Dolphin Beast, a distance of several dozen kilometers could be easily covered, and before long, it had already swam to the island.

It was doing its best to conceal its own aura as it swam along the edge of the island toward the cave abode of the human cultivator.

Shortly thereafter, it arrived near the cave abode before casting its gaze in that direction.

It was greeted by the sight of a lush forest that didn't appear to have been any different from the forestry around it.

The beast stared at that area of the forest for a long time before opening its mouth to release a streak of faint blue light, which flew into that area.

As soon as the blue light came into contact with the forest, it immediately vanished without a trace.

The Pig Dolphin Beast was quite elated to see this. The restriction was still standing, which meant that the human cultivator still hadn't left.

The Pig Dolphin Beast was quite relieved to see this, and it was just about to leave when an amused chuckle suddenly rang out nearby.

The Pig Dolphin Beast shuddered before turning in that direction, upon which it was so frightened that its soul almost left its body.

Standing on the shore not far away was an amused azure-robed young man, and it was none other than the human cultivator it had once seen from afar many years ago.

The Pig Dolphin Beast let loose an alarmed oink as it hurriedly tried to flee back into the sea, but the azure-robed young man made a grabbing motion, and all of the seawater in a radius of roughly half a kilometers swept back before rising up into the air.

The Pig Dolphin Beast was trapped within the seawater, completely unable to move.

"A late-Nascent Soul Stage Pig Dolphin Beast? That's quite rare," the azure-robed young man remarked.

The man was none other than Han Li, and his expression at the moment suggested that something was troubling him.

During the past few decades, he had continued to cultivate in seclusion in his cave abode, attempting to open up his 36th immortal acupoint, but even though he had continued to take Myriad Axis Pills without pause during this time, the final immortal acupoint remained completely unmoved.

On this day, he was feeling rather frustrated and was taking a stroll to take his mind off things, and he certainly wasn't expecting to encounter such a demon beast.

The Pig Dolphin Beast oinked panic and alarm as it struggled with its six stubby legs with all its might, but to no avail.

Its voice was extremely shrill, resembling the bloodcurdling howls of a fat pig that was about to be slaughtered, and it was putting on quite an amusing display that had put Han Li in a much better mood.

"Don't worry, I won't kill you," he said with a faint smile, then flicked a finger through the air to send a fiery red pill flying into the Pig Dolphin Beast's wide open mouth.

Its alarmed oinking instantly ceased, immediately following which red light flashed erratically over its rotund body, and its aura began to rapidly elevate.

A dazed look appeared on its face upon sensing this, and its struggles also gradually subsided.

Meanwhile, the red light radiating from its body continued to grow brighter and brighter, and it quickly broke through a bottleneck to reach the Deity Transformation Stage.

At the same time, the red coloration of its skin and fur completely faded, leaving it as white as snow.

The muscles on its lower abdomen squirmed momentarily, and a pair of short stubs appeared, as if two more legs were about to emerge.

"You must have decent aptitude if you're about to grow two more legs so quickly," Han Li murmured to himself before lowering his hand, and the seawater that was enveloping the Pig Dolphin Beast instantly fell back into the sea with a loud splash.

The Pig Dolphin Beast was freed, but instead of flying away, it remained standing in mid-air, staring at Han Li with a dazed expression.

"I've already helped you break through your Deity Transformation Stage bottleneck, are you still not satisfied?" Han Li asked with a faint smile.

The Pig Dolphin Beast stared at Han Li for a moment longer, then suddenly flew back into the sea and disappeared into the waves.

Meanwhile, Han Li cast his gaze toward the distant horizon with a faint smile.

He was feeling a little frustrated, but certainly not disheartened or agitated.

It was only to be expected that a Golden Immortal Stage breakthrough would be difficult to make. Otherwise, Golden Immortal cultivators wouldn't have been so rare. However, he hadn't been able to find any way to resolve this problem.

Day quickly transitioned into night, and stars appeared in the night sky.

Han Li looked up at the starry night sky, and his eyes suddenly lit up as a thought occurred to him.

He flipped a hand over to produce a gray stone slab that was covered in tiny antiquated text, and it was none other than the Great Universe Origin Arts that he had obtained from Patriarch Cold Flame.

Not long after obtaining this cultivation art, Han Li had been swept up in a string of chaotic events. As a result, he had forgotten all about it, and this stone slab had been sitting in his storage pouch this entire time.

The Big Dipper Origin Arts that he had come across in the Spirit Domain Realm had allowed him to open up seven profound acupoints, and after that, it hadn't taken him much effort at all to open up his first seven immortal acupoints.

If he wasn't mistaken, there seemed to have been some type of connection between profound acupoints and immortal acupoints. Perhaps it would become a lot easier for him to open his 36th immortal acupoint if he could first open 36 profound acupoints.

With that in mind, Han Li sat down onto the ground while holding the stone slab instead of returning to his cave abode.

Back when he had first obtained this cultivation art, he had only inspected it briefly, and now that he was carefully examining it, the excitement on his face quickly faded, slowly replaced by a wry smile.

Sure enough, both the Great Universe Origin Arts and the Big Dipper Origin Arts were similar in nature, and the former was even more profound.

However, just as Patriarch Cold Flame said, this stone slab was holding half of the cultivation art, which would only allow one to open up 18 profound acupoints. That meant that he would have to find the second half of the cultivation art in order to open 36 profound acupoints.

Patriarch Cold Flame had obtained the first half of these Great Universe Origin Arts from a set of ruins, so Han Li would most likely have to go to the same place to obtain the second half.

With that in mind, Han Li couldn't help but internally reprimand himself for not asking Patriarch Cold Flame more questions about those ruins.

It most likely wasn't going to be easy for him to find Patriarch Cold Flame again.

It appeared that Patriarch Cold Flame had most likely joined the Ubiquitous Pavilion, but trying to find someone from such an enormous organization was no different from searching for a needle in a haystack. Additionally, he didn't know much about the Ubiquitous Pavilion to begin with, and just like in the Transient Guild, the identities of its members were most likely kept secret from one another.

After contemplating the matter a moment further, he shook his head before stowing the stone slab away.

There was simply nothing that he could do about this for now.

With that in mind, Han Li turned and made his way back toward his cave abode, only to suddenly stop in his tracks before turning back to look out at the sea.

A burst of urgent oinking rang out, following which the surface of the sea parted with a loud splash, and the Pig Dolphin Beast flew out before landing beside Han Li.

It then opened its mouth, and a black object dropped out before rolling over to Han Li.

A sizzling sound could be heard coming from the Pig Dolphin Beast's mouth, and there were some black marks there, out of which some dark red blood was seeping out, as if that area had been corroded by something.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he swept a sleeve through the air to send a burst of azure light flying into the Pig Dolphin Beast's body, and the injuries on its mouth quickly began to heal.

An elated look appeared in the Pig Dolphin Beast's eyes, and it oinked at Han Li while wagging its tail from side to side, as if it were trying to suck up to him.

Han Li paid no further heed to the beast as he bent down to pick up the black object on the ground.

It was a fist-sized black rock that was giving off faint black light, and even though it was already nighttime, the black light emanating from the object was still very much visible, seemingly able to devour all of the light around it.

Han Li's brows suddenly furrowed slightly as a burst of sharp pain shot through the fingers of his hand that were in contact with the rock. Immediately thereafter, a semi-transparent membrane appeared over his hand.

The black light emanating from the rock seemed to possess some type of corrosive power that was too much even for his current physical body to bear.

After inspecting the rock for a moment, Han Li injected his spiritual sense into it, upon which a hint of surprise quickly flashed through his eyes.

The rock contained a very special type of power that wasn't any law power, but it was also very profound, and he couldn't tell exactly what it was.

"Are you giving this to me?" Han Li asked.

The Pig Dolphin Beast immediately nodded in response.

"This is a very interesting rock. Where did you get it from?" Han Li asked.

The Pig Dolphin Beast turned to the distance and opened its mouth to say something, but all it could do was oink, and an agitated look instantly appeared in its eyes.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he released a burst of azure light from his fingertip into the Pig Dolphin Beast's throat.

In order for demon beasts to speak, they first had to refine a certain throat bone.

This Pig Dolphin Beast possessed a decent cultivation base, but it was still yet to refine that throat bone.

The azure light flashed through the beast's throat for a moment before quickly dissipating, and an ecstatic look appeared in the Pig Dolphin Beast's eyes as it began to speak in a very inarticulate fashion.

"Senior... Er..."

"Alright, can you tell me where you got this rock from now?" Han Li asked.

"Yes... This rock... Many years ago... I... Er... With my parents from elsewhere... While moving here... Er... Obtained from near an island..." the Pig Dolphin Beast stuttered in response.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this. "Do you still recall which island it was?"

"It's been too long... I was too young at the time... So I don't remember..." the Pig Dolphin Beast replied, and its speech was gradually becoming more fluent.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air upon hearing this, and a ball of seawater instantly rose up before forming a screen of water that depicted a detailed map of the Black Wind Sea.

"Can you recall roughly where it was on this map?" he asked.

The Pig Dolphin Beast stared at the map for a long time, then pointed its snout on a certain spot as it said in an uncertain voice, "I think it may have been here."

Han Li cast his gaze toward that spot on the map, and a hint of surprise appeared on his face.

As it turned out, this was a place that he had once been to. It was none other than Red Moon Island, the island on which he had carried out his first Transient Guild mission.

"So that's where you found it," Han Li murmured to himself.

"Maybe, I'm not sure," the Pig Dolphin Beast said with an uneasy expression.

"It's alright, I know it might be hard for you to remember. By the way, do you have any more of these rocks?" Han Li asked.

Chapter 359: Response

"No, I only have this one. I was going to keep it and try and figure out what it was, but it's clearly beyond my ability to comprehend, so I thought it would be best to give it to you, Senior," the Pig Dolphin Beast said as it lowered its large head in a fawning display.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he flicked another pill through the air, and the Pig Dolphin Beast immediately opened its mouth to swallow the pill with an ecstatic expression.

A burst of light flashed over its body once again, and its aura swelled even further.

"Go on. Make sure you don't speak a single word of this to anyone," Han Li said.

The Pig Dolphin Beast hurriedly nodded in response, then rushed back into the sea before swimming away.

Han Li watched for a moment as the beast departed, then flipped a hand over to produce a red jade box.

This box was crafted from a type of special warm jade, and it was giving off a warm and soothing aura.

He placed the black rock into the box, and after observing for a moment to ensure that the box wasn't affected by the black light emanating from the rock, he stowed the box away, then withdrew the True Extreme Film over his hand before returning to his cave abode.

Instead of returning to his secret chamber, he arrived in the section of his medicine garden where the primary bean had been planted.

He had been focused entirely on cultivation these past few decades, so he didn't have the spare time or attention to manifest time crystals. Due to the fact that he already had a sufficient supply of Myriad Axis Pill, he instructed his giant ape puppet to use all of the Heaven Controlling Vial's spirit liquid to water the primary bean.

Upon arriving in that section of the medicine garden, Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he discovered that the primary bean had already sprouted, and a thin green seedling had poked its way out of the soil.

Even though it was only a tiny seedling, it was giving off a vast aura of vitality.

He carefully observed the seedling for a moment to find that just like before, there were some faint golden patterns on its two leaves.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this.

Having already grown a batch of Dao Warriors, he had gained some experience and wasn't as clueless as he had once been.

The most difficult and time-consuming part of the Dao Warrior nurturing process was getting the primary bean to sprout.

Once the primary bean sprouted, half of the work had already been done, and barring any mishaps, he would be able to quickly obtain another batch of Dao Warriors.

With that in mind, Han Li observed the seedling for a moment longer before leaving the medicine garden and returning to his secret chamber.

After rounding a corner, he cast his gaze toward another secret chamber.

Daoist Xie had already been in seclusion for several centuries in there, yet he still wasn't displaying any signs of coming out, and it was unclear what he was doing in there.

Han Li withdrew his gaze before entering his secret chamber and sitting down with his legs crossed. After that, he put on his Transient Guild mask, then activated all of the restrictions in the secret chamber before checking on his Dewform Herb acquisition mission, but there had still been no responses.

This wasn't a surprise to him, and after heaving a faint sigh, he released two more missions, one of which was to acquire the complete Great Universe Origin Arts, while the other was to appraise the black rock that he had just obtained.

For some reason, he felt like the rock was something quite special.

After doing all of that, he meditated momentarily before summoning his giant ape puppet to his side and taking the Heaven Controlling Vial from it.

There was already a drop of green spirit liquid swirling around in the vial, and he set the vial down in front of himself before making a hand seal.

The Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light, and all of the Tim Dao Runes on its surface were flashing incessantly while giving off time law power fluctuations.

He made a hand seal, and the Mantra Treasured Axis instantly flew up before descending in front of him.

At this point, the number of Time Dao Runes on the axis had reached 130.

Back when he was still at the mid-True Immortal, the number of Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis seemed to have hit an upper limit at 108.

However, now that he had reached the late-True Immortal Stage, the number of Time Dao Runes on the axis had begun increasing again.

In that case...

Han Li picked up the Heaven Controlling Vial before injecting his immortal spiritual power into it.

All of the world's origin qi around the cave abode instantly began to churn violently, forming a massive vortex that drew in countless translucent threads formed by the world's origin qi.

Gusts of fierce wind blew over the surface of the sea, raising massive waves, and this astonishing phenomenon lasted three days before fading.

Inside his cave abode, Han Li was holding a time crystal with a hint of weariness on his face.

With his current immortal spiritual power reserves, it was already far less taxing than before to manifest time crystals.

After resting for a brief moment, he made a hand seal, and the Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

He then began to chant an incantation, the Mantra Treasured Axis began to revolve, while the Time Dao Runes on its surface radiated dazzling golden light.

A ball of resplendent golden light appeared at the center of the axis, and it quickly transformed into a vertical golden eye that cast its gaze toward the time crystals in Han Li's hand.

A faint crack rang out as the crystal shattered, and the golden thread within flew out before shooting into the vertical golden eye.

Han Li shuddered as if he had been dealt a heavy blow, and the golden light radiating from the Mantra Treasured Axis instantly became even brighter.

Moments later, a ball of dazzling white light emerged on the axis, then transformed into a semi-transparent Time Dao Rune, a very encouraging sight for Han Li.

Just as he had anticipated, more Time Dao Runes could now be added to the Mantra Treasured Axis.

He withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis, then handed the Heaven Controlling Vial to the giant ape puppet so that it could continue to produce more spirit liquid.

The more Time Dao Runes the axis had, the more powerful it would become.

……

Over two decades flew by in the blink of an eye.

Inside his cave abode, Han Li's entire body was radiating dazzling golden light, while the Mantra Treasured Axis was rapidly revolving behind him, giving waves of golden ripples that illuminated the entire cave abode a bright golden color.

The axis was riddled with rings upon rings of Time Dao Runes, which totaled 360.

During these past years, he had been constantly using time crystals to add more Time Dao Runes to the axis, yet upon reaching 360, the Mantra Treasured Axis seemed to have reached its upper limit once again, making it impossible to add more.

Han Li made a hand seal, and countless rings of golden ripples emerged before spreading outward in all directions.

These golden ripples were far brighter than before, and everything enshrouded within them came to a complete standstill.

The air and the world's origin qi had all stopped flowing, as if they had been frozen in place.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this.

The time-slowing effect of the Mantra Treasured Axis had become significantly more powerful once again, and by his estimates, time had been slowed down by a factor of roughly 1:3,000.

He swept a sleeve through the air, and the Mantra Treasured Axis disintegrated into specks of golden light that vanished back into his body.

With the increased number of Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis, it was also becoming more taxing to use, and even with his late-True Immortal Stage immortal spiritual power, maintaining it was no easy task.

Han Li gently exhaled as he sat down with his legs crossed.

Not only had the increase in the number of Time Dao Runes enhanced the power of the Mantra Treasured Axis, the power of time imbued within it had also increased significantly, and whenever he used the axis, it would release an enormous amount of time law powers.

Given the abundance of time law powers in the Mantra Treasured Axis, perhaps he would be able to glean the laws of time without having to rely on a dao pill.

With that in mind, he promptly devoured a recovery pill before closing his eyes again.

Close to half a day later.

The space within Han Li's secret chamber suddenly began to shudder, and even through all of the restrictions, one could sense formidable time power fluctuations emanating out from within.

Right at this moment, golden light flashed from the stone door of Daoist Xie's secret chamber, and the door slowly opened.

Daoist Xie slowly emerged from within with its entire body enveloped by countless thin arcs of golden lightning, making it appear as if he were wearing a veil of golden lightning.

Beneath the veil of lightning, its body was looking rather indistinct, as if it could vanish into thin air at any moment.

Upon emerging seclusion, its gaze quickly fell upon Han Li's secret chamber, and after standing there momentarily, it turned around and made its way back into its own secret chamber.

Several days later, the phenomenon taking place in Han Li's secret chamber finally subsided.

Inside the secret chamber, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed. His robes were rather tattered, and there were traces of blood all over his body, while his complexion was also extremely pale.

Just as like his previous few attempts, this one had also concluded in failure.

It seemed that there was some type of force that was preventing him from gleaning the laws of time.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he made a hand seal, and a burst of azure light surged over his body, upon which all of the gashes instantly healed.

He then changed into a brand new robe before taking a pill, and only after closing his eyes to meditate for another half a day did his complexion gradually return to normal.

Han Li opened his eyes and cast his gaze directly forward, and after a prolonged silence, he heaved a faint sigh.

It seemed that it was truly going to be impossible to master the laws of time without the help of a dao pill.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to produce his Transient Guild mask, which he promptly put on before directing his attention to the missions section.

A hint of elation immediately appeared on his face, only to be quickly replaced by disappointment.

As it turned out, there had been a response to one of his missions, but it was the black rock appraisal mission rather than the Dewform Herb acquisition mission.

Despite his disappointment, Han Li still cast an incantation seal onto the mission.

It wasn't the mission that he was most hoping for a response in, but he was also quite curious about that black rock, nonetheless.

The text of the mission began to gently pulse while fluctuating in brightness, and around 15 minutes later, the text released a beam of azure light, projecting it into the secret chamber.

A figure wearing a crimson dragon mask slowly took shape, and the number "3" was engraved onto their mask.

Han Li faltered slightly at the sight of this figure, but his expression was concealed behind his own Transient Mask.

This was the mask that belonged to none other than Wyrm 3.

Chapter 360: Full Collection

"Greetings, Fellow Daoist," the masked figure said as they clasped their fist in a salute, and judging from their voice, this was indeed Wyrm 3.

However, Han LI had never heard Wyrm 3 speak so politely to anyone, and he was rather befuddled by this, but he naturally didn't display his befuddlement outwardly, and he returned the salute before asking, "You've taken on my mission, so you must know what this object is, right?"

At this moment, he was wearing the mask of Raccoon 11, and he had also altered his voice, so he wasn't worried that Wyrm 3 would be able to identify him.

"Of course. However, prior to that, I have a question: are you in the Black Wind Sea at the moment, Fellow Daoist?" Wyrm 3 asked, seemingly on a completely unrelated note.

A hint of wariness welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this, and he didn't reply.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist. Even the same type of ore can display certain differences depending on where they came from, and that's why I'm asking," Wyrm 3 said with a smile.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then nodded in confirmation. "I am indeed in the Black Wind Sea at the moment."

"I see. In that case, I can tell you that the rock is called Hard Ink Crystal, and I once saw it in the Black Wind Sea many years ago. The material is so hard that even direct attacks from Acquired Immortal Treasures aren't able to destroy it. On top of that, it contains a special type of power that's extremely corrosive, making it an exceptional material for refining yin-attribute immortal treasures.

“If some of this material were incorporated into an existing yin-attribute immortal treasure, not only would that immortal treasure attain corrosive properties, it would also become far sturdier as well. If you offer this rock to cultivators using yin-attribute cultivation arts, I'm sure they'd be willing to exchange everything in their possession for it," Wyrm 3 explained with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response. "Thank you for such a detailed explanation. I'll issue you the compensation right away."

It was rather surprising to him that this was such a valuable object.

"Before that, there's something else I'd like to ask you, Fellow Daoist," Wyrm 3 suddenly said.

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"Where did you obtain this Hard Ink Crystal from, Fellow Daoist?" Wyrm 3 asked in a direct and straightforward manner.

"Why are you asking me this?" Han Li asked in a slightly surprised manner.

"Truth be told, this is a treasure that I've been looking for for a very long time, but I need quite a large quantity of it. If you can tell me where you obtained this piece from, I can waive the compensation for this mission and give you substantial compensation to boot," Wyrm 3 said in an earnest voice as they cupped their fist in another salute toward Han Li.

"There's no need for that. The origins of this object concern some private matters of mine that I don't wish to disclose, so I'll still issue you the mission compensation as agreed," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

Despite the earnest tone of Wyrm 3's voice, he could tell that they weren't telling the truth. At the very least, they were omitting something important.

"Hold on a second. This is an extremely important matter to me, so please lend me your assistance, Fellow Daoist. I'm willing to pay 300 Immortal Origin Stones for this piece of information," Wyrm 3 hurriedly interjected.

Han Li was quite surprised to hear this.

No matter how precious this material was, surely 300 Immortal Origin Stones was too much to be paying just for some information on its whereabouts.

This made him even more convinced that Wyrm 3 was withholding some important information.

"My apologies, but I cannot disclose this information, so please don't pursue this matter any further. I still have some other errands to attend to, so let's end things here," Han Li refused once again with a shake of his head, and as he did so, he began to make a hand seal to conclude this communication.

All he wanted was to cultivate in peace at the moment, and he certainly didn't want to get swept up into any trouble just for some Immortal Origin Stones.

"Please wait, Fellow Daoist," Wyrm 3 hurriedly said in an urgent voice. "I noticed that you had released a mission searching for a Dewform Herb as well. I just so happen to have one in my possession, and I'm willing to exchange it for the whereabouts of the Hard Ink Crystal."

"You have a Dewform Herb?" Han Li asked as a hint of surprise and elation appeared in his eyes.

Wyrm 3 was slightly reassured by Han Li's reaction, and they replied with a smile, "I do, and it's over 100,000 years old, so it should be ready for you to use right away."

Han Li lowered his head in silence, seemingly still rather hesitant.

"Of course, the Dewform Herb is a precious spirit plant, but it's certainly no top-tier treasure, so I'll throw in an additional 200 Immortal Origin Stones. How about that?" Wyrm 3 asked, raising the stakes once again.

Han Li raised his head with a surprised expression upon hearing this.

This Hard Ink Crystal was only something that he had obtained by chance, and he had only turned down Wyrm 3 as he didn't want to attract any potential trouble. In truth, he had already decided to agree to exchange the information for a Dewform Herb, and he was only considering some matters related to dao pill refinement just now, but his silence seemed to have been misinterpreted.

"Given the generosity you've displayed, it would be rude of me to continue to refuse," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist."

Wyrm 3 was ecstatic to hear this, and they made a string of hand seals, upon which countless azure runes instantly appeared on the azure light screen in front of Han Li to form a teleportation array.

A storage ring then appeared within the array, and Han Li picked up the ring without any hesitation before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

Instead of immediately inspecting the contents of the storage ring, he carefully inspected the entire storage ring, and only after verifying that it hadn't been tampered with in any way did he turn his attention to its contents, namely a small pile of Immortal Origin Stones and an azure jade box, which was around a foot in length and had several azure talismans adhered to it.

Han Li pulled the jade box out of the storage ring, and it was giving off a gentle azure luster.

He immediately identified the box to have been crafted from Azure Spirit Cream Jade, which was a type of premium spirit jade that was ideal for storing all types of spirit plants.

Han Li gently removed the talismans from the box before lifting its lid, and he was greeted by the sight of an azure spirit plant with long and thin leaves that were as green as jade, but its roots were white in color.

There were white spots that resembled beads of dew on the spirit plant's leaves, and it didn't appear all that remarkable, but it was giving off powerful spiritual qi fluctuations.

A cloud of white mist quickly appeared in the air around it, and within the mist were numerous transparent water droplets.

This was none other than the Dewform Herb that he had been searching extensively for, and just as Wyrm 3 claimed, it appeared to have been over 100,000 years of age.

Furthermore, its roots were completely unharmed, so he could continue to nurture it.

Han Li replaced the lid on the jade box before stowing it away, then said, "The answer to your question is very simple: I picked up the Hard Ink Crystal somewhere in the Black Wind Sea by chance."

Wyrm 3's eyes immediately lit up as they asked, "Oh? Do you still recall where it was that you picked it up from?"

"Let me think... If my memory is correct, then it was somewhere near a place called Red Moon Island," Han Li replied.

"Red Moon Island..."

Wyrm 3 faltered slightly upon hearing this.

"Is there a problem, Fellow Daoist?" Han Li asked.

"No, it's just that I've been there once, and it's quite a bleak and desolate island, so I didn't think that something like Hard Ink Crystals could be found near it," Wyrm 3 replied.

"I see. After picking up this piece of Hard Ink Crystal at the time, I searched the nearby area, but didn't find any more, so the chances of you finding more of this material there are most likely rather slim. In any case, I wish you luck," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist," Wyrm 3 replied as they cupped their fist in a salute.

The two of them chatted for a brief while longer before concluding the communication.

Han Li took off his mask, then rose to his feet with a contemplative look on his face.

Judging from Wyrm 3's words and actions just now, there was definitely some information that they were withholding.

With that in mind, Han Li thought back to the mission that he had carried out on Red Moon Island, trying to think if there was anything special about the island, but he then quickly rid himself of that train of thought, deeming it as nothing more than a waste of time.

After that, he cast an incantation seal to open the door of his secret chamber, then made his way to his medicine garden.

While it was true that he did now have a Dewform Herb of sufficient age, a single one wasn't very much to work with.

It was almost certain that he was going to be failing many times in his attempt to refine a dao pill, so he had to prepare more batches of ingredients.

At this point, he had already nurtured many batches of all of the other ingredients, and the Dewform Herb was the only one that he had been missing.

He arrived in a corner of his medicine garden, then quickly cleared a new plot of soil before setting up some restrictions around it.

After that, he carefully planted the Dewform Herb there, and only after toiling away for close to half a day did he finally step back to examine his handiwork.

A faint smile appeared on his face at the sight of the planted Dewform Herb, and he issued an instruction to the giant ape puppet to use all of the Heaven Controlling Vial spirit liquid to water this plant, to which the puppet nodded stiffly in response.

After that, Han Li took another glance at the Dewform Herb before leaving the medicine garden.

He had only just emerged from the garden when a surprised look appeared on his face.

As it turned out, Daoist Xie was standing not far away.

"When did you come out of seclusion, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

"Not too long ago. I saw that you were cultivating in your secret chamber, so I didn't go to disturb you," Daoist Xie replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then asked, "It looks like your seclusion was quite successful."

"I recalled a couple of secret techniques, and I've mastered them to a decent extent over the past few centuries," Daoist Xie replied.

"Congratulations, Brother Xie," Han Li said with a smile.

"It's all thanks to the Immortal Origin Stones that you provided me with. Speaking of those, I've used them all up during my seclusion," Daoist Xie said.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

He had given Daoist Xie over 1,000 Immortal Origin Stones last time, and if it weren't for the fact that he profited immensely from killing Tao Yu, he wasn't going to be able to afford Daoist Xie's upkeep.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a storage tool, then handed it to Daoist Xie as he said, "There are 1,000 Immortal Origin Stones in here. Make sure to use them sparingly as it's not so easy to get more Immortal Origin Stones here in the Black Wind Sea."

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then made its way back into the secret chamber before going back into seclusion.

Moments later, a burst of lightning power fluctuations began to emanate out of the secret chamber even through the restrictions inside.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face once again upon seeing this, and he returned to his own secret chamber as well.

Chapter 361: Pill Tribulation

At this moment, countless kilometers away from Han Li's cave abode, a gray-robed figure with a crimson dragon mask on their face was seated with their legs crossed in a dark underground space with.

This person was none other than Wyrm 3, who had just made that exchange with Han Li.

After remaining on the spot for a while longer, Wyrm 3 suddenly stood up, then turned and strode down one of the several passageways connected to this space.

After walking through the pitch-black underground passageway for an indeterminate period of time, Wyrm 3 arrived in an open space in the form of a cave that was several hundred feet in size, at the end of which was a gray stone door behind a faint silver light barrier.

Wyrm 3 made a hand seal while chanting an incantation, and the silver light barrier shuddered before parting down the center.

Wyrm 3 opened the door to reveal a circular secret chamber that was over 200 feet in size, but was completely empty aside from a stone table and a stone chair.

Seated atop the stone chair was an elderly man in a black cloak who was sipping on a cup of spirit tea.

The tea was crimson in color and was also giving off a strong bloody odor.

The elderly man had a hooked nose that resembled the beak of an eagle, and there was a cold gleam in his golden eyes.

Wyrm 3 took a glance at the teacup that the elderly man was holding, and a hint of disgust flashed through their eyes, only to be immediately concealed.

"Did you find out where he got it from?" the elderly man asked as he set down his teacup.

His voice was extremely ghastly to listen to, like the sound of two pieces of rusty metal scraping together.

Wyrm 3 sat down beside the elderly man, then replied, "He found it near Red Moon Island."

"Red Moon Island? Didn't you already conduct a search there before?" the elderly man asked with a hint of surprise on his face.

"I visited Red Moon Island last time under the guise of carrying out a Transient Guild mission, but there's no guarantee that my plan wasn't exposed in advance, so perhaps they took some measures to conceal things at the time," Wyrm 3 replied.

The elderly man offered no response to this, and he began tapping a finger absentmindedly against the table with a contemplative look on his face.

Wyrm 3 also remained silent, and some time later, the elderly man broke the silence as he asked, "What do you think of this? Do you think it's another red herring from Black Wind Island?"

"I don't think so. If Black Wind Island is behind this, I don't think they would've arranged for the location to be Red Moon Island again," Wyrm 3 replied.

"I suppose that's true. In that case, let's search the entire area around Red Moon Island again, then proceed according to the original plan," the elderly man said, to which Wyrm 3 nodded in response.

The elderly man rose to his feet before departing, and only after he had left the room did Wyrm 3 stand up before removing their mask and making their way outside.

As they walked, a murky layer of light rose up over their body before quickly fading away, and they had transformed into a woman with an exceptional figure, while her gray robe had also turned into a red dress that drifted around her like a fiery red cloud.

Before long, she had faded into the darkness once again.

……

Around a dozen more years flew by in the blink of an eye.

Inside his medicine garden, Han Li carefully uprooted a Dewform Herb that was around a foot tall, then placed it in a jade box.

This was already the third Dewform Herb that he had matured.

After stowing the jade box away, Han Li made his way out of the medicine garden, but instead of heading to his secret chamber, he exited his cave abode altogether.

Shortly thereafter, he appeared in the sky above the island amid a flash of azure light, then flipped a hand over to produce several array plates of different colors.

He then began to chant an incantation, and the array plates began to glow brightly before flying downward as several streaks of light.

The space around the cave abode suddenly began to flash with spiritual light as a thick yellow light barrier emerged, releasing a vast expanse of yellow mist that completely inundated the entire cave abode.

At the same time, boundless blue light rose up from the sea around the island to form a hemispherical blue light barrier that encompassed the entire island with flashing runes of different sizes on its surface.

Han Li continued to chant his incantation, releasing several streaks of blue light that vanished into the light barrier.

A series of ripples immediately began to surge over the blue light barrier, following which the entire light barrier abruptly vanished along with the island beneath it, making it appear as if this were just a stretch of empty ocean.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this.

He had personally altered these restrictions, and even if a late-True Immortal cultivator were to arrive here, they wouldn't have been able to break these restrictions in a short time.

The outermost concealment restriction was one that he had learned from a scripture in Tao Yu's storage tool, and it was even more profound, able to fool the spiritual sense of even early-Golden Immortal cultivators.

After doing all of that, Han Li turned and flew away into the distance as a streak of azure light.

Several days later, he drew to a halt above a certain region of the sea.

This place was just as barren and deserted as the area where he had chosen to construct his temporary cave abode, except the cave abode was situated in the northwestern region of the Black Wind Sea, while this was the southwest.

He released his spiritual sense, then flew toward a certain direction before descending onto an island moments later.

The island wasn't very large, only several dozen kilometers in size, and it was home to a gray mountain. Aside from that, the entire mountain was covered in soil and gray rocks, but barely any plants, presenting a rather bleak sight to behold.

Han Li swept his gaze over the island before flicking his fingers through the air to release streaks of sword qi that struck the gray mountain halfway up.

Countless rocks came tumbling down like rain, and before long, a crude cave abode had taken shape.

Han Li flew into the cave abode, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a flurry of several hundred array flags.

After that, he chanted an incantation before pointing at the array flags, and they instantly transformed into balls of light of different colors that vanished in a flash into different parts of the cave abode.

Several light barriers then quickly appeared to encompass the entire island before vanishing into thin air as well.

With all of the restrictions set up, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed, then swept a sleeve through the air once again to release a streak of golden light that transformed into Daoist Xie.

"Brother Xie, it's very unlikely that anyone will come here, but if someone tries to barge into this place while I'm in seclusion, then please do your best to keep them at bay," Han Li said.

"Rest assured, unless any beings far above the Golden Immortal Stage come here, I'll be sure to keep them out of your way," Daoist Xie replied with a nod, then vanished into thin air amid a flash of golden lightning.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, he was quite surprised to discover that his spiritual sense was no longer able to detect Daoist Xie's location.

He immediately activated his Spirit Refinement Technique to enhance his spiritual sense, and only then was he able to detect a very faint trace of lightning fluctuations nearby.

If it weren't for his enormous spiritual sense and the enhancement effects of his Spirit Refinement Technique, there was no way that he would've been able to detect these faint lightning fluctuations.

Despite his surprise, Han Li quickly shook his head and set the matter aside.

He had gone out of his way to construct a new cave abode and set up so many restrictions here as he was about to begin refining a dao pill.

According to the scriptures, a pill tribulation could arise in the instant that a dao pill took shape.

The scriptures stated that pill tribulations arose due to the fact that all dao pills contained the purest of law powers, to the point that they transcended the natural laws of the realm. As a result, the power of the realm would automatically reject dao pills, sending down pill tribulations to prevent dao pills from taking shape.

It was said that pill tribulations were extremely formidable, even more so than most lightning tribulations, and even though this place was very secluded, there was still no guarantee that such a massive spectacle wouldn't attract any unwelcome guests.

The problem with his former cave abode was that moving the medicine garden was quite a chore, and that was why he had decided to come here. Even if someone were to discover him here, with Daoist Xie buying him time, he would be able to make a getaway.

With that in mind, Han Li took a deep breath before closing his eyes to meditate.

Only after three days and three nights had passed by did he reopen his eyes, following which he swept a sleeve through the air to produce a silver cauldron.

A streak of silver light then shot out of his other sleeve and landed beneath the cauldron, transforming into a ball of silver flames that contained a tiny fiery silver figure.

After that, he swept his sleeves through the air in succession to summon various ingredients that almost took up the entire secret chamber.

At the same time, he was running through the dao pill refinement process in his mind, even though he had already envisioned the process countless times.

After making sure that he was fully prepared, he cast an incantation seal through the air, and the silver flame instantly reared up, while the temperature in the cauldron above it quickly began to rise.

All of a sudden, a white crystal emerged at Han Li's behest before flying into the cauldron.

It was none other than a time crystal, and it gradually began to melt in the face of the sweltering heat inside the cauldron.

The golden thread within the crystal was becoming brighter while giving off bursts of time law power fluctuations, and at the same time, Han Li drew a jade box into his grasp, one that contained a Heavenmade Ginseng Root.

A burst of azure light emerged over his other hand before enveloping the Heavenmade Ginseng Root, and the azure light then took on the form of two large hands that began to gently crush the ginseng root.

The Heavenmade Ginseng Root was an extremely rare spirit plant, but it wasn't very hard at all, and it was instantly crushed to a pulp, releasing a large volume of white spirit liquid.

Han Li pointed a finger forward to release a burst of azure light that caught the spirit liquid, then carefully transported it into the cauldron.

The spirit liquid immediately began to boil, and wisps of white mist rose up from it.

There was a look of concentration on Han Li's face as he controlled the silver flame, and before long, the white spirit liquid had transformed into a small ball of white gooey substance that enveloped the time crystal.

Han Li immediately drew another ingredient over to himself upon seeing this, and this time, it was a small box of silver powder that looked as if it were some type of crushed bone.

He raised a hand to release a burst of azure light that enveloped the bone powder, then transported into the cauldron as well.

At the same time, his other hand was making a constant series of hand seals to keep the silver flame beneath the cauldron in check.

The silver bone powder quickly melted as well, forming a ball of silver liquid that fused as one with the gooey white substance, immediately following which Han Li picked up another ingredient before transferring it into the cauldron.

In the blink of an eye, over half a day had passed by, and most of the ingredients in the secret chamber had already been transferred into the cauldron.

At this moment, there was a longan-sized white pill inside the cauldron, and its surface was rather rough and bumpy.

The white pill was gently revolving while being heated by the silver flame beneath the cauldron, and it was giving off wisps of white spiritual qi.

Chapter 362: Time Reversal Revision

In front of the pill cauldron, sweat had already begun to bead up on Han Li's forehead, and his breathing was also slightly jagged.

He had already tried to mentally prepare himself for the level of difficulty of dao pill refinement, but only when putting the process into practice did he realize just how drastically he had underestimated the process.

Dao pill refinement was completely different from that of normal pill refinement.

There were countless different pill recipes out there, but almost all of them involved refining all of the ingredients before gathering them together to condense into a pill.

In contrast, the ingredient that contained the law power was the core of everything in a dao pill. Hence, during the refinement process, he had to refine the ingredients while constantly fusing them with the material that contained the law power, resulting in a snowball process. Essentially, the ingredient refinement and pill condensing processes had to take place in unison, and that resulted in a massive spike in difficulty.

To further compound his woes, he also had to simultaneously control the fire while balancing out the medicinal properties of all of the ingredients.

In particular, the time law powers within the time crystal had to form some type of balance with all of the other ingredients in order to facilitate perfect fusion, and that only further increased the difficulty of the pill refinement process.

Han Li felt as if he were controlling an enormous army, trying to instruct them to adopt an extremely complex formation, but none of the soldiers in the army were under his control, and on top of that, they were occasionally clashing against one another.

He had to balance out all of the conflicts while guiding everyone into the right formation, and if it weren't for the fact that he had made significant strides in his pill refinement mastery of late, he would've already been completely worn out by now.

Even so, at this point, he was gradually beginning to feel the strain, but there were many ingredients that were still yet to be added to the cauldron, and with the addition of those ingredients, things were only going to become even more difficult to control.

Due to the fact that dao pills contained law powers, they couldn't come into contact with any other law powers prior to the completion of the refinement process. Otherwise, some unforeseen change would take place in the pill, resulting in a failure in the pill refinement.

Hence, Han Li was unable to use his Mantra Treasured Axis to assist him, and he could only rely on his pill refinement skills.

He took a deep breath, then swept a sleeve through the air once again, sending another ingredient tumbling into the cauldron.

As time passed, a few more ingredients were transferred into the cauldron, and at this point, Han Li's breathing had become extremely labored, and his eyes had become bloodshot, while an unnatural flush had appeared on his cheeks.

He took a deep breath as he released a burst of azure light to envelop another ingredient, this time a vial of green spirit liquid, then tipped it into the cauldron as well.

The green liquid swirled around in the cauldron momentarily before fusing into the white pill, which was already beginning to take shape.

A layer of green light appeared over the white pill, but it then slowly faded, and right as it was about to completely vanish, the pill abruptly shuddered as lights of different colors appeared on its surface, clashing erratically with one another.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he was just about to do something, but it was already too late.

A dull thud rang out from within the white pill, following which a crack appeared on its surface.

In the next instant, all of the light radiating from the pill faded, and the spiritual qi permeating throughout the surrounding area also abruptly vanished.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and everything instantly returned to normal, as if Han Li had only been refining a normal pill up to this point rather than a dao pill.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh as he released an incantation seal, and all of the silver flames beneath the cauldron instantly surged back to him to form a fiery silver figure that vanished into his body.

He then made a beckoning motion, and the remnants of the pill flew out of the cauldron before flying onto the palm of his hand.

He held the pill up close to his eye for a thorough inspection, and the slight frustration in his heart gradually subsided.

He was already mentally prepared for his first dao pill refinement attempt to conclude in failure, particularly considering this was going to be a dao pill that contained one of the three paramount laws.

With that in mind, a faint smile appeared on his face.

This failed pill may have been useless to other pill refinement masters, but it was extremely useful to him.

He made a hand seal, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

All of the 360 Time Dao Runes on its surface were giving off dazzling golden light, and the Eye of Truth at its center slowly opened to reveal the eyeball inside.

A beam of radiant golden light shot out of the eyeball, and countless golden runes appeared on the surface of the eye, much like a night sky full of golden stars.

With the emergence of these runes, the golden light released by the Eye of Truth began to flicker incessantly, creating a chaotic kaleidoscope-like effect.

With 360 Time Dao Runes on the Mantran Treasured Axis, the aura and observative powers had both been significantly enhanced.

Han Li closed his eyes so that he could see the world through the lens of the Eye of Truth, and he was able to see through teh restrictions set up in his cave abode with ease.

Not only that, but he was even able to clearly see the flow of spiritual power on the restrictions.

Unfortunately, he only had a few restrictions set up at the moment, and that was nowhere near enough to test the true limits of the Eye of Truth's observative powers.

There were definitely going to be more opportunities to test out the observative powers of the Eye of Truth in the future, but this wasn't the time to be doing such a thing, so he returned to the task at hand, focusing its gaze on the failed pill in his hand.

The beam of golden light shooting out of the Eye of Truth instantly fell upon the pill, which immediately began to glow with dazzling golden radiance while giving off bursts of time power fluctuations.

In the next instant, the pill began to revolve in mid-air, and a burst of green spirit liquid abruptly surged out of it.

At the same time, lights of different colors were flashing from the pill, and it was also displaying various other minute changes.

Essentially, the pill refinement process was being played out in reverse right in front of Han Li's eyes, allowing him to clearly observe the entire process.

One of the main things that had given Han Li the confidence to attempt dao pill refinement was none other than this time reversal ability of his Eye of Truth.

A layer of blue light surfaced in his eyes as he stared intently at the failed pill, latching onto every single detail.

All of a sudden, he spotted the misstep that had resulted in the pill's detonation.

The green liquid had been completely extracted out of the pill, and all of the lights of different colors on the pill also faded, restoring it to the state before the green liquid was added.

The scene continued to unfold, and a layer of white light emerged over the pill, following which some white powder was extracted out of it.

Once again, lights of different colors emerged over the pill alongside various minute changes.

Han Li hadn't made a mistake in this step, but he was still eager to see it again so that he could glean some insight and experience.

Thus, more and more ingredients continued to fly out of the pill one after another, and after reviewing the entire process, Han Li had developed a clearer understanding of the dao pill refinement process.

In the end, the pill was restored back to just the time crystal, which was then reverted back into the green liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial, but Han Li was naturally not interested in this part.

Following a few flickers of golden light, the failed pill re-emerged.

Even though Han Li had reached the late-True Immortal Stage, unleashing the Eye of Truth still exhausted most of his immortal spiritual power.

He exhaled as pulled out a pill before swallowing it, then sat down to meditate, digesting the pill while carefully reviewing the dao pill refinement process in his mind once again.

An hour later, he opened his eyes, feeling completely reinvigorated.

However, he didn't immediately begin another attempt at dao pill refinement as it would take another month to manifest a time crystal.

During the rest of the month, Han Li did nothing aside from constantly using his Eye of Truth to review the pill refinement process over and over again.

A month passed by in the blink of an eye, and the Heaven Controlling Vial finally produced a drop of green liquid that was immediately converted into a time crystal by Han Li.

After that, he brought out another batch of ingredients and made his second pill refinement attempt.

Having reviewed the first attempt countless times, Han Li couldn't have been more familiar with the process, and the pill refinement progressed very smoothly, quickly reaching the stage where the green spirit liquid was to be integrated.

He pulled out a vial of green spirit liquid before guiding it into the cauldron, and it quickly shrank down in volume under the sweltering heat.

Han Li raised a hand to release a burst of azure light that enveloped the liquid before integrating it into the pill, and this time, the process was completed without a hitch.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this, then transferred another ingredient into the cauldron.

Perhaps it was due to his extensive revision of his first pill refinement, but this second attempt was progressing very smoothly, and before long, there were only six or seven ingredients left.

However, at this point, a sheen of sweat had appeared on Han Li's forehead, and he seemed to be nearing his limits once again.

He gritted his teeth and braced himself as he transferred a white spirit gel substance into the cauldron, and a flash of white light abruptly appeared, followed by another dull thump, concluding with a charred odor wafting through the air.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he then quickly composed himself.

After resting for a moment with his eyes closed, he retrieved the failed pill from the cauldron, then summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis and began scrutinizing the pill with the Eye of Truth.

A beam of golden light shot into the pill, and the pill refinement process was played out in reverse once again.

Once again, Han Li was able to quickly pinpoint the reason for this failure.

One month later, he repeated the same process, commencing his third pill refinement, and prior to this, he had once again extensively reviewed his previous failure.

The time reversal ability of the Eye of Truth was virtually allowing him to simulate the pill refinement process over and over again, thereby granting him a huge amount of experience.

Just like last time, the pill refinement process progressed very smoothly, and before long, it was yet again time to add the white spirit gel substance into the cauldron.

He had already mastered the key to this step, and he was able to complete it without any trouble.

After that, he transferred another ingredient into the cauldron.

At this point, most of the pill refinement process was already complete, and he should've been very happy to have come so far after just two failures, but his mood was immediately dampened just 15 minutes later.

Another dull thump rang out from within the cauldron, heralding his third dao pill refinement failure.

Chapter 363: Arrival of the Tribulation

Han Li's expression darkened slightly as he withdrew his flame of Flame of Essence with a sweep of his sleeve, then retrieved the failed pill from inside the cauldron.

This time, he hadn't been able to make much improvement, only successfully integrating one more ingredient before failing on the second one.

The closer he came to the conclusion of the pill refinement process, the more difficult it became, and his brows were tightly furrowed.

With the Eye of Truth, he could review the pill refinement process however many times he wanted, so he was certain that he would eventually find success, but the problem was that he had only prepared nine batches of pill refinement ingredients, and there had already been used up, so there were only six left.

He took a deep breath and cast aside that train of thought, then trained his Eye of Truth on the failed pill once again.

A month later, Han Li commenced his fourth pill refinement.

Everything was progressing smoothly, and he quickly reached the stage where he had previously failed.

Thanks to his extensive revision, he was able to complete this step with ease as well, smoothly integrating a piece of golden honey into the pill.

He took a moment to compose himself, then turned to find that there were still five ingredients left.

He gritted his teeth as he transferred the next ingredient into the cauldron, then began making a rapid string of hand seals with a look of intense focus on his face, pushing the limits of his pill refinement abilities.

Inside the cauldron, the pill was revolving on the spot with spiritual light of different colors flashing over its surface.

With each ingredient that was added, Han Li had to regulate the interactions between the new ingredient and the other ingredients that had already been integrated into the pill to reach a new equilibrium. It was like pouring cold water into hot oil while also ensuring that no oil spilled out.

Han Li was doing everything in his power to mediate the clashes between the medicinal power of all of the ingredients in the pill, trying to stabilize everything, but his efforts proved to be futile.

A dull thud rang out, and Han Li's expression instantly darkened once again.

This time, he had failed without being able to integrate even a single additional ingredient.

He sat in silence for a while before retrieving the failed pill and inspecting it through his Eye of Truth.

A month later, the fifth pill refinement began.

Once again, progress was very smooth, but even though he had already exercised the utmost caution when adding in the next ingredient down the line, the process still concluded in failure.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he repeated the same process of revision.

Two or three months passed by in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed in his cave abode, cycling through a rapid string of hand seals.

Faint crackling sounds were ringing out occasionally from within the cauldron, and even though the lid of the cauldron, flashes of spiritual light of different colors could be seen.

There was also a strong medicinal aroma in the air, and this time, all of the ingredients had already been transferred into the cauldron.

During these past few months, progress had remained agonizingly slow despite Han Li's best efforts, and he was only able to successfully integrate one more ingredient each time.

Even though he had managed to gradually overcome one hurdle after another, he had exhausted all of his ingredients, and the pill in the cauldron at this moment contained the final batch.

He had already failed at this stage last time, so if the trend of one additional successful ingredient integration per pill refinement attempt continued, then this would finally be the one where he was met with success.

What he had to worry about right now was the upcoming pill tribulation.

He only had this final batch of ingredients left, and if he couldn't ward off the pill tribulation, then he wasn't going to get another chance for at least the next few centuries.

He still had some seeds and seedlings of things like the Dewform Herb and the Heavenmade Ginseng Root, so all he would have to do would be to mature them using the Heaven Controlling Vial spirit liquid, but the other ingredients that weren't spirit plants weren't going to be so easy to obtain.

They would have to be purchased using Immortal Origin Stones, and some of them were not so easy to come by. In particular, there were several primary ingredients that he had only found in Tao Yu's storage tool, and he had no idea how much time and effort it would've taken to gather them on his own.

Not only was he currently in the Black Wind Sea, it was impossible to purchase those ingredients even from the Transient Guild.

Hence, this was his final chance, and he couldn't afford for anything to go wrong.

With that in mind, Han Li reaffirmed his focus, observing all of the changes taking place in the pill cauldron with his spiritual sense.

At this moment, all of the ingredients in the pill were clashing violently against one another like a chaotic pot of boiling water, and even though he had identified the reason for his previous failure during his extensive revision, he was still having a great deal of trouble keeping everything in check.

Time slowly passed by, and Han Li gradually entered an immersive state of tranquility, as if his heart had transformed into the surface of a still lake.

The rate at which he was making hand seals began to slow down, but all of his movements had become more precise and profound.

Incantation seals were streaming out of his hands into the cauldron, and the originally incredibly complex situation in the cauldron had suddenly become very simple in his eyes, allowing him to control everything with ease.

All of the clashes taking place in the pill began to subside, and the pill refinement process was rapidly nearing its conclusion.

A faint smile appeared on his face, and he could feel that his pill refinement abilities had broken through a bottleneck and reached a whole new level.

He took a deep breath as a serious look reappeared on his face, and he suddenly switched to a different hand seal.

A burst of loud rumbling akin to claps of thunder rang out within the cauldron, but this was due to all of the surging energy inside rather than the detonation of the pill.

The lights of different colors flashing within the cauldron also became brighter and brighter while gradually fusing together to form pure golden light.

Han Li's eyes lit up upon seeing this, and he knew that this was a precursor of the pill's formation.

His hand seals became more urgent, while the golden light within the cauldron became more and more radiant, and the medicinal aroma in the air also became more pronounced.

Right at this moment, the sound ringing out within the cauldron abruptly took a turn, resembling an animalistic roar.

All of a sudden, a loud thump rang out, and a burst of dazzling golden light erupted out of the cauldron, sending its lid flying, while a longan-sized golden pill flew out from within.

Streaks of fiery golden light erupted out of the pill, forming a series of golden halos that spread through the air in all directions.

The pill was giving off a burst of incredibly profound time law fluctuations that approached the Heavenly Dao, and Han Li was ecstatic to see that there were two golden marks on its surface.

Never had he thought that he would be able to refine a second-tier dao pill. Perhaps this was due to the abundance of time law powers in the time crystal, or perhaps it was due to some other factor.

In any case, a second-tier dao pill was going to be far more efficacious than a first-tier one.

Right at this moment, countless specks of golden light suddenly began to appear in the clear blue sky up above, quickly forming a vast expanse of surging golden clouds.

The golden clouds had no end in sight, and it was as if they had taken up the entire sky, illuminating even the sea down below a bright golden color.

Vast law fluctuations were surging out of the golden clouds, while all of the world's origin qi within a radius of close to 100,000 kilometers was churning violently.

The law fluctuations emanating from the golden clouds were so immense that they were detectable even to cultivators close to 1,000,000 kilometers away.

The golden cloud was also churning violently while becoming denser and denser, and before long, it had formed an opaque golden barrier that completely kept out the light of the sun.

The entire sea was illuminated a bright golden color, but there was an incredibly heavy sensation in the air, as if the sky were about to fall.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he sensed what was happening outside.

He had seen records of pill tribulations before, and he hadn't anticipated it to be so formidable.

A burst of loud rumbling rang out within the golden cloud, and a vast golden vortex appeared, rapidly revolving as rays of incredibly bright golden light appeared at its center.

A burst of crushing law fluctuations surged out of the vortex, descending upon the entire cave abode.

Countless cracks began to appear on all of the walls of the cave abode, and all of a sudden, Daoist Xie appeared in the sky above the cave abode amid a flash of golden lightning.

It raised its head to look up at the golden cloud, and a hint of emotion flashed past its wooden face.

Right at this moment, the golden vortex in the sky abruptly brightened, and a beam of piercing golden light surged out from within, hurtling down toward the cave abode below.

The golden light contained countless golden runes that were flashing erratically while giving off formidable time law power fluctuations that were filled with aggressive intent.

Daoist Xie made no effort to stop the beam of golden light, merely standing still on the spot.

Right at this moment, the beam of golden light struck the cave abode before piercing directly into it.

However, the restrictions and walls of the cave abode remained completely unharmed, and the golden light passed right through them as if it had no substance.

Han Li was quite startled by this turn of events.

The pill tribulation had arrived far quicker than he had anticipated.

He hurriedly made a hand seal, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him before releasing countless golden ripples that instantly enveloped the golden dao pill.

At the same time, he opened his mouth to release the Seven Bright Star Rings, which became interconnected with one another to form a single large ring.

The ring released a burst of dazzling starlight to form a light barrier with countless stars flashing on its surface, as if it were a miniature starry sky.

Countless tiny starlight runes were surging over the surface of the light barrier while giving off hints of law fluctuations.

Before Han Li had a chance to do anything else, the beam of golden light came crashing down like lightning upon the starlight barrier, which immediately brightened considerably as it attempted to keep the beam of golden light at bay.

However, the beam of golden light was able to pass through it just as it had the ceiling of the cave abode, and it struck the dao pill with unerring accuracy.

Chapter 364: Final Roll of the Dice

The golden dao pill shuddered violently upon being struck by the beam of golden light, and arcs of lighting were flashing over its surface.

At the same time, the golden light that it was giving off quickly began to dim, and the enormous spiritual energy that it contained was beginning to display signs of dissipating.

Most importantly, the two golden dao marks on its surface were also flashing erratically, looking as if they were about to rise up from the dao pill and fly toward the golden vortex up above.

Han Li's heart immediately sank upon seeing this.

He had already activated his Mantra Treasured Axis's time-slowing effect, but the beam of golden light was completely unaffected, perhaps because it was also imbued with the power of time laws.

His mind was racing as he made a rapid string of hand seals in a desperate attempt to stabilize the dao pill.

At the same time, bursts of time law powers surged out of the Mantra Treasured Axis, enveloping the golden dao marks on the pill to keep them in place.

However, even with his tremendous power, it was very difficult to stabilize the dao pill and keep the dao marks in place, and at this rate, it would only be a matter of time before the dao pill was completely destroyed.

The golden dao pill was trembling incessantly, as was Han Li.

Stabilizing the pill wasn't just a matter of using as much effort as possible. Instead, he had to strike an extremely meticulous balance, so his immense immortal spiritual power wasn't helping him much here.

Right at this moment, the golden cloud in the sky began to churn once again in an even more violent fashion, resembling a turbulent golden sea.

The speed at which the golden vortex was revolving also increased significantly, and more rays of piercing golden light appeared at its center, resembling arcs of pulsing lightning.

In the next instant, a burst of even more suffocating pressure erupted out of the vortex before descending upon Han Li's cave abode.

The entire cave abode shuddered along with the island that it was situated on, and the cracks on the walls of the cave abode widened even further.

An urgent look appeared on Han Li as he sensed what was happening outside, and his Mantra Treasured Axis also began to revolve rapidly at his behest while all of its Time Dao Runes were giving off dazzling golden light.

A vast burst of golden light surged out of the axis, and it was filled with countless golden runes that were giving off intense time law power fluctuations.

This burst of time law power was almost twice as powerful as what it had previously released, and the burst of golden light instantly split up into several dozen streaks at Han Li's behest, with every single one of them forming a flashing thread of golden light, all of which were emanating formidable time law powers.

The dozens of strands of golden light shot forth before wrapping themselves around the golden dao marks on the pill, and the trembling of the dao marks finally subsided a little, while the violently surging spiritual power within the pill also settled down slightly.

However, Han Li didn't dare to grow complacent, and he continued to try and stabilize the pill with all his might.

At the same time, a series of Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew out of his body before forming a circular sword barrier above his head.

Immediately thereafter, his Heavy Water True Axis also appeared, then swelled to over 10 times its original size before also positioning itself above him.

The Heavy Water True Axis was rapidly revolving while producing bursts of loud rumbling, while more treasures continued to fly out of Han Li's body one after another.

There were the silver bell, strange sword, and Integrated Five Extremes Mountain that he had obtained from Tao Yu, as well as those two yin-attribute immortal treasures and all of the other formidable treasures in his collection.

During these past few centuries, he had already completely refined these treasures, granting him complete mastery over them.

With the support of his immense spiritual sense and immortal spiritual power, all of the treasures released layers upon layers of thick light barriers that virtually filled the entire secret chamber.

Han Li had only just completed these preparations when a resounding boom rang out overhead, and a pillar of golden light that was far thicker than the one before came crashing down upon the cave abode.

The entire surrounding space shuddered violently as gusts of fierce wind swept through the area, raising waves that were several hundred feet tall over the surface of the nearby sea.

This pillar of golden light was extremely bright, and it resembled a bolt of lightning, once again passing through the restrictions and ceiling of the cave abode with ease before striking the outermost starlight barrier formed by the Seven Bright Star Rings.

Just like before, the pillar of golden light pierced through the starlight barrier without any trouble, then went on to strike the sword net formed by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The golden pillar of light was struck by countless peerlessly sharp streaks of sword qi, but once again, it remained completely unaffected, passing right through to strike the Heavy Water True Axis, which also posed no resistance.

All of the light barriers in the secret chamber were flashing erratically, but their efforts to keep the pillar of golden light at bay remained completely futile.

However, the pillar of golden light had been slowed down a little, so it appeared that Han Li's efforts weren't completely futile.

Even so, the situation was still quite dire.

He had already done everything in his power, yet the pill tribulation still refused to be stopped.

Up to this point, the dao pill still wasn't even close to reaching a state of stability.

Given how damaging the first pill tribulation had been, if it were struck by this second pill tribulation that was even more formidable, then it would surely be completely destroyed.

Never had he imagined that the realm would reject dao pills so vehemently.

He continued to resist with all his might while the pillar of golden light passed through several more light barriers, and it was slowed down even further in the process.

All of a sudden, Han Li seemed to have noticed something.

The pillar of golden light had seemed to have pierced through the first few layers of light barriers without any trouble, yet he could tell that it had shrunk down a little.

It seemed that this pill tribulation wasn't unstoppable, after all.

With that in mind, Han Li opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence, which split up into several smaller balls before vanishing into the treasures around him.

At the same time, he released all of his immortal spiritual power without any reservation, injecting it into the remaining treasures.

At this point, he had no choice but to make one final roll of the dice.

All of the treasures lit up significantly while giving off even more formidable law power fluctuations, while the pillar of golden light continued to descend.

One light barrier after another was pierced through as the pillar of golden light rapidly approached the dao pill, and Han Li's expression darkened even further.

The pill tribulation had been weakened up to this point, but the effects were still too minimal.

Right at this moment, the pillar of golden light passed through the black flag immortal treasure, then began descending toward the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

At this point, there weren't many treasures left in its path.

Han Li took a deep breath, and 35 specks of golden light suddenly appeared over his body.

He was planning to unleash a secret technique that could stimulate the latent potential of his immortal acupoints, and it could take up to a century for him to recover from the repercussions, but he had no choice.

All of a sudden, a burst of faint buzzing rang out up above.

Han Li looked up to see what was happening, and a surprised look instantly appeared in his eyes.

As it turned out, the bright gray light released by the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain had formed a gray barrier that had managed to stop the seemingly unstoppable pillar of golden light in its tracks.

Neither the gray light nor the golden light seemed to be able to get the better of the other, and an elated look appeared on Han Li's face as he hurriedly abandoned the secret technique that he was just about to unleash.

He cast his gaze toward the gray light around the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain to find that it was giving off bursts of law power fluctuations, and this was the exact same type of law power that he had been trying to identify before.

It was this burst of law powers that had stopped the pillar of golden light cold in its tracks, and an enlightened look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

The Integrated Five Extremes Mountain had the innate ability to weaken lightning tribulations, and he had refined it for the purpose of helping him transcend his ascension tribulation. This pill tribulation was most likely a type of lightning tribulation as well, so it was no wonder that the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain could pose meaningful resistance.

It seemed that this Integrated Five Extremes Mountain was a far more formidable treasure than he imagined.

The Integrated Five Extremes Mountain that he had initially refined had been quite powerful, but only in the context of the Spirit Realm, and it couldn't even have been considered to be an immortal treasure in the Immortal Realm.

However, Tao Yu had dedicated a large amount of resources to refining this treasures, and Han Li had been rather perplexed by this, but he now realized that Tao Yu had most likely been willing to invest so much into the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain as he was already aware that it would be very effective at warding off pill tribulations.

However, this wasn't the time to be pondering such matters.

The Integrated Five Extremes Mountain was able to keep the pillar of golden light at bay, but the pill tribulation was extremely formidable, and the gray light being released by the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain was slowly being overwhelmed.

However, at the same time, the pillar of golden light was also slowly shrinking.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately cast aside all of his other treasures to focus solely on supporting the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

One treasure after another came clanging down onto the ground, but Han Li didn't spare them so much as even a single glance.

He had invested countless time, effort, and resources into refining this dao pill, and he certainly wasn't going to accept failure at the last hurdle.

Chapter 365: Undercurrents

The gray and golden light continued to clash in mid-air, causing a huge commotion while bursts of violent world's origin qi surged through the area.

Neither side was able to gain the upper hand, and an impasse had ensued.

However, as time passed, both the gray light released by the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain and the pillar of golden light were constantly being worn down.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

He didn't have much immortal spiritual power left, and even with the support of Immortal Origin Stones, he wasn't going to be able to keep this up for much longer.

What was even more concerning was that as it was warding off the pillar of golden light, the law power that the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain contained was constantly being whittled down. At this point, most of it had already been expended, so not only was it also not going to be able to last much longer, it was most likely going to take a very long time to recover after this.

Han Li took a deep breath while replenishing his immortal spiritual power reserves with the Immortal Origin Stone in his hand, while his other hand was still making a series of hand seals so that he could continue to support the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain with his immortal spiritual power.

All of a sudden, the mountain in mid-air abruptly shuddered, following which the gray light that it was radiating quickly faded.

The law power within the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain had finally been exhausted, and it was unable to oppose the pillar of golden light any longer.

Thankfully, at this point, the pillar of golden light had also been severely whittled down, and it struck the dao pill in a flash right after the gray light faded.

The dao pill shuddered violently once again as the two dao marks on its surface began to flash erratically.

At this point, Han Li's immortal spiritual power was close to running out as well, but he made one more last-ditch effort as a burst of dazzling golden light erupted out of the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him, then split up into several dozen strands of golden light once again before wrapping themselves around the dao pill, forming a fist-sized golden ball.

His face had turned deathly pale, and what little remained of his immortal spiritual power had been completely drained, so he wasn't going to be able to do anything else.

The golden ball shuddered while flashing erratically, and it looked as if it could explode at any moment.

Han Li was looking on with an anxious expression, but there was nothing more that he could do.

Right at this moment, Daoist Xie abruptly appeared behind him, then thrust its palms forward, releasing two pillars of golden light that surged into Han Li's body, filling his empty dantian with a burst of pure immortal spiritual power.

Han Li was ecstatic, and he immediately began making a string of hand seals, upon which the golden ball gradually stabilized itself.

Han Li heaved a long sigh of relief upon seeing this, and his Mantra Treasured Axis vanished alongside the golden ball at his behest, revealing the dao pill inside the latter.

Having transcended two pill tribulations, the dao pill appeared even brighter and more vibrant than before, the time law power fluctuations that it was giving off had also become more formidable.

However, there was no time for Han Li to give it a close inspection. The pill tribulation hadn't lasted a very long time, but it had caused a massive phenomenon, and it was sure to have attracted the attention of some nearby cultivators.

With that in mind, he quickly swallowed a pill, then carefully stored the dao pill into a jade box before turning around to give Daoist Xie a nod of gratitude.

"We have to get out of here. I can already sense people coming this way," Daoist Xie said as it transformed into a streak of golden light that vanished into Han Li's body.

Han Li didn't waste any time with words, sweeping a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that stowed away all of the treasures on the ground, as well as the silver cauldron.

He then quickly swept his spiritual sense across the entire cave abode, and only after confirming that there was nothing left inside that could expose his identity did he fly out of the cave abode in a flash.

At this point, the vast golden cloud in the sky had already vanished, but the nearby sea was still slightly more turbulent than usual.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li retrieved all of the array tools near the cave abode, which flew up his sleeve as streaks of light.

He then made a hand seal, and a burst of golden lightning erupted out of his body as he prepared to unleash his lightning teleportation array.

However, right at this moment, gusts of azure wind abruptly emerged out of thin air nearby amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

In the blink of an eye, an azure array had taken shape, and it was giving off tremendous spatial power.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

The azure array was very similar to his lightning array, except it combined the powers of wind and space rather than lightning and space.

Some time was required to set up the lightning array, so it was already too late to get away without being detected by whoever was in the lightning array.

With these thoughts racing through his mind, Han Li immediately stopped in his tracks before flying back toward the cave abode.

At the same time, he put on his Transient Guild mask and adopted a disguise, transforming himself into a middle-aged man.

Mere moments later, a black-robed man with a thin and tall figure emerged within the azure array. His eyes were quite long and thin, as were his eyebrows, giving him a rather sharp and hostile disposition.

The enormous aura emanating from his body indicated that he was also a late-True Immortal cultivator.

Han Li stopped in his tracks before turning to the black-robed man with a surprised expression.

The man cast his gaze toward Han Li as well, and a wary look immediately appeared on his face.

"I don't recall seeing you around these parts before, Fellow Daoist. My name is Miao Yan, and I just so happen to have been cultivating nearby, so I decided to come here and check out the phenomenon that had just taken place. May I ask your name, Fellow Daoist?" Han Li said with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute, putting on a friendly façade.

Despite his friendly demeanor, internally, he was very surprised.

He had never seen this person in the Black Wind Sea, and as far as he was aware, the island masters of Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island were the only two late-True Immortal cultivators that were native to the Black Wind Sea.

Having said that, it was clear to Han Li that there were clearly other powers behind those two islands.

These thoughts were flashing rapidly through Han Li's mind while the black-robed man inspected his surroundings briefly, then turned his gaze back to Han Li as he replied in a rather cold voice, "My name is Ge Yu."

"I see. Did you also come here to investigate the phenomenon that had just taken place, Fellow Daoist Ge?" Han Li asked.

Ge Yu nodded in response, then took a meaningful glance at Han Li as he said, "I immediately came here using my teleportation array upon sensing what was happening here, and I thought I was already extremely fast, but it seems you were able to beat me here."

Han Li's smile remained unchanged as he explained, "My cave abode is just nearby, and I also immediately came here upon sensing the phenomenon, so I naturally got here a little faster."

"Is that right?" Ge Yu mused as he descended toward the cave abode.

Han Li hurriedly trailed along behind him, then pretended to explore the cave abode.

Having already conducted a thorough cleanup job earlier, there was no chance that anything of note would be discovered here.

Sure enough, the two of them quickly searched through the cave abode without discovering anything worthy of note.

"It looks like we're still too late, and whoever was here has already left. I wonder what they were doing to have triggered such a massive phenomenon. Could it be that some powerful treasure was created here? It seems like a bit of a stretch," Han Li mused with a perplexed expression.

Ge Yu merely took a glance at Han Li without saying anything.

Right at this moment, several streaks of light appeared on the distant horizon, then quickly flew onto the scene to reveal a group of cultivators, all of whom were at the early-True Immortal Stage.

Upon detecting the cultivation bases of Han Li and Ge Yu, all of the newcomers immediately chose to keep their distance.

Shortly thereafter, more cultivators arrived on the scene from different directions, and Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon seeing this, but internally, he was feeling a little uneasy.

The vast majority of these cultivators weren't Earthly Immortals, so they were clearly outsiders. It seemed that the situation in the Black Wind Sea was far more complex than he had anticipated, and it appeared that many True Immortals from the outside had entered this region during the years that he had been away.

Could it be that all of them had come to search for resources?

The problem with this theory was that while it was true that the Black Wind Sea was superior to the Spirit Realm, it was considered to be extremely lacking in resources in the context of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and in this regard, it was inferior even to the Primordial Wave Continent.

"It looks like there's nothing here. The situation may become more complex with more people arriving on the scene, so I'll be taking my leave," Han Li said with slightly furrowed brows as he cupped his fist in a parting salute toward Ge Yu, then flew away as a streak of azure light.

Ge Yu remained on the spot and watched Han Li depart for a moment before also flying away himself as a gust of azure wind.

Only then did the other cultivators nearby begin to approach the island.

……

Countless kilometers away, there was a stretch of ocean with an extremely dense cloud of black mist hanging over its surface, and the sky was also very dim.

A burst of spatial fluctuations emerged over the surface of the sea, following which a golden lightning array took shape with Han Li inside it.

He swept his spiritual sense through the surrounding area, upon which his expression eased slightly.

After leaving the island, he had teleported through the Black Wind Sea multiple times before arriving here, so even if there had been someone following him, he should've been able to shake them off his trail by now.

He took a glance at his surroundings, then abruptly swooped down toward the sea below, quickly descending to the seabed before sitting down with his legs crossed.

At this moment, his entire body was racked with sharp pain from using Daoist Xie's immortal spiritual power.

He set up a couple of restrictions, then swallowed a pill before closing his eyes to meditate.

Three days and three nights later, he opened his eyes before rising to his feet.

The discomfort in his body had already completely faded, and having endured this pill tribulation, he had gained a better understanding of the power of time as well, which should've been quite helpful in his bid to master the laws of time through consuming the dao pill.

With that in mind, a hint of excitement appeared in his eyes.

Chapter 366: Early Onset

Moments later, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to remove the surrounding restrictions, then flew out of the sea toward his cave abode.

On the way back, he suddenly felt a dull and heavy sensation in his head.

What's going on? Could it be that I still haven't fully recovered?

He closed his eyes, planning to inspect his own internal condition, yet right as he activated his Spirit Refinement Technique, the enormous spiritual sense in his mind suddenly began to churn and surge violently without any warning.

It was as if there were countless tiny blades slashing through his mind with reckless abandon, and the onset of pain was so severe and abrupt that he couldn't help but let loose an agonized yell.

He threw his hands onto his own head, and his face instantly became as pale as a sheet.

Immediately thereafter, he stopped cold in his tracks, then plummeted straight out of the heavens, plunging into the sea down below like a dead weight.

His entire body was inundated by the cool seawater, yet it did nothing to relieve his pain, which was only worsening by the second. His sanity was gradually eroded by the agony, and a layer of faint crimson light had appeared over his eyes.

……

Han Li reflexively tried to open his eyes, but he was feeling extremely groggy. He forced his own eyes open with great difficulty, but everything in front of him was an indistinct blur, and all he could hear were animalistic howls and roars ringing out around him.

These sound seemed to be able to penetrate directly into his mind, setting his blood alight. It was as if some long-repressed fury in his heart had finally risen to the fore, striking him with a sense of asphyxiation, and only by releasing all of this pent-up fury could he restore his own sanity.

His hands were swinging wildly through the air, throwing erratic punches and palm strikes in a frantic effort to release his unbridled frustration and fury.

He wanted to roar with all his might, but he couldn't hear anything over the chaotic commotion ringing out around him. As he continued to lash out aimlessly at his surroundings, the surrounding commotion was becoming louder and louder, and he seemed to have finally found an outlet through which he could vent his fury.

At this moment, his mind was completely blank.

As the commotion grew louder and louder, the fury in his heart slowly subsided, and he began to detect a strong bloody odor in the air.

Right at this moment, his vision began to slowly recover, andt he first sight that he was greeted by was a vast expanse of bright red.

It was as if he had fallen into a boundless sea of blood.

On top of that, there were countless mangled carcasses of all types of different creatures strewn all around him, and it seemed that a horrific slaughter had just taken place here.

Right at this moment, a burst of sharp pain speared through Han Li's mind, and the clarity of his vision was finally completely restored.

He shook his head vigorously, slowly recovering from his stupor, and the clarity in his mind also returned.

In this instant, he felt completely feeble and powerless, and his entire body was throbbing with intense pain, as if he had just endured an extremely fierce battle.

However, as he raised his head once again to inspect his surroundings, he discovered that he was standing on an island, facing the turbulent sea up ahead.

He felt as if his memories were a little jumbled, and he couldn't recall anything from the time after he left the small island on which he had been engaging in dao pill refinement. Thus, he had no idea how he had ended up here.

He took a deep breath and closed his eyes, attempting to recollect what had happened up to this point, yet as soon as he attempted to do so, a burst of agony instantly shot through his mind once again.

He hurriedly abandoned this train of thought before shaking his head once again, and only then did the pain subside a little.

All of a sudden, a thought seemed to have occurred to him, and he turned around to look behind him, upon which he discovered that he was standing on quite a large island that was several dozen kilometers in size, but it was severely ravaged and on the verge of collapse.

At the center of the island was what was once a large mountain range, but it had been split in half down the center, and a huge lake had appeared over the entire island, with seawater gushing in to fill it.

All of the other mountains in the mountain range had also been destroyed, as had all of the vegetation on the island, and it was truly a horrific sight to behold.

A stunned look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

At this point, most of the pain in his mind had already subsided, and he was able to release his enormous spiritual sense as normal to inspect his surroundings.

In doing so, he was shocked once again to discover that just like the island, the seabed down below had also been severely ravaged, riddled with many deep craters and trenches, as if it were a field that had been plowed.

There were some spots where the rifts were so deep that the magma beneath the earth had come gushing out, but at this point, it had already solidified.

Through his spiritual sense, Han Li was able to detect that this destruction had been wrought over an enormous area.

All of the islands within a radius of thousand of kilometers had been completely destroyed, with some having sunk down to the seabed, while others resembled tattered old rags, just like the one that Han Li was situated on.

Interspersed throughout the remnants of the islands on the seabed were many demon beast carcasses, all of which had been quite formidable, with no lack of Body Integration and even Grand Ascension Stage demon beasts among them.

All of them had been killed in extremely horrific fashion. A Grand Ascension Stage wyrm that was over 1,000 feet in length had been torn into seven or eight pieces, and its blood had stained a massive area of the sea red. Even in death, there was still a look of horror deep in its eyes.

Right at this moment, a bolt of golden lightning descended out of the sky, landing not far away from Han Li to reveal none other than Daoist Xie.

"What happened here, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

Daoist Xie was silent for a moment, then asked, "Do you not remember what just happened, Fellow Daoist? You're personally responsible for all of this destruction."

"Me?"

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a hint of foreboding welled up in his heart.

"On the way back to your cave abode, it was as if you had suddenly gone insane. You went on a spree of destruction as if you had been possessed, and you completely lost your sanity. No matter how I tried to call out to you, you displayed no reaction," Daoist Xie explained.

Han Li was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then asked, "How long was I in that... deranged state?"

"About 15 minutes," Daoist Xie replied after a brief moment of contemplation.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as he fell silent.

Thanks to this reminder from Daoist Xie, he was able to recall what had happened prior to this short bout of amnesia.

During his flight, he had suddenly been struck by a burst of sharp pain in the head, and after that, he had quickly lost consciousness, and the only thing that he could recall was that his heart had been overwhelmed by intense killing intent.

How did this happen? Could it be that I fell prey to some kind of sneak attack?

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he raised his head as he murmured to himself, "It's the Spirit Refinement Technique..."

At his current level of power, even a Golden Immortal wouldn't have been able to manipulate his mind like this without his detection.

Thinking back to what had just happened, the Spirit Refinement Technique was the only possible explanation.

After a brief moment of hesitation, he tried to activate his Spirit Refinement Technique, and he was instantly struck by a burst of intense agony in his mind that caused him to give an involuntary groan.

He hurriedly stopped what he was doing, and only then did the pain in his mind slowly subside.

That confirmed his suspicions that all of this had been caused by the Spirit Refinement Technique, and his expression darkened even further as he arrived at this verdict.

According to that immortal by the name of He Kang, [1] mastering the third level of the Spirit Refinement Technique should've ensured that he would be fine for the next 30,000 to 40,000 years. However, only less than 20,000 years had passed since he mastered the third level of the spiritual sense, so why had this spiritual sense crisis already arisen?

Had He Kang lied to him, or had some other factor resulted in this early onset of the spiritual sense crisis?

Han Li slowly exhaled as he composed himself.

In any case, seeing as the problem had already arisen, the most important thing for him to do now was to find a solution. Otherwise, he was going to be doomed to the fate of becoming a mindless barbarian who only knew slaughter and nothing else.

It was very fortunate that all of this had taken place in a very secluded area, and the duration of his deranged rampage had been quite short, perhaps due to the fact that this was only the first onset. Otherwise, he could've easily attracted a great deal of attention and landed himself in a huge amount of trouble.

Even though the crisis had been averted for now, there was no telling when he was going to enter that deranged state again, and that was clearly a very dangerous state to be in. Furthermore, according to what he had learned about the Spirit Refinement Technique in the past, these onsets of insanity were only going to become more prolonged with shorter intervals between each successive onset.

According to He Kang, the only way to resolve this issue was to cultivate the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Back in the Blaze Dragon Dao, Han Li had conducted some research into the Spirit Refinement Technique, but he had thought that he would have at least 20,000 to 30,000 years before the onset of the spiritual sense crisis, and he had many other matters to attend to at the time, so he hadn't been very diligent in his research.

According to what he had learned, there were very few records pertaining to the Spirit Refinement Technique in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and it had been a very long time since the last crisis that had arisen from the Spirit Refinement Technique, so very few people even knew about the forbidden technique.

The Blaze Dragon Dao's Merit Conveyance Palace did carry the Spirit Refinement Technique, but it was listed as a forbidden scripture that couldn't be accessed by anyone other than the dao lords. On top of that, the Merit Conveyance Palace only carried the first three levels of the cultivation art, so that wouldn't have helped Han Li anyway.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as his brows became tightly furrowed.

Even a major sect like the Blaze Dragon Dao didn't have the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique, so where was he supposed to find it in the Black Wind Sea?

[1]. For more information on He Kang, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2247: Spiritual Sense Chains and Punishment Lightning.

[Back]

Chapter 367: Taking the Pill

Han Li remained standing on the spot for a moment in silence, and Daoist Xie didn't say anything, either, merely hovering in front of him.

All of a sudden, a thought seemed to have occurred to him, and he flipped a hand over to produce an azure tiger mask.

He looked at the mask in his hand for a moment with a contemplative look on his face, then stowed it away again.

Immediately thereafter, he stowed Daoist Xie away as well before flying away into the distance as a streak of azure light.

Several days later.

Han Li appeared in the sky above his cave abode, and after sweeping his spiritual sense briefly over the area, he heaved an internal sigh of relief.

None of the restrictions around the island appeared to have been touched at all, and the entrance of the cave abode was also tightly sealed. It seemed that no one had been here since he last left.

He swooped down and vanished into the restrictions in a flash, quickly entering the cave abode.

After briefly visiting all of the areas in the cave abode, he made his way into his secret chamber.

Once there, he swept a sleeve through the air, and a yellow light barrier emerged to encompass the entire secret chamber.

Only then did Han Li put on the azure tiger mask before activating the Transient Guild array plate projection. Right as he was about to release a mission, he stopped what he was doing.

Even though it was virtually impossible to track someone down in the Transient Guild using their mask alone, he had already been using this tiger mask for quite some time, so continuing to use it would only incur unnecessary risk. Hence, it would be best to find an opportunity to switch to a different mask in the future.

With that in mind, Han Li quickly released a mission searching for the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Due to the fact that the Spirit Refinement Technique was considered to be a forbidden art in the Immortal Realm, he only provided a very vague description of what the cultivation art was, mentioning that it had a significant enhancement effect on one's spiritual sense without actually directly mentioning its name.

However, anyone who had cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique or were aware of it would definitely be able to tell that he was referring to none other than the Spirit Refinement Technique.

For this mission, Han Li offered quite a substantial compensation and even left room for negotiation if one weren't satisfied with the reward.

After that, he stowed the mask away before heaving a faint sigh.

Given his current circumstances, all he could do was rely on the Transient Guild for now to see if there were any solutions. If he couldn't find any, then perhaps he would have to venture out of the Black Wind Sea.

Back when he first joined the Transient Guild, it had provided him with many pleasant surprises, but as his cultivation base increased, the problems that he was facing also changed, and the Transient Guild was gradually becoming unable to fulfill all of his needs.

For example, it had taken a very long time to secure the supplementary ingredients required for the dao pill, and he was hoping that he wouldn't be disappointed once again.

He shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, then closed his eyes and activated his Spirit Refinement Technique.

His enormous spiritual sense began to circulate throughout his mind, starting fast before slowing down.

As this happened, Han Li felt a cool and refreshing sensation in his mind without any discomfort, and it was as if that spiritual sense crisis had been nothing more than a distant dream.

This was quite a relief, indicating that his spiritual sense had already returned to normal. He didn't know when the next spiritual sense crisis was going to strike, but it most likely wasn't going to be anytime soon.

With that in mind, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce an azure jade box, then applied a few golden talismans to it.

Even with the talismans acting as a seal, there were still faint law fluctuations emanating from the box, and it contained none other than the dao pill that he had just refined.

He looked at the jade box for a moment, then set it aside before closing his eyes again, preparing to prime himself into his best condition.

As he reopened his eyes three days later, his immortal spiritual power and spiritual sense were all in peak condition, and his heart was also as still as a calm lake.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Daoist Xie was released amid a flash of golden lightning, and Han Li said, "Brother Xie, this is quite an obscure location that we're in, but I'll need you to keep a lookout for me again as a safety precaution."

Daoist Xie remained silent as he nodded in response, then vanished into thin air amid a flash of lightning.

Meanwhile, Han Li swept his sleeve through the air once again, and a dense azure light barrier appeared over the door of his secret chamber before fading away in a flash.

Only after doing all of this did Han Li pick up the jade box from the ground again, and he removed the talismans on its surface before lifting its lid to reveal the golden dao pill inside.

He gently picked up the dao pill between two of his fingers and gave it a close inspection before swallowing it.

In the next instant, his brows instantly became tightly furrowed in pain, and at the same time, vibrant golden light was radiating from his body.

Immediately thereafter, the Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him, revolving on the spot while also radiating dazzling golden light.

All 360 Time Dao Runes on the axis were also glowing brightly while rapidly revolving, giving off far brighter radiance than usual.

At the same time, a golden dao mark appeared over Han Li's body, one that was identical to the dao mark on the dao pill.

A few seconds later, a second golden dao mark appeared, and both were giving off bright golden radiance that illuminated his entire body a faint golden color.

The light that was radiating from the dao marks were filled with countless golden runes, all of which were giving off indescribably formidable law power fluctuations.

Han Li's entire body was inundated by these golden runes, and his eyes were tightly shut as he made a rapid string of hand seals.

Five years passed by in the blink of an eye.

The entire island that Han Li's cave abode was situated on was still enshrouded under multiple restrictions that completely concealed it, and it would've been impossible to uncover the island's exact location unless one were in direct contact with it.

This morning, a series of ripples suddenly appeared on the calm surface of the sea, and it was gradually getting closer.

A loud splash then rang out as the upper half of a white sea beast emerged from the waves, slowly swimming toward the island.

The beast had a pristine white body that looked as if it had been carved out of jade, and it was none other than the Pig Dolphin Beast.

At this point, it had already completely consolidated its Deity Transformation Stage cultivation base, and its eight legs were giving off a faint white light while acting as two rows of oars that were propelling it quickly through the water.

After making a breakthrough to the Deity Transformation Stage with Han Li's assistance, it had been in seclusion in its cave abode this entire time.

Not long ago, it had consolidated its own cultivation base, and it had immediately come out of seclusion, hoping to meet Han Li again.

While Pig Dolphin Beasts weren't particularly formidable, they possessed an innate ability that granted them heightened sensitivity to all types of spiritual qi fluctuations, and they also liked to collect ore and spirit materials.

This time, it had brought its entire collection with it, and it was hoping that it could exchange its collection for some more benefits from Han Li.

It didn't take long before the Pig Dolphin Beast had swam a lap around the island. The island had disappeared, and there was an invisible barrier standing in its way.

The barrier was quite gentle and soft, but it was also just as unyielding.

It wasn't overly surprised by this, and it knew that these restrictions had to have been set up by that almighty human cultivator, so it naturally wasn't going to try and barge its way in by force.

However, it seemed that it wasn't going to be able to meet Han Li this time.

With that in mind, the Pig Dolphin Beast took a couple more glances in the direction of the island, then turned to swim away, but right at this moment, a burst of enormous energy fluctuations suddenly emerged to encompass the entire island and the nearby area.

The energy fluctuations were extremely formidable, striking the Pig Dolphin Beast with the impression that it was facing the wrath of the entirety of heaven and earth.

It began to tremble uncontrollably, but it didn't dare to move even a single inch, and at the same time, the nearby world's origin qi suddenly became extremely chaotic and turbulent, forming numerous golden spiritual qi vortexes of different sizes, some of which were in excess of an acre in area, while others were only the size of human fists.

Regardless of what size they were, all of the golden vortexes had countless radiant golden runes swirling within them, and the entire sea sea was filled with these golden vortex, producing what appeared to have been a golden spirit cloud that wasn't any smaller than the one that had taken shape during the pill tribulation.

The countless swirling golden vortexes presented a stunning sight to behold, and formidable law power fluctuations were spreading out of the golden vortex in all directions.

All of a sudden, all of the golden vortexes converged toward a certain spot like the receding tide.

In the blink of an eye, all of the golden vortexes had disappeared without a trace, and all that remained was a massive thread of golden light that was several dozen kilometers in length hanging in hte sky.

The thread of light was quite translucent and was gently swaying from side to side as if it were a living creature.

Countless golden runes of different sizes were dancing over its surface, and it was giving off a burst of deafening rumbling alongside extremely formidable time law power fluctuations.

Even though it was only a single thread of light, it seemed to contain more power than all of the countless golden vortexes combined, and it was swaying in the air like a giant dragon that was imbued with boundless power.

All of a sudden, all of the golden light and runes around the thread of light quickly faded, and the thunderous rumbling also gradually subsided.

All that remained was a golden thread of light that was suspended peacefully in mid-air.

It had become even more translucent in appearance, and the time law power fluctuations that it was releasing had also become more formidable.

Furthermore, in contrast with before, the time law power that it was giving off at this moment wasn't chaotic in the slightest. Instead, it was extremely profound and complied perfectly with the natural order.

Just like before, the thread of light continued to sway gently from side to side, but this time, all of the space in its wake seemed to have been completely frozen and immobilized.

This was very similar to the time-slowing effect of the Mantra Treasured Axis, but also seemingly a little different somehow.

Right at this moment, a burst of golden light flashed past the cave abode down below, and the thread of light in the sky suddenly shrank down before vanishing into the cave abode in a flash.

The phenomenon in the nearby area instantly subsided, and everything returned to normal.

The Pig Dolphin Beast stared blankly in the direction of the island for a moment, then hurriedly plunged headfirst into the sea, frantically swimming back to the coral island.

The phenomenon that had just taken place had been quite a spectacle to behold, but it was far smaller in its scale and impact than the dao tribulation, so it didn't attract much attention.

Chapter 368: You're Awake

Meanwhile, elsewhere in the Immortal Realm.

This was a space that was filled with countless golden clouds of different sizes, filling the entire area with radiant golden light.

These golden clouds were drifting up and down incessantly while also constantly taking on all types of unidentifiable forms, presenting a mesmerizing sight to behold.`

On top of one of the golden clouds was an enormous golden stone plaque that was over 100,000 feet tall, and it was radiating bursts of golden light that were swirling incessantly.

A series of golden designs were inscribed upon the stone plaque, and they appeared to have been some type of runes, filling virtually the entirety of the plaque.

These golden runes varied in size and brightness, but generally speaking, the larger tended to be brighter as well.

The largest of the runes were the size of houses, giving off resplendent golden light, while the smallest ones were only fist-sized and were also quite dim.

Some of the golden runes were completely still, while others were flashing incessantly while giving off formidable time law power fluctuations.

Right at this moment, the stone plaque suddenly began to glow with dazzling golden radiance while also emitting a sharp screeching sound.

A new line of golden text then appeared on a blank spot near the bottom of the stone plaque, and the line of text was also gently flashing with golden light.

It didn't take long before the golden radiance emanating from the stone plaque subsided, and everything returned to its original state.

All of a sudden, countless specks of golden light appeared out of thin air in front of the giant plaque, and it formed a huge golden eye, following which an indistinct and emotionless voice rang out, one that didn't sound male or female.

"It looks like one more person had mastered the laws of time..."

The voice echoed in the space for a while before fading away, and in the next instant, the giant golden eye also disintegrated into specks of golden light again.

……

Inside the secret chamber of his cave abode, Han Li's entire body was basked in radiant golden light, while his Mantra Treasured Axis was slowly revolving behind him.

Hovering above his head was a translucent golden thread that was around a foot in length, and it was slowly swaying from side to side like a spirit snake.

Even though it had been shrunk down by countless orders of magnitude, the time law power fluctuations that it was giving off hadn't abated in the slightest, and it was filling the entire secret chamber, influencing everything around it.

Aside from Han Li and the golden light that was radiating from his body, everything else in the secret chamber appeared to have been completely still.

Han Li opened his eyes, and a hint of excitement appeared on his face as he looked at the translucent thread above his head.

The process of mastering the laws of time had been quite an arduous one, and it had taken him several years just to digest the dao pill.

After that, it had taken him several more years to master the laws of time thanks to the power of the dao pill.

During this period, several mishaps had occurred, but thankfully, he was quite well prepared and had a large supply of precious pills that allowed him to weather the storm.

Furthermore, even though his past attempts to master the laws of time had ended in failure, he had gotten a little closer every single time, and that had assisted him in this process. It was only thanks to a combination of all of these factors that he had managed to succeed in this endeavor.

After mastering the laws of time, everything had become different. He could sense that he had attained a special understanding of this mysterious power, and his interpretation of the Mantra Axis Scripture had also changed.

The clearest sign of this was that he felt a greater sense of control over his Mantra Treasured Axis.

In the instant that he attained this time law thread, he had even gleaned a trace of the passage of time in the entire world around him.

Only after a long while did the excitement in his heart slowly subside, and he made a hand seal, upon which the golden light radiating from the translucent golden thread vanished.

Everything in the secret chamber instantly returned to normal, and as he continued to make more hand seals, the golden thread began to transform according to his will, elongating, shrinking, and even tying itself into knots at Han Li's behest.

The different forms that it took on also had an impact on the time law powers that it was giving off, and an intrigued look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

It seemed that this time law thread was far more profound than he anticipated, but he would have plenty of time to examine it in the future.

Maintaining the time law thread was very taxing on his immortal spiritual power, so he was just about to stow it away when a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he flipped a hand over to summon his Heaven Controlling Vial instead.

He had examined the vial countless times in the past without any notable outcomes, but now that he had mastered the laws of time, perhaps he would be able to glean some more of the Heaven Controlling Vial's secrets.

With that in mind, Han Li took a deep breath, yet before he had a chance to do anything, the Heaven Controlling Vial suddenly began to glow as radiantly as a green sun, then flew out of his grasp before hovering in mid-air.

At the same time, the Mantra Treasured Axis behind Han Li also brightened considerably while revolving rapidly, and the golden time law thread shot forth into the axis in a flash.

The light radiating from the Mantra Treasured Axis had become 10 times brighter than normal, and all of its Time Dao Runes had lit up in unison.

The Eye of Truth quickly took shape at the center of the axis, and even though the eye was still closed, it was also radiating dazzling golden light with countless golden runes flashing around it.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, but he remained still on the spot, refraining from doing anything.

Just like last time, he could sense that the Heaven Controlling Vial, the Mantra Treasured Axis, and even the time law thread were no longer under his control.

A hint of anticipation welled up in his heart.

Whenever something like this happened, he almost always stood to benefit, so he was eager to see what was going to unfold this time.

All of a sudden, the Heaven Controlling Vial and the Mantra Treasured Axis began to resonate with one another, and the light that they were giving off became brighter and brighter, while bursts of formidable energy fluctuations began proliferating outward in all directions.

Right at this moment, the Eye of Truth sprang open, and the time law thread shot out from within before vanishing into the Heaven Controlling Vial.

The surface of the Heaven Controlling Vial instantly began to glow a radiant green color, and it rapidly swelled to the size of a millstone.

Countless green runes appeared on its surface, surging up and down while flashing incessantly like stars in the night sky.

All of a sudden, the green runes rose up from the surface of the vial before converging inside it to form a green cloud that was churning incessantly, with a vortex slowly taking shape within it.

A burst of special energy fluctuations were emanating out of the green cloud, and they weren't particularly formidable, but the space around the Heaven Controlling Vial was rippling violently.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and right at this moment, the green cloud within the Heaven Controlling Vial transformed into a thick pillar of green light that erupted outward.

Countless bursts of translucent light emerged, forming the same translucent wall of light from before.

A hint of disappointment flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

While it was true that the wall of light was clearly something quite profound, he was hoping that the Heaven Controlling Vial would be able to display something different this time, but that didn't seem to have been the case.

However, he then noticed that a green vortex design had appeared on the wall of light, and it was the same green vortex that had previously appeared inside the vial.

The wall of light shuddered as countless streaks of light flashed over its surface, and the green vortex suddenly began to flash, devouring all of the streaks of light as it began to rapidly expand.

Initially, it was only around the size of a washbasin, but in just a few seconds, it had swelled to the size of a house.

A burst of tremendous suction force erupted out of the vortex to envelop Han Li's entire body, and he could sense that his body wasn't being affected by this burst of suction force at all, but in the next instant, his spiritual sense was pulled involuntarily out of his mind and into the vortex.

Before he had a chance to do anything, he felt a burst of sharp pain in his head, immediately following which he fell unconscious.

An indeterminate amount of time passed by before Han Li slowly regained consciousness and opened his eyes.

He was greeted by the sight of a dilapidated ceiling that was riddled with cobwebs and holes, through which he could see the sky overhead.

He could also hear something indistinct, but it was also very loud.

At this moment, his entire body was racked with agony, and even lifting a finger felt like a herculean task.

He turned his head to the side with great difficulty, and in doing so, he discovered that he was laying on a bed in what appeared to have been a dilapidated temple.

As for the sound that he was hearing, it was coming from a yellow-robed young boy with light golden skin, and he was knelt down by his bedside, sobbing in grief.

Han Li was completely dumbstruck upon seeing this.

Where is this place? Wasn't I in my cave abode examining the Heaven Controlling Vial? How did I end up here?

Han Li tried to recall what had happened, but all of a sudden, he was struck by a splitting headache, causing him to reflexively throw his hands onto his own head as he gave a muffled groan.

Thankfully, the pain subsided in an instant, and he had only just heaved a sigh of relief when his expression abruptly stiffened.

Just now, a stream of chaotic and alien memories had flooded into his mind.

These memories were fragmented and incomplete, yet before he had a chance to examine them, the young boy beside his bed had heard his muffled groan, and he immediately raised his head with an ecstatic expression despite the tears that were still swimming in his eyes.

"Master, you're awake!"

Chapter 369: Master and Disciple

Master?

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this.

He didn't recall ever accepting such a disciple, but for some reason, the young boy looked a little familiar to him.

"I knew you'd be alright, Master! I managed to get two Dragon Gall Flowers from Master Zhen, and I've already brewed them into medicine. I'll fetch it for you right now."

The young boy hurriedly wiped the tears from his face as he rose to his feet and made his way outside.

Han Li looked on with a dazed expression as the young boy departed, then took a glance down at his own body, only to be stunned to find that he had become a thin and withered old man.

He was wearing an azure daoist robe, and his hands were as wizened as a pair of old tree branches.

What happened? How did I suddenly age so much? What is this place, and who is that boy?

A string of questions flashed through Han Li's mind, none of which he had an answer for.

At this moment, the pain in his body had mostly abated, and he struggled up into a seated position, pressing a hand against the edge of the bed for support.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he hurriedly began inspecting his own internal condition, upon which he became even more concerned.

It had become clear to him that this body definitely wasn't his, but for some reason, he seemed to have possessed it.

On top of that, this body had suffered extremely severe internal injuries to its organs. In particular, it had fallen prey to a type of lethal poison.

With Han Li's normal cultivation base, he would've been able to recover from these ailments in a very short time, but this body only possessed a late-Foundation Establishment Stage cultivation base, so it was completely unable to suppress the poison and these internal injuries.

In other words, this body didn't have much life left in it, and it was only a matter of time before it met its demise.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he took a deep breath, then drew upon which little remained of the magic power in this body before flicking a finger through the air.

A series of water droplets instantly appeared in the surrounding air, then converged toward the space in front of him to form a mirror of water that was around a foot in size, through which Han Li was able to see the reflection of an elderly daoist priest with a white beard.

He then swept a hand through the air to scatter the mirror before falling into deep thought.

At this point, the pain in his head had mostly faded, and he had recalled what had previously happened.

The time law thread, his Mantra Treasured Axis, and the Heaven Controlling Vial seemed to have resonated with one another from that wall of light, and the vortex on the wall of light seemed to have sucked his soul into this place.

Could this be some type of illusion?

Han Li raised his head to inspect his surroundings, only to find that everything around him was extremely realistic, with no signs of any illusion being present.

If this isn't an illusion, then what could it be?

More snippets of memories began to surface in Han Li's mind, and he attempted to sort through them.

Before long, he had already examined all of those memories, and an enlightened look appeared on his face.

These memories belonged to none other than the elderly daoist priest whose body he was currently possessing.

The daoist priest's name was Ling Yunzi, while the young boy just now was his only disciple, Li Yuanjiu.

Ling Yunzi sustained severe injuries during a fight over a spirit plant, and even though he was able to escape, his injuries were too severe, and he perished not long ago.

However, Han Li's soul had somehow possessed this recently deceased body, leading Li Yuanjiu to the false conclusion that his master had been resurrected.

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed something to his left.

Suspended in mid-air there was a very indistinct golden axis that was virtually completely invisible, and he wouldn't have been able to notice it had he not just so happened to have looked in that direction.

The golden axis was none other than his Mantra Treasured Axis, and the 360 Time Dao Runes on its surface were gently flashing.

At this point, around two dozen of the Time Dao Runes had already dimmed, and with each second that passed, one more Time Dao Rune would fade, just like last time the wall of light had been conjured up.

Han Li's mind was racing, and he seemed to have grasped onto something, but it was unclear to him exactly what it was.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps rang out as Li Yuanjiu hurried into the room, carefully holding a clay bowl with both hands. The bowl contained a black medicinal liquid that was giving off a pleasant aroma, and Li Yuanjiu carried the bowl to the bed as he said, "Drink this medicine, Master."

Han Li took a glance at the medicine, and he could see that the spiritual qi fluctuations that it contained weren't insignificant, indicating that the ingredients used had to have been quite precious for a Foundation Establishment cultivator.

"Put it here, I'll drink it later," Han Li said as he slowly stood up from the bed.

"Master, you're carrying severe injuries right now, you need to rest!" Li Yuanjiu hurriedly said.

"Don't worry about me, I know my own body," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

He had already grown accustomed to his body, so he was able to move in it just fine.

After taking a moment to gather his bearings, Han Li made his way out of the room.

Li Yuanjiu couldn't help but feel as if his master were acting a little strange, but he didn't dare to say anything as he set down the bowl of medicine and hurriedly followed Han Li outside.

Upon emerging from the dilapidated temple, Han Li discovered that it was situated on a mountaintop that was surrounded by more lush mountains, presenting a piece of fine scenery.

However, this mountain range was rather secluded, and the calls of wild animals could occasionally be heard, while the world's origin qi here was also quite sparse.

Han Li released his spiritual sense to inspect the surrounding area.

For some reason, even though this body's cultivation base was very much lackluster, it seemed to have inherited much of Han Li's enormous spiritual sense, and he was quickly able to assess everything within a radius of several thousand kilometers.

However, the entire area was filled with more mountain ranges, and he was unable to ascertain his current location.

"Are you alright, Master?" Li Yuanjiu asked as he followed Han Li outside.

"Where is this place, Yuanjiu?" Han Li asked.

"Th... This is the Mulan Mountain Range where we've always been cultivating. Why would you ask this, Master?" Li Yuanjiu asked with a puzzled expression.

"My memories are a little jumbled right now, perhaps due to my injuries," Han Li explained.

A concerned look appeared on Li Yuanjiu's face upon hearing this, but before he could say anything, Han Li continued, "Don't worry, it's not a major problem. Let me ask you this: which immortal region is this Mulan Mountain Range situated in?"

"The Mulan Mountain Range is situated on the Bramble Wood Continent of the Golden Origin Immortal Region," Li Yuanjiu replied.

Han Li had never heard of the Golden Origin Immortal Region before, but it was definitely outside of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

With that in mind, a contemplative look appeared in his eyes.

He cast his gaze to the left to find that the Mantra Treasured Axis projection had also followed him outside, and close to 100 of its Time Dao Runes had already faded.

"Master, I think you should rest. After you recover from your injuries, we can go back and exact our vengeance on those bastards!" Li Yuanjiu said as he gritted his teeth in fury.

He and Ling Yunzi were from a sect by the name of the Iron Beast Sect in the Mulan Mountain Range, and Ling Yunzi was the son of one of the sect's elders, but unfortunately, his aptitude was quite mediocre, and he was unable to reach the Core Formation Stage, something that he had received much disdain and heckling for over the years.

Li Yuanjiu was an abandoned infant that Ling Yunzi had picked up during one of his outings, and he had raised Li Yuanjiu before accepting the boy as his disciple.

Ling Yunzi knew that his own cultivation aptitude was mediocre, so he gave all of his cultivation resources to Li Yuanjiu, but unfortunately, Li Yuanjiu's aptitude wasn't much better, and he was still stuck at the Qi Condensation Stage.

Even though they were master and disciple, they were just as close as any father and son.

Back when Ling Yunzi's father was still alive, he and Li Yuanjiu were still able to get by in the sect, but several years ago, Ling Yunzi's father had perished during a battle against a formidable foe.

As a result, Ling Yunzi and Li Yuanjiu's statuses in the sect had plummeted, and they were deprived of all cultivation resources before being kicked out of the sect altogether.

Thus, the two of them had become itinerant cultivators.

Li Yuanjiu's aptitude wasn't anything special, but he worked extremely hard in his cultivation, and he had recently reached the pinnacle of the Qi Condensation Stage, bringing him to the cusp of the Foundation Establishment Stage.

The two of them had ventured into a perilous area to search for a type of spirit plant that was very helpful for making breakthroughs, and they had searched for about a month before finally finding the spirit plant, then went through a great deal of effort to slay the demon beast that was guarding the plant.

During the battle, Ling Yunzi had sustained some severe injuries.

However, a group of Iron Beast Sect cultivators had arrived on the scene just then, and they were led by the son of another elder who had constantly been at odds with Ling Yunzi back when he was in the sect.

Those people had taken the spirit plant, and in his attempt to stop them, Ling Yunzi's injuries had been even further compounded.

If it weren't for a life-saving talisman that he had been carrying, he and Li Yuanjiu would've most likely been slain right there and then.

Han Li didn't have much of Ling Yunzi's memories left in his mind, but they were enough to tell a story, and he heaved a faint sigh as he said, "The path of cultivation is a cruel and heartless one where only the strong get to live, while the weak are left to die. Your cultivation base is insufficient right now, so don't think about revenge. You'll only be throwing your life away for nothing."

"Yes, Master," Li Yuanjiu replied as he lowered his head with a dejected expression.

Han Li turned to the boy and swept his spiritual sense through the boy's body, upon which he was surprised to discover that Li Yuanjiu possessed a false spiritual root just like himself, one that possessed four out of five attributes, with only the metal attribute missing. [1]

Hence, it was no wonder that his rate of cultivation progress was so slow. However, just like Han Li, his spiritual sense was also quite formidable for his cultivation, and Han Li couldn't help but wonder if this was just a coincidence or if this meeting had been pre-ordained by fate.

"Yuanjiu, I haven't been able to help you much in your cultivation, and you've been made to suffer by my side all this time. I don't have much time left, and I'm going to bestow upon you a secret technique now. Make sure to work hard in your cultivation and live up to the high hopes I have for you," Han Li suddenly said.

Li Yuanjiu was horrified to hear this, and he hurriedly waved his hands in response. "No, Master! I don't want any secret technique, I just want you to live!"

A stern look appeared on Han Li's face as he said, "Yuanjiu, cultivators like ourselves are constantly attempting to defy the natural order, but my time in this world has already run out, and heaven and earth can no longer tolerate my existence. If you want to make something out of yourself and do me proud, then listen up."

Li Yuanjiu still wanted to say something further, but Han Li didn't give him another chance to speak, sweeping a sleeve through the air to release a burst of spiritual light that vanished into the boy's head in a flash.

[1]. For more information on false spiritual roots, please refer to RMJI Chapter 127: Knowledge on Spiritual Roots.

[Back]

Chapter 370: Karma and Fate

The burst of spiritual light scattered in Li Yuanjiu's mind into countless tiny runes that revolved around his head, containing none other than the Great Development Technique. [1]

Li Yuanjiu's entire body instantly stiffened, and before long, his eyes rolled over into the back of his head as he fell unconscious and collapsed to the ground.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of spiritual light that picked up Li Yuanjiu before carrying him into the dilapidated temple.

"It seems you and I were fated to meet here, and I'm temporarily borrowing the body of your master, so I'll give you this Great Development Technique as compensation," Han Li said in an indifferent voice before preparing to fly away.

However, a hint of surprise then appeared on his face, and he discovered upon a closer inspection that Li Yuanjiu also possessed a remarkable spirit physique, except it hadn't yet been awakened.

Following a closer examination, a hint of intrigue arose in Han Li's eyes, and he swept his sleeve through the air once again to send another streak of spiritual light flying into Li Yuanjiu's body.

"So be it. It's not every day that I get to meet someone so similar to myself, so I'll give you a bit more assistance."

The streak of spiritual light split up into two in Li Yuanjiu's mind, and one of them exploded into countless tiny runes that depicted another cultivation art, namely Heavenbearing Devil Arts. [2]

This cultivation art was something that Han Li had obtained from Man Huzi, [3] and at the time, he had promised to find Man Huzi a disciple so that the Heavenbearing Devil Arts wouldn't be lost, but he had never been able to find a suitable candidate.

On top of that, he had been busy preparing for a Deity Transformation Stage breakthrough at the time, so he had set the matter aside, and even now, he still hadn't fulfilled that promise.

As it turned out, Li Yuanjiu's spirit physique was perfect for the Heavenbearing Devil Arts.

As for the other streak of spiritual light, it shrank down into a tiny speck of light and hid itself in a corner of Li Yuanjiu's mind.

That speck of light contained another cultivation art that came from the same origins as the Provenance True Devil Arts and the Heavenbearing Devil Arts.

However, the seal on it would only be undone once Li Yuanjiu reached the Deity Transformation Stage someday.

However, the path of cultivation was always one that was fraught with peril and unpredictability, so the chances of Li Yuanjiu reaching the Deity Transformation Stage before his lifespan ran out were slim to none, even with the assistance of the two cultivation arts, and his mediocre aptitude certainly wasn't going to help his cause, but Han Li had already done everything that he could for the boy.

He hadn't intended to offer the boy any assistance, but he couldn't help but be moved by Li Yuanjiu's devotion to his master.

With that in mind, Han Li heaved an internal sigh, shaking his head as he directed his gaze away from Li Yuanjiu.

Han Li cast his gaze into the distance, then made a hand seal as he released his enormous spiritual sense over the surrounding area once again.

All of the world's origin qi in a radius of several dozen kilometers instantly converged to form a white cloud.

This was a secret technique that he had previously learned, allowing him to forcibly draw upon the world's origin qi with his spiritual sense.

This secret technique was very taxing on one's spiritual sense, but this body possessed far too little magic power, and Ling Yunzi wasn't carrying any storage tools, either, presumably having lost them during the prior battle, so if he didn't use this secret technique, then he wouldn't even be able to fly.

Han Li drifted up into the air before landing on the cloud, and the white cloud churned slightly before hurtling away at an incredible speed as a streak of white light.

The matters concerning Li Yuanjiu were largely inconsequential. What was important for him was to find out as much about this place as he could as there had to have been some reason that he had ended up here.

With that in mind, he began to scour the surrounding area with both his eyes and his spiritual sense, but after flying for a while, he discovered that the entire area was completely mundane and unremarkable.

He cast his gaze to the left, where the Mantra Treasured Axis projection remained hovering by his side, and at this point, close to half of the Time Dao Runes on its surface had already faded.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he made a hand seal, upon which the white cloud beneath him accelerated significantly.

A short while later, he suddenly stopped in his tracks, then cast his gaze toward an obscure valley down below.

On a mountain face deep within the valley was a giant purple flower the size of a millstone. Its petals were extremely large and thick, and they were of a very vibrant reddish-purple color.

There were also some red feelers among the flower petals, at the top of which were a series of fist-sized water droplets that were giving off a sweet and fragrant aroma.

Han Li descended in front of the giant purple flower atop his white cloud, and an intrigued look appeared on his face.

This flower was clearly a spirit plant, and the aura that it was giving off was very similar to that of the Blood Crystal Lotus Root.

The purple flower was swaying gently in the wind, and Han Li hesitated momentarily before flicking a finger through the air, sending a gust of fierce wind sweeping toward the flower.

The giant purple flower shuddered, and all of its feelers instantly shot forth like lightning, elongating significantly before intertwining to form a large net that descended upon Han Li.

Of course, Han Li wasn't going to fall prey to something like this, and his white cloud shot back like lightning to evade the flower's feelers.

The feelers waved around in the air while the flower's petals began moving like a giant mouth, producing a faint screeching sound that expressed its rage and frustration.

After thrashing around for a while, the feelers quickly shrank back down to their original length, while the purple flower petals also stopped moving.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and a contemplative look appeared in his eyes.

The flower was indeed quite a remarkable spirit plant, but there was nothing else particularly special about it.

Thus, he promptly departed, flying out of the valley before continuing onward.

As he did so, he was surprised to discover more and more of those giant purple flowers appearing in the mountain range, but none of them were being picked.

He was rather perplexed by this, but he didn't stop to investigate. Instead, he continued to make more hand seals to further accelerate the speed of his flight.

Judging from the number of Time Dao Runes that remained lit on his Mantra Treasured Axis, he didn't have much time left.

After flying for a while longer, a look of surprise and elation suddenly appeared on Han Li's face, and he quickly drew to a halt in front of a col.

Within the col was a cluster of buildings, and there were many restrictions that were flashing with spiritual light set up in the area. There were also some streaks of light flying through the air, and this was a sect.

From Ling Yunzi's memories, Han Li learned that this was none other than the Iron Beast Sect.

He quickly began to chant an incantation while making a hand seal, and his spiritual sense surged out of his body, forming a series of invisible ripples around him.

All of the surrounding world's origin qi also converged to form a layer of transparent spiritual light around him, following which he quickly descended onto a plaza in the sect.

He continued to search through Ling Yunzi's memories while casting his gaze toward a mountain to his right, and atop that mountain stood an azure pavilion, which had the brightest of all restrictions in the sect around it.

This was the Iron Beast Sect's scripture library, and it contained all types of cultivation arts and scriptures.

Han Li flew toward the pavilion before quickly descending in front of it, but his brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the restriction around the building.

The restriction wasn't particularly advanced, and under normal circumstances, he would've been able to bypass or remove it with ease.

However, the magic power in this body was simply far too lackluster, and his immense spiritual sense wasn't going to help him much when it came to bypassing restrictions.

Right at this moment, a streak of light arrived from afar, descending in front of the scripture library as well.

The streak of light then faded to reveal a middle-aged man who was the early-Core Formation Stage, and there was a look of haughtiness and arrogance about him.

Before Han Li even had a chance to take a closer look, his body abruptly shuddered, and an overwhelming sense of fury and resentment welled up in his heart.

This man was the very same person who had severely wounded Ling Yunzi not long ago.

Even though Ling Yunzi had already perished, what remained of his will in this body still harbored intense resentment toward this man.

"Don't worry, I've been using your body, so I'm naturally obliged to fulfill some of your wishes," Han Li mused internally as he cast a cold gaze toward the middle-aged man.

All of a sudden, the man shuddered as a chill ran down his spine, and he hurriedly looked around, but was unable to find anything.

He then swept his spiritual sense through the area several times, but to no avail, once again.

"What the hell!" he murmured to himself with tightly furrowed brows, then raised a hand to release an azure talisman into the restriction.

At the same time, he demanded in an arrogant voice, "Open the restriction! I've come here to retrieve something under orders from the sect master!"

A gray-robed elderly man appeared within the restriction, and a hint of disdain flashed through his eyes, but he then quickly put on a warm smile as he said, "Please wait a moment, I'll open the restriction for you right away, Administrator Wang."

He pulled out a badge as he spoke, and a burst of light shot out of the badge, upon which an opening appeared in the restriction.

"Can you not have done that a little faster? How slow can you be?" the middle-aged man harrumphed coldly before flying into the scripture library without even sparing a glance at the gray-robed elderly man.

The gray-robed elderly man's expression darkened slightly as he swept his badge through the air, and the opening on the restrictions was instantly sealed.

However, what they had failed to notice was that a transparent figure had also flown into the scripture library in the instant right before the opening was sealed.

[1]. For more information on the Great Development Technique, please refer to RMJI Chapter 232: Great Development Technique.

[Back]

[2]. For more information on the Heavenbearing Devil Arts, please refer to RMJI Chapter 457: Heavenbearing Devil Arts.

[Back]

[3]. For more information on Man Huzi, please refer to https://a-record-of-a-mortal-is-journey-to-immortality.fandom.com/wiki/Man_Huzi.

[Back]

Chapter 371: Illusion or Reality

The transparent figure was naturally none other than Han Li in Ling Yunzi's body, and after following the middle-aged man through the light barrier, he didn't immediately pursue him.

Instead, he remained on the spot and looked up at the pavilion before him. At the same time, he released his spiritual sense to examine the surrounding area, upon which his eyes immediately lit up.

Meanwhile, the middle-aged man quickly made his way over to the entrance of the pavilion, and he was just about to enter the building when Han Li abruptly directed his gaze toward him.

At the same time, a layer of translucent light appeared on Han Li's glabella, and a tiny translucent sword projection shot forth, covering a distance of thousands of feet in the blink of an eye before piercing straight into the middle-aged man's mind.

The entire process lasted no more than a second, and it was extremely silent and discreet.

All of a sudden, the middle-aged man stopped cold in his tracks, following which his eyes bulged, and he tipped forward without any warning before falling to the ground.

"Administrator Wang! Are you alright?"

The gray-robed elderly man hurriedly approached the middle-aged man before lifting him up from the ground, only to discover that his breathing had ceased, and there was no longer any hint of vitality left in his body.

After taking a moment to compose himself, the gray-robed man swept his gaze through the surrounding area while also releasing his spiritual sense to examine the entire area encompassed within the restriction.

However, with his cultivation base, it was naturally impossible for him to see through Han Li's concealment technique, and after a brief moment of hesitation, he suddenly yelled, "Help!"

A burst of commotion instantly rang out within the scripture library, and several cultivators emerged from the building. Upon spotting the gray-robed elderly man and the lifeless middle-aged man, they immediately had a rough idea of what had happened, and everyone erupted into a blind panic.

Han Li paid no heed to these people as he drifted calmly through them before entering the scripture library and releasing his spiritual sense once again.

The scripture library was split up into three floors, with the bottom two floors containing some miscellaneous books, including things like travel journals and illustrated handbooks.

None of these things were particularly valuable, so the bottom two floors were unguarded, and there were no restrictions set up there, either.

As for the third floor, it contained some cultivation arts, and the entire level was enshrouded within an intricate restriction.

Han Li naturally had no interest in those cultivation arts, and he began reading through the scriptures on the first and second floors.

At this point, everyone in the scripture library had already rushed outside, so Han Li didn't have to worry about being noticed.

He had intentionally chosen to kill the middle-aged man at the entrance of the scripture library to draw everyone outside, and he quickly read through one scripture after another, learning a great deal about the Bramble Wood Continent in the process, but this information wasn't very useful to him.

He turned to the left to find that fewer than a quarter of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis projection remained lit.

He didn't know what was going to happen once all of the Time Dao Runes were snuffed out, but he had a rough idea of what was going to transpire.

However, he had no time to worry about things like this, and he quickly withdrew his gaze before continuing in his reading.

A short while later, he suddenly stopped what he was doing, then cast his gaze toward a book that was slightly yellow with age.

This was a travel journal written by a cultivator who enjoyed exploring the continent, and an image on one of the book's pages had caught Han Li's attention.

The image depicted a bald and browless golden figure with a pair of long golden feelers on its head, as well as some golden hooked spikes on its body, presenting a fearsome sight to behold.

This was quite similar to a Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch.

After the illustration came a passage of text.

"Today, I traveled to the Golden Flame Mountain Range and encountered an almighty battle that shook the heavens and laid waste to the earth. I presume this was a battle between immortals, but thankfully, I was able to get away in time to avoid a terrible fate. This creature was one of the two immortals in the battle, but I wasn't able to identify it..."

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this.

This clearly wasn't the same Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch as the one that he had before, so perhaps it was another one.

Up to this point, he still hadn't managed to recover his Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch, and he had invested a great deal of effort into trying to recover it, but hadn't been able to gather any useful leads thus far.

After committing this snippet of information to memory, Han Li didn't delay any further as he continued to read through the book, but there was no further information about the Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch.

This left him feeling a little disappointed, but time was of the essence, and he quickly picked up another scripture about spirit plants.

After flipping through a few pages, he stopped once again.

On the page that he had stopped on was a vibrant purple flower, the very same type as the one that he had seen in that mountain range earlier.

"The Spirit Devouring Flower attracts living beings with its aroma before devouring them for sustenance. The flower can be used as an ingredient for body refinement pills, but it contains a type of corpse poison that must be expelled through the use of a secret technique before it can be used as a medicinal ingredient, and the secret technique is one that's quite difficult to execute."

An enlightened look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

It was no wonder that the purple flowers appeared to have been quite abundant in spiritual qi, but they were left alone without anyone willing to pick them.

Right as he was about to keep reading, a burst of buzzing suddenly rang out nearby, and Han Li turned to discover that all of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis projection had already faded.

Immediately thereafter, the projection began to glow brightly while quickly taking on a more substantial form, and it was also rapidly revolving and giving off a loud buzzing sound.

Han Li cast his gaze outside, upon which a hint of intrigue appeared in his eyes.

The buzzing sound was extremely loud in his ears, but it seemed that none of the people outside were able to hear it at all.

Despite how rapidly the Mantra Treasured Axis was revolving, it didn't cause any harm to its surroundings, and it seemed to have been somehow detached from this reality.

All of a sudden, a speck of black light appeared at the center of the vortex, and it rapidly expanded, staining the entire axis black in the blink of an eye.

As the Mantra Treasured Axis continued to revolve, a black vortex that was very similar in appearance to the green vortex on the wall of light emerged, and all of this had taken place in an instant.

Before Han Li had a chance to react, a burst of enormous suction force erupted out of the vortex, latching onto his soul and sucking it out of Ling Yunzi's body. All the while, he was completely powerless to resist.

The final thing that he saw was a glimpse of Ling Yunzi's body, which abruptly shuddered before disintegrating to countless specks of light that dissipated into nothingness.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li felt his vision go black, and his consciousness began to fade.

After an indeterminate period of time, he gradually awakened and opened his eyes.

Once again, he was greeted by the sight of the wall of light, and the black vortex on its surface flashed a few times before vanishing into thin air.

The wall of light itself also quickly disintegrated, and everything returned to normal.

Looking at the familiar cave abode around him, a mixture of elation and disappointment flashed through Han Li's eyes.

He was very glad to be back, but at the same time, he felt rather disappointed that he hadn't been able to reap any substantial benefits from this phenomenon generated by the Heaven Controlling Vial.

He immediately closed his eyes and quickly thought back over the entirety of the strange out-of-body experience that had just transpired, trying to find something useful from it, but ultimately, his efforts proved to be futile.

He heaved a faint sigh, then made a hand seal, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

As expected, the 360 Time Dao Runes on the surface of the axis had all been snuffed out, just like last time that wall of light had been conjured up.

The golden time law thread was wound around the Mantra Treasured Axis, but it had also become very dim.

Han Li made a beckoning motion with one hand, stowing the time law thread into his own body, and right at this moment, a loud thunderclap rang out in front of him, following which Daoist Xie emerged amid a flurry of golden lightning.

"Congratulations on finally mastering the laws of time, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie congratulated.

"Even with the assistance of a second-tier dao pill, I was still very fortunate to have been able to master the laws of time. As one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time are truly profound. By the way, you saw everything that happened here just now, right?" Han Li asked.

"What are you referring to?" Daoist Xie asked in a puzzled voice. "All I saw is that you seemed to have spaced out for a moment after conjuring up that wall of light. Is there something wrong?"

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, but instead of offering an explanation, he remained silent as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Judging from Daoist Xie's answer, the 360 seconds that his soul had spent in the Golden Origin Immortal Region seemed to have only been the equivalent of an instant in the real world.

In that case, did this so-called Golden Origin Immortal Region truly exist? And was there actually such a sect as the Iron Beast Sect?

On top of that, were Ling Yunzi and Li Yuanjiu real people, or were they just figments of his imagination?

If all of that had been just an illusion, then why was it that it felt so incredibly real?

Han Li's brows became slightly furrowed, and he was unable to make sense of what had just transpired.

A long while later, he shook his head with a wry smile.

What had just happened had been extremely peculiar, and he couldn't wrap his head around it at the moment, so he would just have to think about it at a later date.

Chapter 372: Unexpected Gains

Han Li heaved a faint sigh and wasted no further time contemplating this topic.

Seeing as he had already mastered the laws of time, his top priorities now were to secure the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique and make a breakthrough to the Golden Immortal Stage.

With that in mind, he put on his Transient Guild mask, then summoned the array plate projection, only to find that his Spirit Refinement Technique acquisition mission still hadn't received any responses.

He heaved a faint sigh, then stowed the mask away, but he wasn't overly disappointed.

After all, this was a matter of luck, and at the very least, it seemed that he wasn't going to enter that deranged state again anytime soon.

At this point, he was only one immortal acupoint away from reaching the Golden Immortal Stage, and if he could make the breakthrough, then that would significantly increase his chances of survival in the Immortal Realm.

However, he still had no idea how to complete the breakthrough.

A contemplative look appeared on his face, and he flipped a hand over to produce the gray stone slab that contained the Great Universe Origin Arts.

He had released a mission in the Transient Guild searching for the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts, but that mission hadn't received any responses up to this point, either.

He stared at the stone slab for a moment, then abruptly rose to his feet before making his way outside.

Just now, he had decided to cultivate the Great Universe Origin Arts. Even though he only had the first half, perhaps it would provide him with some inspiration with regard to how he could break through the final immortal acupoint.

Even if that didn't prove to be the case, the Big Dipper Origin Arts had significantly enhanced his physical prowess, so cultivating the more complete Great Universe Origin Arts certainly couldn't have been detrimental.

Han Li handed his Heaven Controlling Vial to his giant ape puppet, instructing it to continue watering the spirit plants in his medicine garden, then flew out of his cave abode and arrived on a mountain at the center of the island.

This was the highest point on the entire island, and from there, everything on the island was laid bare before his eyes.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of azure sword qi, which shaved off a small chunk of the mountain summit to create a flat and smooth stone platform.

After that, he swept both sleeves through the air to release a series of materials, all of which were giving off bursts of starpower.

These materials had virtually all been acquired from Tao Yu's portly guard. That man had also been cultivating starpower-based abilities, and he had also been a late-True Immortal cultivator, so he possessed a huge supply of starpower materials.

From there, Han Li opened his mouth to produce a ball of azure flames that enveloped the mountaintop, quickly melting it down into a soft and malleable texture.

He then made a hand seal, and a series of materials came flying out before landing in the azure flame, where they were quickly refined and fused as one with the mountain.

The originally mundane and unremarkable mountain quickly began to glow brightly, and four or five days passed by in the blink of an eye.

At this point, the mountain summit had already undergone a complete makeover. The mountain had already been cylindrical in shape, but it had been transformed into a pagoda, resembling a giant stone platform that was giving off radiant blue starlight.

There were also numerous runes that depicted all types of star designs engraved onto the stone platform, forming an extremely complex array.

Everything here was very similar to the Star Gathering Platform back in the Origin Realm Temple, except it was far more grand and spectacular.

Han Li had created the array on the stone platform by referencing the Star Gathering Array on the Star Gathering Platform, while also infusing elements of star array design that he had mastered over the years.

The portly guard's storage tool contained some very intricate star arrays, as well as some cultivation arts and secret techniques related to stars. In order to refine the Seven Bright Star Rings, Han Li had previously taken some time to study those arrays, cultivation arts, and secret techniques.

A Seven Bright Starlight Array had been integrated into the array on the stone platform, so its ability to gather starlight would've undoubtedly been superior to that of the Star Gathering Platform of the Origin Realm Temple.

Most importantly, this Seven Bright Starlight Array was closely linked to the Seven Bright Star Rings, so when using this array, Han Li could draw upon the power of the Seven Bright Star Rings to enhance the array's effects.

After doing all of this, Han Li descended onto the platform, then gave a pleased nod.

He sat down onto the ground with his legs crossed, then closed his eyes as he began to study the gray stone slab in his hand.

Before long, day had transitioned into night, and countless stars appeared in the night sky.

Han Li opened his eyes before casting his gaze upward, then swept a sleeve through the air to release eight blue crystals, which were giving off a collective aura that was very similar to that of the Starwash Stone.

These crystals were called Starheaven Stones, and just like Starwash Stone, they contained extremely pure starpower, except the starpower in Starheaven Stones was far more abundant than in Starwash Stones, making them an even superior energy source for star arrays.

These Starheaven Stones had also been acquired from the portly guard's storage tool, but there weren't many of them, so they weren't going to last very long.

However, that wasn't a problem as he had already released a Starheaven Stone acquisition mission in the Transient Guild. Starheaven Stones were quite precious, but not as rare as dao pill ingredients, so it shouldn't be too difficult to acquire them.

The eight Starheaven Stones were accurately embedded into the eight slots around the array, and bursts of blue light instantly emerged within those slots before quickly flowing over the array on the stone platform.

Before long, the entire array had lit up with dazzling blue radiance, while the stone platform had taken on a translucent appearance.

The blue light that was radiating from the platform projected a series of star diagrams in the air, and these diagrams were slowly revolving around the stone platform, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

Right at this moment, the starlight in the sky abruptly brightened, then came raining down from above, forming an incredibly thick pillar of light that converged toward the stone platform before encompassing the platform in its entirety.

This burst of starpower was at least 10 times as formidable as what the Star Gathering Platform had been able to summon, and Han Li nodded to himself with a pleased expression, clearly quite happy with his own handiwork.

However, this level of starpower still wasn't quite sufficient for his current needs, so he made a hand seal and began to chant an incantation, upon which the Seven Bright Star Rings flew out of his body before hovering above his head.

As soon as the seven rings were summoned, the array on the stone platform instantly brightened considerably, and seven huge spots of blue light appeared, each of which was around the size of a millstone with countless runes flashing within them.

The seven spots of starlight appeared to have been arranged in a haphazard fashion, but in reality, they were organized in the arrangement of a profound array.

Right at this moment, the Seven Bright Star Rings also descended out of the sky and onto the seven spots of blue light on the platform.

The blue light radiating from the stone platform brightened even further, while the pillar of starlight descending from the heavens also brightened considerably.

Bursts of starpower were cascading down like a waterfall, producing a massive commotion, and only upon seeing this did Han Li close his eyes before channeling the Great Universe Origin Arts.

This cultivation art also contained the manifestation method for the first seven profound acupoints, and it was far more complex and profound than the Big Dipper Origin Arts.

A dull thump rang out as the pillar of starlight split up into seven smaller pillars of light that surged into Han Li's body.

Even though the pillars of starlight had shrunk down, the starlight that they contained had become even more concentrated, virtually forming substantial pillars.

Seven specks of blue light instantly appeared on Han Li's body, and those were the seven spots where the seven pillars of starlight had descended upon.

Enormous starpower surged into the seven profound acupoints, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as a pained look appeared on his face.

A burst of tearing pain immediately shot through the profound acupoints that had already opened up, and it was as if there were countless steel needles poking around inside.

He took a deep breath and closed his eyes, and his brows quickly unfurrowed again.

This level of pain was still tolerable to him.

He cycled through a series of different hand seals, and the starlight cascading down from the heavens became even brighter as it flooded into his body.

A vast expanse of blue mist emerged to encompass the entire stone platform, and Han Li's body was also enveloped in starlight.

The night passed by in the blink of an eye, and as the sun began to rise, the stars in the sky quickly faded, while the starpower descending from the heavens also vanished.

At this point, Han Li's robes were drenched in blood, and his complexion was also a little pale.

He opened his eyes, and he was looking a little weary, but there was a hint of excitement on his face.

The seven profound acupoints on his body had clearly become larger than before, while the True Extreme Film that had appeared over his body had also become slightly brighter and denser.

The Big Dipper Origin Arts that he had previously cultivated had only been a simplified version of the Great Universe Origin Arts, and now that he had begun cultivating the latter, the profound acupoints that had already been opened up in his body had expanded even further, while his physical prowess had also been enhanced.

He clenched his fists tightly as he sensed the changes that had taken place in his body, and even though he had only been cultivating for one night, his True Extreme Physique was already displaying some measure of improvement.

If he could open up all 18 profound acupoints, then his physical prowess would undoubtedly be enhanced even further.

He slowly exhaled as he suppressed the excitement in his heart, then took a restorative pill before closing his eyes to meditate.

A gentle azure glow appeared over his entire body, forming a ball of azure light.

It didn't take long before night arrived once again, and the ball of azure light faded to reveal Han Li, who had already made a full recovery at this point.

He opened his eyes and took a glance up at the starry night sky, then immediately activated the array once again.

The array on the stone platform was activated, quickly drawing down rays of starlight that enveloped his entire body, and Han Li immediately began channeling his cultivation art to absorb the starpower cascading down upon him.

Over a year passed by in the blink of an eye, and Han Li had refined his seven existing profound acupoints once again using the method described in the Great Universe Origin Arts.

At this moment, he was seated with his legs crossed on the stone platform with blue light flashing over his entire body.

His seven profound acupoints had become around twice as bright as before, while his physical prowess had also been significantly enhanced, and his True Extreme Film was looking even denser and more radiant.

A hint of excitement appeared on Han Li's face as he felt all of these changes in his own body.

The physical enhancements were naturally quite welcome, but that wasn't what he was excited about.

During this past year of cultivation, he discovered that the immortal acupoint in his body that overlapped with his existing profound acupoints had also expanded significantly and also become more resilient, allowing them to take in more of the world's origin qi.

This was very much a pleasant surprise, and he had never heard of immortal acupoints being able to undergo changes after they were opened.

Chapter 373: Response

Han Li took a deep breath to compose himself.

He had only made an initial foray into his cultivation of the Great Universe Origin Arts. Furthermore, he had already previously opened up the first seven profound acupoints, and that was why he had been able to progress so quickly, but the remaining 11 profound acupoints most likely weren't going to be so easy to cultivate.

With that in mind, Han Li exhaled before closing his eyes again.

The array on the stone platform began to operate once again, drawing a vast expanse of starlight down from the heavens and funneling it into Han Li's body.

Five years passed by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, a thunderous commotion suddenly rang out from the island, resonating across the entire heavens.

In the next instant, a glowing blue figure rose up into the sky from the island before flying around in the air like a prowling dragon.

All of the space within a radius of hundreds of kilometers around the island was buzzing and trembling incessantly, while massive waves swept over the surface of the sea, and all of the clouds in the sky were also scattered far and wide.

Some time later, the commotion ceased, and the blue figure also stopped in their tracks, revealing none other than Han Li.

At this moment, his entire body was enveloped within a translucent blue film of light that almost had a substantial form.

The film of light was adhered to the surface of his skin, and it was very similar to the True Extreme Film that had arisen following his attainment of his True Extreme Physique.

At this point, it was more appropriate to call it a suit of True Extreme Armor rather than a True Extreme Film.

Numerous streaks of blue light were surging incessantly over the film of light, making it appear as if there were countless stars orbiting around Han Li's body.

On top of that, there were 18 specks of blue light shimmering on Han Li's chest and abdomen.

After five years of arduous cultivation, he had finally mastered the first half of the Great Universe Origin Arts.

Even he was rather surprised by how quickly he had been able to master this cultivation art.

Given his past experience, he had originally predicted that it would've taken him a considerable amount of time to master this cultivation art, a projected time span of at least several dozen years, yet during his cultivation, he discovered that all of the bottlenecks that he thought he would encounter simply failed to pose any resistance, and he was able to open up one profound acupoint after another with ease.

All of these profound acupoints overlapped with the immortal acupoints that he had previously opened.

In retrospect, he could only speculate that perhaps the immortal acupoints that he had previously opened made it easier for him to subsequently cultivate profound acupoints, and that was why he was able to master the first half of the Great Universe Origin Arts in such a short time.

Initially, he had been concerned that he wouldn't have sufficient Starheaven Stones, but as things turned out, he had some to spare.

What was even more encouraging to him was that the immortal acupoints that overlapped with his profound acupoints had been significantly bolstered and expanded.

Right at this moment, Han Li let loose a low roar as he threw a punch at the sea down below.

A burst of tremendous force erupted out of his fist before striking the surface of the sea, and a massive fist-sized black hole was smashed into the sea, parting all of the seawater around it.

The force unleashed by Han Li's punch pierced straight through the waves before slamming into the seabed, creating another unfathomably deep hole, at the bottom of which faint glimmers of red light could be seen.

Han Li then unclenched his fist before bringing his hand down in a chopping motion, and the sea down below was parted once again as a massive trench emerged.

Once again, the seabed was also split apart, forming an enormous rift that was just as unfathomably deep as the hole from before.

Han Li slowly withdrew his palm and gave a pleased nod upon seeing this.

Even though he had only mastered the first half of the Great Universe Origin Arts, his already extremely formidable physical body had been significantly enhanced.

He had only put less than 30% of his strength into the two strikes that he had unleashed just now, yet they were already extremely formidable blows.

The True Extreme Film around Han Li's body faded at his behest, and he flew back down onto the island, quickly descending onto the stone platform.

He then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that enveloped the entire stone platform, and a burst of dull rumbling rang out as the stone platform was separated from the mountaintop.

After that, Han Li began to chant an incantation, and the stone platform rapidly shrank down before being stowed away.

Even though he had already mastered the first half of the Great Universe Origin Arts, this stone platform was something that had taken him a great deal of effort to construct, so he naturally wasn't just going to discard it.

After doing all of this, Han Li flew back to his cave abode and arrived in his bedroom.

During these past five years, he had been going through a constant cycle of cultivating the Great Universe Origin Arts at night and recovering from his injuries during the day, so it had already been a very long time since he had taken a proper rest.

Now that he had successfully mastered the cultivation art, he was finally allowing himself to relax, and a wave of exhaustion instantly swept over him.

Before long, he fell into a deep sleep on his bed, and only after a day and a night did he awaken before emerging from his bedroom, completely reinvigorated.

The first thing that he did was check on the medicine garden, where he discovered that all of the spirit plants were thriving as usual.

The giant ape puppet had followed Han Li's instructions, using most of the spirit liquid produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial on the primary bean, and at this point, it had already sprouted, so Han Li could look forward to another harvest of Dao Warriors soon.

From there, Han Li explored all of the other parts of his cave abode briefly before arriving in his secret chamber, where he sat down and began to consider his future plans.

At the moment, his top priorities were to find the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique and make a breakthrough to the Golden Immortal Stage.

However, both of these objectives were rather difficult to achieve in the Black Wind Sea, and he couldn't help but be tempted to leave this secluded region.

Several centuries had already passed by, so the efforts that the Northern Glacial Immortal Region was taking to hunt him down would've surely lessened significantly. On top of that, he had become far more powerful than back when he faced Tao Yu in battle.

At his current level of power, he was confident that he would be able to take care of Tao Yu even without Daoist Xie's assistance.

As soon as this thought appeared in his mind, it immediately began to take root.

Even though he had made significant strides in his cultivation during his time in the Black Wind Sea, it had also been a very miserable experience.

After some extensive consideration, Han Li decided not to leave the Black Wind Sea for now. At the very least, he had to get a good grasp on the situation in the outside world first.

With that in mind, he put on his Transient Guild mask and made a routine examination of the missions that he had previously released.

All of a sudden, an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

He had received a response on his Spirit Refinement Technique acquisition mission.

He immediately made a hand seal, and a burst of azure light emerged from the passage of text detailing the mission.

Around 15 minutes later, the burst of azure light flew out into Han Li's secret chamber, where it took on the form of a gray figure.

The figure was dressed in a gray cloak with an azure cat mask on their face that carried the number "16".

The figure behind the mask inspected Han Li with a sharp and piercing gaze, while Han Li cupped his fist in a salute and said, "Greetings, Fellow Daoist."

The gray figure merely nodded in response.

"You've taken on my mission, so I presume you already know what I want, right?" Han Li asked.

"There's no need to be so ambiguous about it, Fellow Daoist," the gray figure chuckled in a slightly raspy voice. "There are all types of shady dealings taking place in the Transient Guild. You're looking for the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique, isn't that right?"

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he smiled and said, "In that case, I won't waste any time. Do you have the second half of the cultivation art, Fellow Daoist?"

"Of course," the gray figure replied, "Why else would I have taken on your mission?"

"That's good to hear. Can we finalize things today? Rest assured, I'll be sure to offer you satisfactory compensation in exchange for the cultivation art," Han Li immediately replied.

"The compensation that you're offering is indeed quite substantial, but the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique is extremely valuable, so I'm afraid what you're offering won't be sufficient," the gray figure said.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he asked, "In that case, what do you propose, Fellow Daoist?"

"If you really want to obtain the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique, then come to this place in a month, and we'll speak in person," the gray figure replied before specifying a location.

Before Han Li had a chance to reply, the gray figure ended the communication.

Han Li's brows furrowed even tighter upon seeing this, and he slowly removed his mask.

He then flipped a hand over to produce the jade slip that contained the map of the Black Wind Sea, then directed his gaze toward the location specified by the gray figure, which was a location that was truly on the very outskirts of the Black Wind Sea.

Han Li stared at the jade slip in silence, and there was a contemplative look on his face.

Only after sitting in silence for half a day did he raise his head with a determined expression, seemingly having arrived at some type of decision.

After that, he stowed the jade slip away, then rose to his feet and quickly made his way to his medicine garden.

He slowly swept his gaze across his medicine garden, then abruptly began making a string of hand seals to release numerous streaks of azure light.

All of the restrictions in the entire medicine garden were instantly undone, and a series of array tools flew out of the garden before landing in his grasp.

In the blink of an eye, the entire garden had been deconstructed.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li released more streaks of azure light out of his hands to stow away all of the spirit plants in the garden along with the spirit soil beneath them.

The primary bean was also stowed away, and it didn't take long before the entire garden had been cleared out.

After emptying out the medicine garden, he quickly departed and stowed away everything else in the cave abode as well.

Chapter 374: Exchange

Close to an hour later, Han Li appeared in the sky above the island.

With a sweep of his sleeve, a series of restrictions appeared around the island before disintegrating one after another, following which sets of array tools flew out into the open before vanishing up his sleeves.

He had already been cultivating on this island for several centuries without any incident, but during his cultivation, he had triggered astonishing phenomena on quite a few occasions on the island, so it was no longer safe to continue to stay here.

Han Li took one final glance at the island, yet right as he was about to depart, a white demon beast appeared on the surface of the sea down below with a loud splash, then began calling out to him.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he looked down, and he was amused to find that the demon beast was none other than the Pig Dolphin Beast.

He descended toward the Pig Dolphin Beast, and the latter immediately began swimming toward him, splashing through the water with its tail.

"Have you come to say goodbye?" Han Li asked as he stroked the Pig Dolphin Beast's smooth head with a smile on his face.

The Pig Dolphin Beast began rubbing its head gently against the palm of Han Li's hand, and Han Li smiled as he flipped a hand over to produce a pill that he tossed through the air.

The Pig Dolphin Beast's eyes immediately lit up as it opened its mouth to catch the pill.

"I have to thank you for the Hard Ink Crystal that you have me. It really did help me a lot. That pill is my parting gift to you," Han Li said.

The Pig Dolphin Beast faltered slightly upon hearing this, seemingly rather unwilling to part with Han Li.

Han Li gave the Pig Dolphin Beast's head one final pat, then flew away as a streak of azure light, quickly vanishing into the distance.

The Pig Dolphin Beast stared blankly at the direction that Han Li had flown away in, and a long while later, a determined look appeared in its eyes as it sank down into the sea.

……

A month later, on the outskirts of the Black Wind Sea.

A streak of azure light appeared above an island that was close to 10 kilometers in size, then faded to reveal none other than Han Li in his azure tiger mask.

He was meeting someone from the Transient Guild, so he hadn't adopted a disguise and was merely wearing his Transient Guild mask.

He inspected his surroundings briefly, then descended onto the island.

This was an extremely secluded area of the Black Wind Sea, and there were sparse black clouds in the sky, obscuring the light of the sun like a layer of black mist.

These clouds weren't just normal dark clouds, and they were giving off a cold and forbidding aura.

Han Li took a brief glance at the thin black clouds in the sky, then quickly withdrew his gaze before sitting down with his legs crossed, and a layer of azure light quickly surfaced over his body.

This was the location that had been specified by the gray figure, and Han Li had actually already arrived here in secret two days ago.

During the past two days, he had conducted a thorough examination of the nearby area.

He had been invited here by someone completely unfamiliar to him, and they were about to engage in a transaction concerning a forbidden art, so he naturally had to take the necessary precautions.

Before long, close to a day had already passed by.

All of a sudden, Han Li opened his eyes before rising to his feet, then cast his gaze toward a certain direction.

There, on the distant horizon, a speck of gray light appeared before approaching the island at an incredible speed, appearing in the sky above the island in the blink of an eye.

The gray light then faded to reveal a gray-robed figure wearing an azure cat mask that bore the number "16", and it was none other than the same gray figure that Han Li had spoken to earlier.

The two of them examined each other momentarily, following which the cat-masked figure cupped their hand in a salute as they said, "You must be Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11. I am Wildcat 16. Sorry for being late."

"It's fine, I only just got here as well," Han Li replied as he returned the salute.

"That's good, I'm glad to hear I didn't keep you waiting for long," Wildcat 16 said.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he said in an indifferent, "Let's skip the formalities and discuss the matter at hand."

Wildcat's demeanor was very different from during their last communication, and that left Han Li feeling a little perplexed.

"Of course, but this is not the place to talk, so please come with me, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11," Wildcat 16 replied with a nod, then flew through the air as a gray shadow.

Han Li hesitated momentarily before deciding to follow along.

Before long, they had been flying for half a day, and Han Li had remained a set distance behind Wildcat 16 this entire time while also constantly keeping tabs on his surroundings using his spiritual sense.

The further they flew, the denser the black clouds in the sky became, and in the end, the entire sky was filled with dense black clouds that were giving off an astonishing glacial aura.

The sea down below had also been influenced by the yin qi in these black clouds, and the water had been stained black while also releasing bursts of bone-chilling glacial qi that were so formidable that even Body Integration cultivator would've quickly been frozen solid here.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he inspected his surroundings.

Meanwhile, Wildcat 16 continued to fly onward, displaying no indication of stopping.

Han Li was growing more and more apprehensive, and he suddenly stopped cold in his tracks.

Wildcat 16 also drew to a halt, then turned around and asked, "Why have you stopped, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11?"

"We've already been flying for a very long time, so I think it's only right that you tell me where we're going. I don't exactly enjoy being led on a trip into the middle of nowhere," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11, we're almost there. This is a matter that concerns a forbidden art of the Immortal Realm, so even though we're already on the outskirts of the Black Wind Sea, we can't afford to get complacent. If anyone finds out what we're up to, we won't be able to remain in the Black Wind Sea any longer, so it's best that we go somewhere safe before we continue our conversation," Wildcat 16 said in a serious voice.

"Don't try to placate me, Fellow Daoist Wildcat 16. There's not a single soul to be seen here, so I suggest you come clean and tell me the truth. Otherwise, I'll have to take my leave," Han Li harrumphed coldly.

Despite his abrasive words, Wildcat 16 appeared to be completely unbothered, and after a brief moment of contemplation, they said, "I understand your concern, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11. Truth be told, I do not have the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique. Instead, it's in the possession of a friend of mine, and that friend is waiting up ahead for us."

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, and Wildcat 16 continued, "Just as I said, this is a very serious matter, and my friend doesn't wish to deal with this matter in person. That's why they asked me to meet you on their behalf."

Han Li fell silent upon hearing this, and it seemed that he was contemplating something.

"I can assure you that I'm telling the truth, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11. If you don't believe me, then there's nothing I can say to convince you, and we'll have to call off the deal," Wildcat 16 said in a resigned manner.

Han Li continued to remain silent, and his mind was racing as he weighed up his options.

Wildcat 16 also waited in silence, making no effort to try and hurry Han Li.

"Alright, in that case, I'll come with you, but do tell me how much longer we have to go," Han Li said after some extensive contemplation.

A hint of relief flashed through Wildcat 16's eyes upon hearing this, and they replied, "There's not far left to go. At our speed, we'll definitely be able to get there within two hours."

Han Li had noticed the fleeting hint of relief that had flashed through Wildcat 16's eyes, but he made no comment on it.

With that, the two of them continued onward, and after flying for close to another hour, a burst of faint rumbling suddenly rang out up ahead.

The further they went, the louder this rumbling became, and a wary look appeared in Han Li's eyes.

Shortly thereafter, the two of them drew to a halt.

Gusts of inky-black yin wind had suddenly appeared up ahead, with the largest gusts resembling enormous tornadoes, while the smallest ones were only the size of houses.

The countless gusts of black yin wind filled the entire space up ahead, and the sound of ghastly howling and sobbing could be heard ringing out within the yin wind.

Just these harrowing sounds alone were enough to strike Han Li with a sense of dizziness, and he hurriedly activated his Spirit Refinement Technique to alleviate this rush of dizziness, but the apprehension in his heart had been further exacerbated.

His current spiritual sense was not inferior to that of the average Golden Immortal, so there was no way that the sounds ringing out from within the gusts of yin wind should've been able to affect him.

All of a sudden, an alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face.

It was only very faint, but a hint of instability had arisen within his spiritual sense, and his heart immediately sank, thinking that the backlash from the Spirit Refinement Technique was about to strike again.

"Is this your first time seeing this Soul Stirring Wind, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11? They have an extremely potent disruptive effect on one's soul, and unless the proper protective measures are taken, even True Immortal cultivators like ourselves won't be able to last very long in there at all," Wildcat 16 said.

Han Li was rather relieved to hear this, and he asked, "Are you saying that we have to venture into these winds?"

"That's right, but rest assured, we won't be venturing very far into these Soul Stirring Winds, and I've also prepared some things for this very purpose," Wildcat 16 replied with a nod.

Han Li offered no response to this, seemingly waiting to see exactly what Wildcat 16 had prepared.

Wildcat 16 didn't waste any more time words, either, and he raised a hand to produce an egg-sized black bead that appeared to have countless shadows flashing within it, presenting quite a profound sight to behold.

He then began to chant an incantation, and a ring of black light surged out of the black bead, stretching to a radius of over 100 feet to encompass both Han Li and Wildcat 16.

The ghastly sounds ringing out up ahead immediately became much more subdued, while the biting chill in the air also subsided significantly.

Chapter 375: The Second Half

"I didn't think that you would have a treasure that could keep out the Soul Stirring Winds," Han Li said as he took an intrigued glance at the black bead.

"It's not that remarkable a treasure. Let's go," Wildcat 16 said in a casual manner, seemingly not wanting to explain too much about the black bead.

With that, he led the way forward, flying into the vast expanse of yin winds up ahead, followed closely by Han Li.

As they flew onward, the surrounding yin winds became more and more ferocious, encompassing the entire space around Han Li's duo.

However, the ring of black light released by the black bead remained resilient against the yin wind, and at most, the Soul Stirring Winds were only able to create some ripples on the surface of the ring of light.

With their powers, they were naturally able to ward off the effects of this significantly weakened Soul Stirring Wind, and they quickly continued onward.

All the while, the surrounding Soul Stirring Winds continued to become more and more formidable, and it was as if there were tens of thousands of evil spirits wailing around them.

"Do you know the origins of this Soul Stirring Wind, Fellow Daoist Wildcat 16? It feels as if these winds are blowing straight out of the depths of hell, and without that treasure of yours, I wouldn't have dared to venture so far into this area at all," Han Li suddenly said as he inspected the surrounding gusts of yin wind.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11. These Soul Stirring Winds have already existed here for countless years, so I'm afraid I do not know their origins. However, there's a rumor in the Black Wind Sea that this place is connected to the Infernal Realm, and that's where the Soul Stirring Wind is leaking out from," Wildcat 16 replied.

"Does the Infernal Realm really exist?" Han Li asked.

"The so-called Infernal Realm is nothing more than an unsubstantiated legend, and no one knows for sure whether it actually exists, so take these stories with a grain of salt," Wildcat 16 replied with a smile.

"I've heard that these Soul Stirring Winds encompass a massive area, and it's virtually impossible to pass directly through them. That's why the Black Wind Sea is only connected to the outside world through the teleportation array on Black Wind Island. I wonder if it's possible for a Golden Immortal to pass through these winds," Han Li mused with a contemplative look on his face.

"According to my knowledge, some powerful cultivators from the Black Wind Sea have previously attempted to pass through these Soul Stirring Winds, but none have succeeded. Many years ago, a Golden Immortal Stage senior attempted this feat, and he was trapped inside for several decades before being forced to come back out.

“According to him, the Soul Stirring Wind in the deepest part of this area is extremely formidable, so much so that even a Golden Immortal Stage soul isn't able to withstand it," Wildcat 16 replied with a shake of their head.

"I didn't think that these Soul Stirring Winds would be too formidable even for a Golden Immortal cultivator to pass through," Han Li mused with a contemplative expression.

Now that he had mastered the laws of time and had Daoist Xie by his side, he was wondering if it would be possible to force his way through these Soul Stirring Winds to leave the Black Wind Sea if his true identity were ever exposed, but it seemed that this was not a feasible course of action.

"This is why this place is known as an impregnable natural barrier. Perhaps only cultivators at or above the High Zenith Stage would be able to pass through these Soul Stirring Winds, but it's yet to be seen whether there are even any High Zenith Stage Jade Immortals at all in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region," Wildcat 16 said.

Han Li nodded in response and didn't speak any further on the subject.

Both of them flew onward in silence for some time, yet for some reason, past a certain point, the surrounding Soul Stirring Winds seemed to have reached a stable state and wasn't growing any more formidable.

Right as Han Li was speculating about why this could be the case, Wildcat 16 suddenly stopped in his tracks.

"Have we arrived?" Han Li asked as he also drew to a halt.

Wildcat 16 nodded in response, and after taking a couple of cautious glances at his surroundings he made a hand seal, upon which the black light radiating from the black bead instantly swelled, encompassing the two of them as they descended into the sea down below.

The seawater here had already turned as black as ink, and it was giving off a bone-chilling glacial aura that was quite uncomfortable for Han Li's duo even with the protection of the black bead.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to draw a ball of seawater into his grasp, and he discovered that it was giving off extremely abundant yin qi that was not inferior to that of some yin-attribute true waters, but the energy that this seawater contained was extremely chaotic, rendering it unusable.

The two of them quickly sank down to the seabed, and Wildcat 16 was clearly very familiar with this place, leading Han Li into a marine trench.

There, he flipped a hand over to produce a black jade badge, then chanted an incantation, and the badge immediately began radiating a vast expanse of black light that illuminated the seabed, causing it to tremble as five black stone pillars slowly emerged.

Each pillar was as thick as a water vat with countless runes that were radiating faint black light inscribed upon them.

Han Li stood off to the side with his hands clasped behind his back as he observed the proceedings through narrowed eyes.

Wildcat 16 continued to chant his incantation, and the black light radiating from the five stone pillars grew brighter and brighter before connecting together to form a ball of black light that was over 100 feet in size.

The ball of light began to revolve, picking up more and more speed as it did so, and all of a sudden, a faint crack rang out as an inky black cylindrical spatial passageway appeared.

Han Li was quite intrigued to find that this black spatial passageway was very similar to the one leading to that secret area on Dark Veil Island.

He attempted to release his spiritual sense into the spatial passageway, only for it to be kept at bay by a burst of gentle force.

"This is the place that I mentioned earlier, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11. After you."

Wildcat 16 stepped away to the side and made an inviting hand gesture as he spoke.

Han Li nodded in response, then flew into the spatial passageway without any hesitation.

Wildcat 16 was a little surprised by Han Li's willingness to cooperate, but he immediately followed along.

On the surface, Han Li appeared quite calm and collected, but deep down, he was feeling rather resigned.

Given how careful and cautious he had always been, he definitely wouldn't have entered an unknown place like this so easily under normal circumstances.

However, for the sake of the Spirit Refinement Technique, he had no choice but to cooperate. He had already made it to this point, and it was too late to turn back.

However, that didn't mean that he was completely at the mercy of whoever was waiting for him in the secret area.

Aside from his laws of time and Mantra Treasured Axis, Daoist Xie now possessed Golden Immortal Stage power, so if anything were to go awry, then he was confident that he would be able to strike down Wildcat 16 in a very short time and take his bead treasure before fleeing the scene.

As soon as Han Li stepped into the spatial passageway, his body was immediately enveloped by a burst of power, and his surroundings transformed into a complete blur.

He immediately drew upon the immortal spiritual power in his body, preparing to unleash his most powerful treasures at a moment's notice, but thankfully, he didn't have to.

Shortly thereafter, he found himself in a space with a radius of several dozen kilometers, and the entire area was filled with lush vegetation, similar to the environment in the secret area on Dark Veil Island.

At the center of this secret area stood a black mountain that was tens of thousands of feet tall, and there were several cave entrances on the mountain, indicating that there were cave abodes inside.

Furthermore, there was some type of restriction in this secret area that rendered Han Li unable to release his spiritual sense out of his body at all.

Han Li inspected his surroundings while drawing upon his immortal spiritual power, and a burst of golden lightning emerged over his body before fading in a flash, following which an elated look flashed through his eyes.

He had just discreetly examined his connection with the lightning teleportation array that he had set up in the Black Wind Sea, and the connection was still intact, so he could teleport out of this place at any moment.

Right after he left his cave abode on that secluded island, he had made a trip to the lightning teleportation array to find that it was completely untouched.

After that, he had taken some time to bolster the array, and with this life-saving trump card up his sleeve, he was feeling a bit safer.

Right at this moment, Wildcat 16 emerged beside Han Li.

"My friend is waiting for you up ahead, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11," Wildcat 16 said, then flew directly toward the black mountain before Han Li had a chance to reply.

Han Li trailed along behind Wildcat 16, and the two of them quickly flew into one of the cave entrances.

After traveling along a passageway for a while, a hall appeared up ahead.

The furnishings in the hall were quite minimalistic, with only a stone table, several stone chairs, and a black screen that was shimmering with black light and had different designs occasionally taking shape on its surface.

A tall red-robed man was standing in front of the screen with his back facing Han Li's duo, and Han Li was struck by a sense of familiarity at the sight of the man.

The red-robed man turned around upon hearing the sound of footsteps, and Han Li was rather taken aback to discover that he was none other than Wyrm 3.

"Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11, this is Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, and he's the one who's actually taken on your mission," Wildcat 16 said.

Wyrm 3 took a glance at Han Li, then sat down on one of the chairs as he made an inviting hand gesture and said, "Take a seat, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11."

Han Li did as he was told, while Wildcat 16 cupped his fist in a salute toward Wyrm 3 before turning to depart.

"I'll leave you two to speak in private."

Han Li turned to look at the departing Wildcat 16 with a peculiar look in his eyes, while Wyrm 3 said, "Don't mind him, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11, I can explain the situation to you."

"Alright, in that case, I won't waste any time with idle chatter. Do you have the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Han Li asked in a direct and straightforward fashion.

While Wildcat 16 had referred to Wyrm 3 as a friend of his, from Han Li's observation, it appeared that they were more like superior and subordinate.

"Of course," Wyrm 3 replied with a smile, then swept a sleeve through the air to send a gray jade slip flying toward Han Li.

Han Li caught the jade slip, then cast an inquisitive gaze toward Wyrm 3.

In response, Wyrm 3 made an inviting hand gesture, and Han Li pressed the jade slip to his own forehead.

The restrictions here prevented him from releasing his spiritual sense out of his body, so he had no choice but to examine the jade slip through direct contact.

The jade slip contained a cultivation art, but only the first few lines were visible, while the rest were enshrouded in a concealment restriction.

However, the first few visible lines alone were enough to tell Han Li that this was indeed the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique that he had been searching for.

Chapter 376: Reincarnation Disciple

After reading through the first few lines in the jade slip several times, Han Li carefully swept his spiritual sense briefly over the concealment restriction that obscured the rest of the cultivation art, then promptly withdrew his spiritual sense from the jade slip.

He didn't know exactly what this restriction was, but given his extensive experience and master in this field, he could tell that this was definitely no ordinary restriction. If he were to try and break through it by force, the jade slip would most likely be instantly destroyed, and his spiritual sense would be severely harmed in the process as well.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to send the gray jade slip drifting back to Wyrm 3's side, then said, "Let's not waste any time here, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3. What do you need me to do in exchange for the full cultivation art?"

A smile appeared on Wyrm 3's face as he set the jade slip down onto the stone table beside him, following which he replied, "Before we discuss that, I have something to ask you, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11."

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"How much do you know about this Spirit Refinement Technique?" Wyrm 3 asked in a calm manner.

This was a completely unexpected question to Han Li, and he contemplated the question momentarily before replying, "According to my knowledge, this is a forbidden art of the Immortal Realm, and it can enhance one's spiritual sense, but most of the people who cultivate it end up becoming deranged monsters who wreak havoc across the Immortal Realm. Hence, it's banned in all immortal regions, thereby making it a forbidden art."

"Is that all you know about it?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"That's all. Is there something wrong with what I've said?" Han Li asked.

"That's only the basic information that everyone knows about the Spirit Refinement Technique. If I'm not mistaken, you've already mastered the third level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, right? May I ask who it was that taught you the technique, and did they not go into further details about it back then?" Wyrm 3 asked.

The image of the immortal by the name of He Kang surfaced in Han Li's mind, but he naturally wasn't going to reveal that information, and he replied, "I obtained the first half of the Spirit Refinement Technique by chance, and at the time, I wasn't aware that it was a forbidden technique, so I cultivated it on my own."

This wasn't exactly a lie. All He Kang had done was bestow upon him the first three levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and he hadn't gone into any further detail beyond that.

Wyrm 3 seemed to have been astonished to hear this. "You're saying that you managed to master the first three levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique on your own without any guidance?"

"Is there a problem?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

Wyrm 3 was silent for a moment, then replied, "Not at all, I'm simply stunned by your exceptional cultivation aptitude."

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist. I was merely very fortunate to have made this much progress in the Spirit Refinement Technique," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

"Seeing as you don't know much about the Spirit Refinement Technique, I'll start from the beginning. Otherwise, it'll be difficult to proceed with the rest of our discussion," Wyrm 3 said.

"Please enlighten me," Han Li prompted as a hint of intrigue appeared in his eyes.

"What you just said is all true. The Spirit Refinement Technique has a very severe drawback, but it's also an extremely formidable secret technique that was once vastly renowned in the Immortal Realm.

“However, the Spirit Refinement Technique isn't a forbidden art just because most of those who cultivate it end up becoming insane. Additionally, the other main contributing reason to its forbidden status is the fact that it came from the Reincarnation Palace," Wyrm 3 revealed.

"The Reincarnation Palace?" Han Li was quite taken aback to hear this.

Wyrm 3 was rather surprised by Han Li's reaction, but he then smiled as he remarked, "It seems like you're already aware of the Reincarnation Palace, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11."

"I have heard some things about the Reincarnation Palace, but not much. Please continue, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Han Li replied.

"Seeing as you've heard of the Reincarnation Palace, I'm sure you're also aware that the Reincarnation Palace is an enemy of all of the Immortal Palaces. At this point, all those who have cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique have some ties to the Reincarnation Palace, and that's why they're being hunted so vehemently," Wyrm 3 said.

"I have heard about that," Han Li confirmed with a nod as thoughts of Baili Yan and Daoist Hu Yan sprang into his mind.

"It's said that the Spirit Refinement Technique was created by the founder of the Reincarnation Palace, and it's always been a symbol of one's affiliation with the Reincarnation Palace. However, countless years ago, the first half of the cultivation art was somehow leaked, but only the Reincarnation Palace has the second half.

“Furthermore, due to the fact that the first half was leaked, extra precautions have been taken to ensure that the second half isn't also leaked, and it's forbidden to bestow the second half of the cultivation art upon anyone outside of the Reincarnation Palace," Wyrm 3 continued.

"Does that mean you're a member of the Reincarnation Palace, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3?" Han Li asked.

"That's right," Wyrm 3 replied with a nod.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this.

Wyrm 3 was a very important figure in the Transient Guild, and Han Li certainly wasn't expecting him to be a member of the Reincarnation Palace as well.

It wasn't exactly an uncommon occurrence for people from different sects and powers to join the Transient Guild, but the majority of the guild's members were ordinary members like Han Li.

The fact that Wyrm 3 held such a lofty status in the Transient Guild yet was also a member of the Reincarnation Palace was a rather intriguing revelation.

"If you want to obtain the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique, then all you have to do is actually something very simple," Wyrm 3 continued.

"Are you saying..."

"That's right. As long as you're willing to join our Reincarnation Palace, I'll hand over this jade slip right away," Wyrm 3 declared in a direct and straightforward fashion.

Han Li gently drummed his fingertips against the surface of the stone table as he fell silent.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 also remained silent as he waited patiently.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps rang out, and a servant entered the room, carrying a platter that held two cups of spirit tea.

The teacups were translucent, and it was unclear what type of material they had been crafted from. The spirit tea that they were holding was also quite remarkable, and even though it wasn't giving off much of an aroma, the white vapor that drifted up from the tea would occasionally take on the form of cranes that flew around the teacup briefly before slowly dissipating.

"How rude of me to not have offered you any tea, even though you've already been here for so long. This White Mist Spirit Tea is unique to our Reincarnation, and it's quite exquisite. Have a taste, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11," Wyrm 3 said with a smile.

The servant set the two cups of tea down onto the stone table before quickly departing.

Han Li was still engrossed in his own thoughts, and only after hearing what Wyrm 3 had to say did he turn his attention to the tea on the table, upon which a hint of surprise appeared on his face.

The white mist wasn't just normal water vapor. Instead, it was extremely rich immortal spiritual qi, and the fact that it could manifest certain forms on its own indicated that it was an exceptional spirit tea.

The immortal spiritual qi that was contained in this single cup of tea was enough to make up for a month of cultivation for him, and this was by far the most exceptional spirit tea that Han Li had ever come across.

However, he didn't have a habit of drinking tea in unfamiliar places, so even though he was rather tempted, he decided not to touch the tea in the cup.

Wyrm 3 was rather amused by Han Li's cautious approach, and he picked up his own teacup before taking a sip.

Meanwhile, Han Li remained seated in silence, and he appeared quite calm on the outside, but internally, he was feeling quite conflicted.

The crisis that had taken place in the Blaze Dragon Dao had left a very deep impression on him. Baili Yan had already been on the cusp of reaching the High Zenith Stage, yet just because he was a member of the Reincarnation Palace, most of the Golden Immortal Stage dao lords had turned on him and plotted his downfall in collaboration with the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace.

Daoist Hu Yan clearly had close ties with the Reincarnation Palace as well, and it was unclear whether he was dead or alive.

Han Li didn't know much about the Reincarnation Palace, but he knew that it was a sworn enemy of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region and even the Heavenly Court.

Even though he was currently being hunted by the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace over his killing of Tao Yu, he still didn't want to join the Reincarnation Palace and place himself in direct opposition against the Immortal Palaces.

He was still only a late-True Immortal cultivator at the moment, and he wanted to avoid trouble at all costs.

However, if he didn't join the Reincarnation Palace, then he wouldn't be able to obtain the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and that would be no different from an extended death sentence.

Neither of these options were particularly appealing to Han Li, and he remained silent for a long while.

Finally, Wyrm 3 set down his teacup as he broke the silence. "Are you worried that joining our Reincarnation Palace will pit you against the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace?"

"That's right," Han Li replied in a candid fashion.

"I'm assuming you must've been residing in the Black Wind Sea for a long time, so you don't know much about the world outside. The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace is quite a formidable power, but our Reincarnation Palace isn't the only force that can stand against it. It's just that none of those forces are willing to step forward for no good reason.

“On top of that, our Reincarnation Palace has always resided in the shadows, so it won't be easy for the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace to find us," Wyrm 3 said with a smile.

"Is there any proof to support your claims? Surely you can't expect me to just take your word for it," Han Li said in a solemn voice.

"Eventually, you'll come to find out whether I'm telling the truth or not. The fact of the matter right now is that you've mastered the first three levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique, so if you're caught by the Immortal Palace, you'll be dealt with as a member of our Reincarnation Palace anyway.

“On top of that, I can tell that you've recently suffered a bout of backlash from the Spirit Refinement Technique, so if you can't secure the second half of the cultivation art in a timely fashion..."

Wyrm 3's voice trailed off here, but it wasn't difficult to tell what he was implying.

Han Li's heart sank slightly upon hearing this.

He had already done everything in his power to restrain his spiritual sense, but Wyrm 3 had still managed to detect the spiritual sense crisis that had recently befallen him.

Han Li fell silent once again as he continued to tap the stone table in an absentminded manner, but at this point, the choice was becoming rather clear to him.

Wyrm 3 could tell that Han Li needed one final push, so he continued, "I don't mean to brag, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11, but our Reincarnation Palace is no less formidable than the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

“We have all types of pills, materials, secret techniques, and cultivation arts, and we're not inviting you to join our Reincarnation Palace as just an ordinary member. Instead, this is an invitation for you to become a Reincarnation Disciple."

Chapter 377: Joining the Reincarnation Palace

"What is a Reincarnation Disciple?" Han Li asked.

"Just think of it as the most core members of the Reincarnation Palace, and not just anyone can become a Reincarnation Disciple. Not only does the candidate have to possess special aptitude, they can only be selected by the Reincarnation Palace," Wyrm 3 explained in a concise fashion.

"I'm just an ordinary itinerant cultivator with no special talents or aptitude to speak of," Han Li said.

"Don't be so modest, Fellow Daoist Raccoon 11. You're a Dao Pill Master, and that's certainly an exceptional talent in my books," Wyrm 3 said with a smile.

Han Li immediately rose to his feet upon hearing this, and he was glowering intently at Wyrm 3 with a sharp and piercing gaze.

Wyrm 3 looked back at Han Li with a calm expression, directly meeting his gaze.

The two of them stared at each other for a long time, and Wyrm 3 remained calm and collected the entire time.

After a while, the sharpness in Han Li's gaze slowly faded, and he asked, "How do you know about that?"

"Your Dewform Herb was obtained from me, and you released quite a few other dao pill ingredient acquisition missions in the Transient Guild, so it wasn't difficult to figure out what you were up to," Wyrm 3 explained with a smile, while Han Li remained silent.

Wyrm 3 continued, "That pill tribulation that took place in the Black Wind Sea not long ago was triggered by you, right? Given all of those factors, I would have to be a fool not to have deduced that you're a Dao Pill Master."

"I assume that must mean Ge Yu is also a member of your Reincarnation Palace, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. He already realized at the time that you were a Dao Pill Master, and he simply chose not to confront you on the matter," Wyrm 3 conceded with a nod.

"The Reincarnation Palace truly is just as formidable as you proclaim. I thought I managed to fool him at the time," Han Li said as a self-deprecating look appeared on his face.

At the same time, he was feeling quite relieved.

It seemed that the Reincarnation Palace had only found out that he managed to refine a dao pill, but that was the extent of what they knew about him.

It wasn't really a big deal that his identity as a dao pill master had been exposed.

"There's no need to feel disheartened, Fellow Daoist. Ge Yu was only able to see through your ruse as he's proficient in the use of a sensory secret technique. If someone else had been in his place, they would've most likely been fooled.

“Having said that, if Ge Yu hadn't found out about your dao pill refinement, then you wouldn't have been able to obtain the second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique, so it all works out in your favor anyway," Wyrm 3 said with a smile.

"While your introduction has given me a rough understanding of the Reincarnation Palace, I still don't know much about its internal structure. Would you be able to enlighten me on that subject, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3?" Han Li asked as he sat back down.

"Of course. Our Reincarnation Palace is different from other sects in that we have no set territory. Instead, we're a relatively decentralized organization, and we don't require our members to stay in certain places.

“On top of that, members communicate using special treasures, so it's very convenient for itinerant cultivators like yourself who are accustomed to freedom," Wyrm 3 replied with a smile.

"That sounds a lot like the Transient Guild," Han Li mused as he stroked his own chin.

Wyrm 3 fell silent upon hearing this, and it seemed that he was hesitating about something.

"Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3?" Han Li asked.

"I was hesitating about whether to reveal a certain piece of information to you, but I suppose it can't hurt," Wyrm 3 replied.

"Please go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"There are many powers in all of the immortal regions that are quite formidable, but they're often unable to deal with everything that they need to address all the time. Hence, they'll permit some smaller powers to become subsidiaries of theirs and work for them. The same applies to our Reincarnation Palace, and you can actually think of the Transient Guild as a subsidiary organization of ours," Wyrm 3 revealed.

"I see," Han Li replied with a surprised look on his face.

This revelation did explain some things. For example, it was no wonder that Wyrm 3 was a high-ranking member of the Transient Guild while also being a member of the Reincarnation Palace.

"Almost no one in the Transient Guild is aware of the relationship between the Reincarnation Palace and the Transient Guild, and even in the Reincarnation Palace, only Reincarnation Disciples are made aware of this.

“After all, our Reincarnation Palace is a sworn enemy of the Heavenly Court, and if word of this were to be leaked, then members of the Transient Guild would be hunted down by the Heavenly Court. Hence, make sure you keep this a secret," Wyrm 3 said in a solemn manner.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, I'll be sure to remain tight-lipped about this subject," Han Li replied as a complex look appeared in his eyes.

It seemed that Wyrm 3 was revealing such an important piece of information to him as a sign of trust, but in reality, it was a very forcing gesture.

Now that he had been made privy to such an important secret, he most likely wasn't going to be able to leave this place unless he agreed to join the Reincarnation Palace.

"For the sake of convenience, all Reincarnation Palace members will wear Transient Guild masks when carrying out missions, and just like in the Transient Guild, members use these masks to communicate, conduct exchanges, and release and accept missions," Wyrm 3 said as he pointed at the mask on his face.

"I'm assuming members of the Reincarnation Palace have certain obligations to fulfill, just like members of the Transient Guild, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's correct. Once every 1,000 years, a Reincarnation Palace member must complete a mission. Of course, they can choose not to complete the mission, but they'll need to issue Immortal Origin Stones or other resources equivalent in value to the mission content," Wyrm 3 replied with a nod.

"In that case, high-ranking members of the Transient Guild may not necessarily be members of the Reincarnation Palace, but members of the Reincarnation Palace, including Reincarnation Disciples, are generally high-ranking members of the Transient Guild, right?" Han Li asked.

"You can think of it that way. That's about as much information on the Reincarnation Palace that I can reveal to you at this point," Wyrm 3 said before taking another sip of tea.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then said, "You've been very earnest in your invitation for me to join the Reincarnation Palace, so it would be quite rude of me to continue to refuse. I agree to join the Reincarnation Palace."

"Great! I knew I was right to have approached you. While it's true that itinerant cultivators enjoy more freedom, the more you progress in your cultivation, the greater your demand for cultivation resources will become, and eventually, you'll hit a dead-end, so it's definitely a wise decision for you to join our Reincarnation Palace," Wyrm 3 said as he set down his teacup.

"From this day forth, both of us will be members of the Reincarnation Palace. Please look after me, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Han Li said with a smile.

"No problem. If you have any questions, feel free to ask me. You're a Dao Pill Master, so I'm certainly more than happy to be on good terms with you," Wyrm 3 chuckled in a joking manner.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Wyrm 3.

Now that he had agreed to join the Reincarnation Palace, an unspoken barrier of apprehension between them seemed to have been torn down, bringing them a lot closer.

Wyrm 3 flipped a hand over to produce a crimson lion mask, upon which was inscribed the number "5", and he handed the mask to Han Li as he said, "This is your new mask. From this day forth, you'll be Dragon Five, but you're free to keep your Raccoon 11 identity if you so choose."

Han Li nodded in response as he accepted the crimson lion mask.

He had been looking for a new mask, so this had come at the perfect time.

He made a hand seal and cast a streak of azure light into the mask, but to his surprise, it displayed no reaction.

"This mask is different from ordinary Transient Guild masks, and you can only use it with a special incantation seal of the Reincarnation Palace," Wyrm 3 said as he swept a sleeve through the air to send a jade slip flying toward Han Li.

Han Li caught the jade slip before pressing it against his forehead, and moments later, he chanted an incantation before casting an incantation seal into the crimson lion mask, upon which it immediately released a crimson light screen.

Han Li didn't go any further beyond that, withdrawing his hand seal to scatter the light screen.

"On the surface, this mask doesn't appear to be remarkable in any way, but it's actually specially made by the Reincarnation Palace, and it has one additional benefit outside of all of the uses of a Transient Guild mask, and that's its ability to conceal the aura of the Spirit Refinement Technique. It's not perfect, but as long as you exercise some caution, you won't be easily caught by the surveyors of the Heavenly Court," Wyrm 3 added.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, and he took another glance at the crimson mask before stowing it away, then turned his gaze back to Wyrm 3.

Wyrm 3 seemed to be aware of what Han Li wanted, and he picked up the gray jade slip on the table and began chanting an incantation while casting several incantation seals into the jade slip.

A layer of murky gray light appeared over the surface of the jade slip, and it was interspersed with specks of black light, presenting an intriguing sight to behold.

The gray light then vanished in a flash, and a hint of excitement appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

"According to the rules of our Reincarnation Palace, all those who join will receive one level of the Spirit Refinement Technique for free. This jade slip contains the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, so you'll have to earn the rest of the cultivation art," Wyrm 3 said as he handed the jade slip to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the jade slip with a hint of disappointment in his eyes.

He had thought that this jade slip contained the entire second half of the Spirit Refinement Technique, but it appeared that things weren't going to be so easy for him.

Having said that, the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique was already sufficient for his current needs.

He pressed the jade slip to his forehead once again before injecting his spiritual sense into it, and sure enough, the concealment restriction inside had already been removed, and everything was revealed to him.

He suppressed the excitement in his heart as he quickly read through the cultivation art, which wasn't very long, only spanning several thousand characters, and it didn't take long for him to commit the entire thing to memory.

After that, he took a deep breath and closed his eyes as he sat still in his chair.

Wyrm 3 also sat in silence, and only after a full 15 minutes had passed did Han Li exhale as he opened his eyes.

The Spirit Refinement Technique had always been a major problem weighing on his mind, and now that it had been resolved, he felt as if a huge load had been lifted from his shoulders.

Chapter 378: Earthly List

After Han Li opened his eyes, Wyrm 3 said, "Now that you've become a Reincarnation Disciple, there's one more thing that you must be made aware of."

Wyrm 3 swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of yellow light as he spoke, and Han Li caught it to discover that it was a jade slip, then took a glance at Wyrm 3 before pressing the jade slip to his own forehead.

Moments later, he removed the jade slip from his forehead, then made a hand seal as he began to chant an incantation, and a layer of crimson light immediately emerged from his crimson mask before forming a crimson screen of light in front of him.

After sweeping his gaze over the screen of light, Han Li reached out a finger without any hesitation before tapping on a tiny stone plaque icon in the corner, upon which a projection of a white stone plaque that was around 10 feet tall instantly shot out of the icon.

At the top of the stone plaque were the words "Earthly List" inscribed in golden seal text, while down below were some lines of small golden text that laid out different cultivation arts, secret techniques, and pill recipes.

After those came some lines of small silver text that provided descriptions of the items on the list, and each of them ended with a number that seemed to be denoting the prices of the individual items.

It only took a quick glance over the list before an elated look appeared on Han Li's face.

"Mountain Body Refinement Arts, earth-attribute Profound Immortal cultivation arts, uses the essence of mountains to refine the physical body... Can be cultivated to the Golden Immortal Stage 150 points."

"High Zenith Spirit Eyes, an ocular ability that lays bare everything between heaven and earth to the cultivator. 200 points."

"Recipe for the Origin Spirit Pill..."

"What you're seeing right now is the Reincarnation Palace Earthly List that's only accessible to Reincarnation Disciples. The cultivation arts and secret techniques on the list have all been gathered by the Reincarnation Palace over the course of countless years, and I won't go into detail about how valuable they are.

“As for the numbers at the end, they lay out the number of contribution points required to secure each item, and you earn contribution points by completing Reincarnation Palace missions," Wyrm 3 explained.

"I see. It seems like there are many perks to joining the Reincarnation Palace. Any one of these items would be extremely sought after in the outside world, but it appears all I can do for the moment is take a look at the list," Han Li replied with a nod.

"That's not true. All new Reincarnation Disciples receive 100 contribution points in addition to a free level of the Spirit Refinement Technique. You can choose something within 100 contribution points on the list now, or save up for the future."

Wyrm 3 flipped a hand over to produce a crimson jade badge as he spoke, then pointed it at the stone plaque projection in front of Han Li, releasing a streak of red light that vanished into the stone plaque in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, the number "100" appeared at the bottom of the stone plaque, and Han Li's eyes instantly lit up upon seeing this.

He expressed his gratitude to Wyrm 3, then began browsing the items on the Earthly List.

There were many items on the list that were extremely tempting to him, and these 100 contribution points couldn't have come at a better time.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes lit up as he spotted all seven levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique on the stone plaque.

Perhaps it was because the first three levels had already been leaked, but those levels were quite cheap to obtain, but from the fourth level onward, the number of contribution points required spiked up drastically.

Among them, the fourth level cost 2,000 contribution points, while the fifth level cost a staggering 10,000.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

He didn't know how much compensation he could expect to earn from completing missions, but judging from the contribution point costs of the other items on the list, it was clear that 10,000 contribution points was an astronomical sum that wasn't going to be easy to accumulate at all.

Having said that, this was only to be expected. There weren't going to be many avenues at all in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region that he could obtain this cultivation art through, so its rarity further increased its value.

Now that he already had the fourth level of the cultivation art, he would be able to stave off the spiritual sense crisis for the time being, and that should give him enough time to save up contribution points for the subsequent levels.

With that in mind, Han Li continued to browse through the list, and before long, another item on the list had caught his attention.

Recipe for the Golden Soul Pill... Didn't Daoist Xie previously mention the Golden Soul Pill to me?

With that in mind, he turned his attention to the description for the item on the list, and his eyes immediately lit up.

The Golden Soul Pill wasn't a pill that could enhance one's cultivation base or provide any restorative effects. Instead, its only use was to stabilize one's soul.

Most importantly, the description claimed that this pill could increase a late-True Immortal cultivator's chances of breaking through their Golden Immortal Stage bottleneck.

In order to prepare for his Golden Immortal Stage breakthrough, Han Li had read many scriptures throughout the years, and the process required one to open 36 immortal acupoints and overcome the first three decays in order to trigger an evolution in their immortal spiritual power.

After that, their soul would also evolve from an ordinary soul into a Golden Immortal Soul.

This process wasn't as difficult as opening the 36 immortal acupoints or overcoming the three decays, but it was definitely no easy feat, either.

He then turned his gaze to the listed price for the pill recipe to discover that it was exactly 100 contribution points.

"It seems like you're interested in this Golden Soul Pill recipe," Wyrm 3 remarked.

Han Li nodded in response. "Do you know why this pill recipe only costs 100 contribution points, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3?"

"The reason for this is that even though a Golden Soul Pill can be very conducive to a successful Golden Immortal Stage breakthrough, the primary ingredient required to refine it is a complete Golden Immortal Stage nascent soul, which is obviously something extremely precious.

“It's very difficult to earn contribution points in the Reincarnation Palace, so I suggest that you exercise prudence in your use of these 100 contribution points and don't just spend them rashly," Wyrm 3 cautioned.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression.

While it was true that finding a complete Golden Immortal Stage nascent soul was extremely difficult for other True Immortal cultivators, he just so happened to have one in his possession right now.

With that in mind, he quickly browsed through the remaining items on the list before his gaze fell back upon the Golden Soul Pill recipe, and he reached out a finger toward that item on the list.

Wyrm 3's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he interjected, "Fellow Daoist Dragon Five..."

"Thank you for the words of advice, but I've already decided to spend my 100 contribution points on this pill recipe," Han Li said in a determined voice.

"It's up to you how you spend your contribution points, but do keep in mind that anything that you secure from the Earthly List must be kept secret, even from those closest to you, and anyone who goes against this rule will be severely punished," Wyrm 3 said in an indifferent voice.

"I'll be sure to keep that in mind," Han Li replied with a nod.

He then tapped a finger on the Golden Soul Pill recipe, and his 100 contribution points were instantly deducted, while a teleportation vortex appeared at the center of the stone plaque projection.

Moments later, a white jade slip emerged from the vortex, and Han Li pressed the jade slip against his forehead before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

Shortly thereafter, he removed the jade slip from his forehead, and his expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was quite elated.

Aside from the Golden Immortal Stage nascent soul, none of the other ingredients required to refine the Golden Soul Pill were all that precious, so they should've been easy to gather.

"Fellow Daoist Dragon 5, I know that it's a little unfair to push a mission onto you right after you've joined the Reincarnation Palace, but at the moment, there's a very important mission that we need you to complete right away," Wyrm 3 suddenly said in a serious voice.

"That's fine. What's the mission?" Han Li asked.

"Don't worry, this mission doesn't pose any danger to you. It's a pill refinement mission," Wyrm 3 revealed with a smile.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon hearing this.

"After you complete this mission, you'll be free to do whatever you want for the next 1,000 years, and you'll also receive 50 contribution points," Wyrm 3 continued as he summoned a jade slip before handing it to Han Li.

Instead of accepting the jade slip right away, Han Li asked, "Dao Pill Master's may be rare, but I'm sure there are others in the Reincarnation Palace, so why are you assigning this mission to me?"

"We do have another Dao Pill Master, but he's busy with some other things at the moment, so we have no choice but to turn to you," Wyrm 3 explained.

Han Li remained silent as a series of thoughts flashed through his mind.

"Truth be told, while this is a Reincarnation Palace mission, it's somewhat related to me as well, so please lend me your assistance, Fellow Daoist Dragon Five," Wyrm 3 continued with a hint of an imploring tone in his voice.

"You're the one who introduced me to the Reincarnation Palace, so seeing as this is a matter that concerns you, I'm obligated to help. I'll accept this mission," Han Li said with a smile.

A hint of elation immediately appeared on Wyrm 3's face upon hearing this, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "Thank you, Fellow Daoist, I'll remember this favor."

"There's no need to be so formal, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3. We're part of the same organization from now on, so it's only right that we help each other," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

One of the reasons why Han Li had decided to accept this mission was so that Wyrm 3 would owe him a favor, and with that in mind, he accepted the jade slip before pressing it against his own forehead.

The jade slip contained a pill recipe, but it was a recipe for a dao pill.

However, it was also not quite the same as other dao pills as the refinement process was simpler. It seemed that some steps had been removed, while some ingredients had also been replaced, producing a rather strange recipe.

The primary ingredient for this recipe was a type of yin-attribute material, indicating that it was a recipe for a yin-attribute dao pill.

After Han Li removed the jade slip from his forehead, Wyrm 3 immediately asked, "Will you be able to refine the pill, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3?"

"I've never come into contact with this pill recipe before, but the refinement process isn't all that complicated, so I should be up to the task," Han Li replied.

Wyrm 3 was ecstatic to hear this.

"Fantastic! You're doing me a huge favor, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5!"

Chapter 379: Imprisoned

"I'm confident in my abilities to refine this pill, but there's something that I have to make clear in advance," Han Li said.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5, I'll be sure to help you in any way that I can," Wyrm 3 prompted.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, I'm not going to state any unreasonable demands. It's just that this is a completely unfamiliar pill to me, so I'll require many batches of ingredients for practice. I'm sure that's something you're already aware of," Han Li explained.

Wyrm 3's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he flipped a hand over to produce a storage ring as he replied, "There's no need to worry about ingredients at all, Fellow Daoist. I've already considered this matter, and I've prepared 30 batches of ingredients for you to experiment with."

"It appears my concerns were unnecessary," Han Li said with a faint smile, then accepted the storage ring and stowed it away without examining its contents.

He couldn't release his spiritual sense out of his body, so it would've been rather inconvenient for him to examine the storage ring's contents, but he was sure that there wouldn't be any problems.

Additionally, he also developed a new understanding of just how wealthy the Reincarnation Palace was. The ingredients required to refine this pill weren't quite as rare and precious as those for the dao pill, but they were certainly not easy to come by, either, so 30 batches would've amounted to an astronomical sum in Immortal Origin Stones.

"Ingredients are easy to come by, but a Dao Pill Master is far rarer. All you need to focus on is refining the pill within 10 years. Don't worry about ingredients, if there's not enough there, I'll find a way to get you more," Wyrm 3 assured with a smile.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "10 years? I'm afraid that might not be enough time for me to guarantee a successful outcome."

"At the very most, we can only wait 15 years. This is a very important matter, so please do your best, Fellow Daoist. Our Reincarnation Palace will be sure to reward you handsomely for your efforts," Wyrm 3 said with a solemn expression.

"I'll be sure to do my best, but I still can't make any guarantees. After all, I only recently became a Dao Pil Master, so my skills may not yet be up to scratch," Han Li replied.

Wyrm 3 merely continued to look at Han Li in silence upon hearing this.

"Time is of the essence, so I won't delay any longer. I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

"You wish to leave this place, Fellow Daoist?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"That's right. I'll return to my cave abode right away to study this pill recipe, and I'll contact you if I need anything," Han Li replied with a nod.

"There's no need to do that. We have a pill refinement chamber and a cauldron prepared for you, so just refine the pill here. If you need anything else, I would also be able to deliver them to you in a timely fashion," Wyrm 3 said.

"I appreciate the kind offer, but I'm more accustomed to refining pills in my own cave abode," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

Wyrm 3 cleared his throat, then said in a meaningful voice, "Truth be told, the Black Wind Sea is not very safe at the moment, so if you trigger another pill tribulation, you may not be able to make a safe retreat as you did last time."

"But..."

Before Han Li had a chance to protest, Wyrm 3 raised a hand to cut him off as he said in a cold voice, "If there aren't any other problems, then I'll take you to the pill refinement chamber right away."

Han Li could only give a resigned nod in response.

"Come with me, Fellow Daoist," Wyrm 3 said as he turned to depart.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he followed along.

The two of them quickly emerged from the cave, following which Wyrm 3 summoned a flying carriage that carried the two of them toward the outskirts of the mountain before landing halfway up another tall mountain.

This was quite a large area, but it was riddled with huge trees, and there was a waterfall nearby, but aside from the splashing of the waterfall, the environment was quite peaceful.

On the mountain face up ahead was an opening that was sealed by a large gate with a layer of azure light over its surface, and there were numerous runes surging incessantly over the azure light barrier, presenting a rather mysterious sight to behold.

Wyrm 3 strode forward before pulling out an azure badge, then waved it through the air to release a streak of azure light that vanished into the stone gate in a flash.

The azure light barrier outside the stone gate quickly faded, and the gate was slowly opened.

"This is where you'll be staying, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5. I assure you that no one will come to disturb you during your pill refinement," Wyrm 3 said.

Han Li nodded in response, then made his way into the cave abode.

In the next instant, he was surprised to discover that the spiritual sense restriction had completely vanished as soon as he stepped into the cave abode, but his spiritual sense was still only restricted to the confines of the cave abode.

The cave abode wasn't very large, but it was immaculately maintained and had everything that one could require, including a pill refinement chamber, a secret chamber, and a medicine garden.

"This is quite a nice cave abode," Han Li remarked to Wyrm 3.

"I'm glad you like it, Fellow Daoist. If you need anything, feel free to contact me anytime. In the meantime, I'll be counting on you," Wyrm 3 said before departing from the cave abode, and as soon as he left, the gate of the cave abode swung shut, following which Han Li heaved a faint sigh.

It appeared that he had been imprisoned.

Following Wyrm 3's departure, Han Li briefly explored the cave abode while flicking his fingers through the air to release a series of array tools that vanished into different parts of the cave abode.

Close to an hour later, Han Li arrived in a secret chamber in the cave abode before sitting down with his legs crossed.

The first thing that he did was remove the azure mask from his face before replacing it with the crimson lion mask, and the mask immediately released a burst of gentle energy that spread over his entire body at his behest.

Han Li could sense that at this moment, his aura had been perfectly concealed, indicating that the restrictions in this crimson mask were more profound than the ones in his azure mask.

Most importantly, the special spiritual sense fluctuations generated due to his cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique had also been concealed.

Ever since he arrived in the Immortal Realm, Han Li had always been rather apprehensive when it came to meeting others, particularly those who possessed a superior cultivation base to his. He would always do his best to restrain his spiritual sense fluctuations so that no one would be able to detect that he had cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique, and thankfully, he hadn't encountered any surveyors up to this point.

Now that he had this new mask, even if he did encounter some surveyors who had cultivated special detection secret techniques, he should've been able to fool them as long as their cultivation base wasn't far superior to his.

Han Li made a hand seal, and a layer of red light immediately emerged over the crimson mask before forming a crimson light screen in front of him.

After that, he released several missions in succession, all of which were acquisition missions for the other ingredients required to refine the Golden Soul Pill.

After doing all of that, he swept a sleeve through the air to wave the crimson light screen away, then flipped a hand over to produce the gray jade slip that contained the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Even though he only had 15 years to refine the pill, he wasn't planning to begin right away.

For other Dao Pill Masters, 15 years would've indeed been a very tight timeframe, but this was naturally not a problem for Han Li.

At this point, only several of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had recovered since the last time it had conjured up the wall of light, but all he needed were 18 functional Time Dao Runes to fulfill his pill refinement needs.

Furthermore, the refinement process for this pill was far simpler than that of the Time Dao Pill, and with his Mantra Treasured Axis up his sleeve and so many batches of ingredients at his disposal, he naturally had no concerns.

Hence, his top priority at the moment was to cultivate the Spirit Refinement Technique and resolve his spiritual sense crisis.

With that in mind, Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip and carefully read through the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, then sat down with his legs crossed and began to cultivate.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 was walking down a black passageway countless kilometers away from Han Li with a contemplative look in his eyes.

The passageway wasn't very long, so he was able to quickly reach the end, at which point a black stone gate that was over 30 feet tall appeared before him.

With a sweep of his sleeve, he sent an incantation seal flying through the air, and the black stone gate slowly opened to reveal a spacious hall, at the center of which stood a figure dressed in a black cloak.

There was a cross design embroidered onto the sleeve of the cloak, and upon hearing the sound of footsteps, the cloaked figure turned around.

It was a middle-aged man, but there was a horrific scar that ran across his forehead from its left corner all the way to his right eyelid before continuing down his cheek, presenting a menacing sight to behold.

"What are you doing here?" Wyrm 3 asked in a cold voice.

"I came here because I have something to speak to you about. Rest assured, no one would've been able to track me here," the cloaked man replied.

"Have you found out something?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"Just as you predicted, it really is under Red Moon Island, but due to the involvement of Black Wind Island, our people are unable to get close to the area for the time being," the cloaked man replied.

"Black Wind Island? How are those people possibly able to stop us?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"What if I were to tell you that there are Golden Immortal cultivators among them?" the cloaked figure replied with a faint smile.

A sharp gleam immediately flashed through Wyrm 3's eyes upon hearing this. "Could it be..."

"According to the information that we've gathered so far, the situation is exactly as you're thinking right now," the cloaked figure replied with a nod.

"I don't care how you do it, but you have to figure everything out about the situation on Red Moon Island before the Origin Void Pill is successfully refined," Wyrm 3 said in a categorical voice.

"I would've done that even if you hadn't told me. I came here because I wanted to confirm something. I heard that you're planning to assign the Origin Void Pill refinement mission to a new member who's only just joined our Reincarnation Palace, is that correct?" the cloaked man asked.

Chapter 380: Unexpectedly Smooth Progress

"That's right. Right now, his name is Dragon 5," Wyrm 3 replied without any hesitation.

The cloaked man's brows furrowed slightly as he asked, "How much time did you give him?"

"15 years," Wyrm 3 replied.

"Pardon me for being blunt, but I don't think even Master Ximen would be able to guarantee the successful refinement of an Origin Void Pill in 15 years," the cloaked man said in a meaningful voice.

"That may be true, but at the moment, Master Ximen isn't in this immortal region, and we have less than 20 years left to make our move. Do we have any other choice?" Wyrm 3 asked.

The cloaked man was silent for a moment, then said, "This is an extremely important matter, and that person has only just joined our Reincarnation Palace. Are you sure he's reliable?"

"I don't know, so I didn't allow him to leave," Wyrm 3 replied.

"What if he can't complete the mission within 15 years?" the cloaked man asked with a concerned expression.

"So many things have happened recently. There weren't many Reincarnation Disciples in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region to begin with, and the battle of the Blaze Dragon Dao has certainly not helped our cause. If we can succeed in this endeavor, then everything that we've sacrificed up to this point will be worth it. Hence, success is our only option," Wyrm 3 said in a determined voice.

"It sounds like you're very confident in this person. Could it be that you've already been secretly observing him for some time?" the cloaked man asked.

"No, I've only just come into contact with him," Wyrm 3 replied with a shake of his head.

The cloaked man's brows furrowed tightly upon hearing this.

"Rest assured, I take sole responsibility for this matter. All you need to do is focus on the task assigned to you and figure out what's happening on Red Moon Island," Wyrm 3 continued.

"Alright, if you're that confident, then I won't speak any further on this subject," the cloaked man said.

"I've answered all of your questions. This is not a place you should stay at for any extended period of time, so you should leave, and let's not meet again anytime soon," Wyrm 3 said in a cold voice.

"Alright, I'll be taking my leave then," the cloaked man said as a burst of black light appeared over his body, and he faded into the darkness like a shadow.

Wyrm 3 sat by himself for a moment, then rose to his feet and cast his gaze in the direction of Han Li's cave abode.

……

10 years flew by in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed in his peaceful cave abode, sitting as still as a stone statue.

His head was enshrouded within a layer of bright translucent light, making his facial features appear rather blurry and indistinct.

The translucent light was gently flowing like water, presenting a pleasant sight to behold.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyelids fluttered slightly before his eyes sprang open.

The translucent light circling around his head instantly surged into his glabella, vanishing without a trace.

Han Li exhaled as an elated look appeared on his face.

After 10 years of tireless cultivation, he had finally made some inroads into the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

His spiritual sense hadn't been enhanced by much, but the lurking unrest in his spiritual sense had already subsided, restoring it to a stable and uninhibited state.

However, in the next instant, the elation in his eyes faded and was replaced by a hint of befuddlement.

According to the jade slip, the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique was far more profound than the third level, and it should've taken more than 10 times the amount of time to master the fourth level, so it should've taken him decades, perhaps even over a century to make the progress that he had already achieved.

Hence, he wasn't even planning to get this far, and his initial goal was only to settle the unrest in his spiritual sense. After all, he still had the pill refinement mission on his plate, so he didn't have much time to work with.

However, to his surprise, his cultivation of the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique had been extremely smooth, and he hadn't encountered any bottlenecks, thereby allowing him to make rapid progress.

His mind was racing as he tried to find a reason for this, but he remained completely stumped.

At the moment, he could only attribute it to aptitude. Perhaps his current constitution was simply very suited to cultivating secret techniques of this nature.

Thinking back, he had had a similar experience in his cultivation of the Great Development Arts.

In any case, he had to stop now. There were only five years left of the allotted 15 years, so he had to commence the pill refinement process.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to produce a storage ring, the very same one that had been given to him by Wyrm 3.

He then injected his spiritual sense into it to confirm that there were indeed 30 batches of ingredients inside.

Right as he was about to commence his first pill refinement attempt, his expression suddenly changed slightly, and he pulled out a batch of ingredients from the storage ring.

He paid no heed to the other ingredients as he focused his gaze on a fist-sized black crystal.

The crystalline material was giving off a layer of faint black light that seemed to be able to suck in all of the surrounding light, and at the same time, it was also giving off a burst of formidable law power fluctuations.

This was none other than the primary ingredient required to refine the Origin Void Pill, and it was called the Black Marrow Crystal.

Han Li reached out to pick up the Black Marrow Crystal, and he was immediately struck by a burst of sharp pain in his fingertips.

The peculiar law powers being released by the Black Marrow Crystal were extremely corrosive, and it was almost too painful for him to hold onto even with his Profound Immortal physique.

A burst of spiritual light appeared over the surface of his palm, instantly forming a layer of azure light that protected his fingers from the Black Marrow Crystal.

At the same time, he flipped his other hand over to produce the Hard Ink Crystal.

These two items were very similar in appearance and aura, except the aura emanating from the Black Marrow Crystal was many times more formidable than that of the Hard Ink Crystal.

It seemed that these two materials were somehow related, and he couldn't help but wonder if Wyrm 3 had previously asked him about the Hard Ink Crystal for the sake of these Black Marrow Crystals.

However, even Hard Ink Crystals were extremely rare in the Black Wind Sea, so how had he managed to acquire so many Black Marrow Crystals?

As soon as this thought sprang into his mind, Han Li immediately shook his head to cast it aside.

His mission was only to refine an Origin Void Pill, so there was no point in thinking about other unnecessary things.

With that in mind, he stowed the Hard Ink Crystal away, then pulled out the jade slip that contained the pill recipe before pressing it against his own forehead.

Half a month passed by in the blink of an eye.

At this moment, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes closed, and there were exactly 30 piles of identical spirit materials laid out on the ground around him.

All of a sudden, his eyes sprang open, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of silver light, which landed on the ground in front of him before transforming into a silver cauldron.

Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth to release a stream of silver flames that began scorching the underside of the cauldron.

Han Li gave a slight nod upon seeing this, then raised a hand, upon which a certain material from one of the 30 piles of materials rose up into the air before flying into the cauldron.

At the same time, his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light, and his time law thread shot out of his fingertip before wrapping itself around the axis.

The time law thread was looking a little brighter than before, but it was still far from returning to its peak.

At this point, only 18 of the 360 Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis were lit, while the rest remained dim.

It seemed that the time law thread was connected to his Mantra Treasured Axis, and it was most likely the case that the time law thread would only make a full recovery once all of the Time Dao Runes were restored.

With that in mind, he made a hand seal, and a burst of golden ripples surged out of the Mantra Treasured Axis to encompass the cauldron, instantly causing everything unfolding within it to slow down.

With only 18 Time Dao Runes restored, the axis's time-slowing effect was quite limited, but it was already sufficient for Han Li's needs.

While Han Li was busy with his pill refinement, the centennial teleportation array activation day had arrived on Black Wind Island.

The streets and shops in Black Wind City were looking far less lively and bustling than before, and aside from some of the prosperous streets at the center of the city, the rest of the city appeared rather bleak and deserted.

There weren't many pedestrians on the streets, and many shop employees looked as if they were on the verge of nodding off to sleep.

For some reason, there had been a huge spike in the number and frequency of natural disasters taking place in the Black Wind Sea of late, including tsunamis, volcanic eruptions, and ferocious storms.

Many islands were destroyed during these disasters, resulting in countless deaths and casualties, and the entire Black Wind Sea was in a state of unease and apprehension, with some rumors even suggesting that the entire region was facing imminent destruction.

Even the conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island had temporarily subsided in the wake of these horrific disasters.

Black Wind Island wasn't affected by these disasters, but business in Black Wind City severely impacted, and there weren't even many people who had gathered to watch the activation of the teleportation array, an event that had always been highly anticipated in the past.

The teleportation array inside the pagoda was buzzing while radiating dazzling light, and two figures were standing nearby, one of whom was none other than the master of Black Wind Island, Lu Jun.

At this moment, he was looking intently at the teleportation array with a hint of excitement in his eyes, and he was accompanied by a white-robed man, the very same one with the Feng surname who had led that group of True Immortal cultivators into the Black Wind Sea.

He was also looking at the teleportation array, but he appeared far calmer and more indifferent.

All of a sudden, an enormous pillar of light erupted out of the teleportation array, causing the entire teleportation pagoda to tremble slightly.

The pillar of light faded after a few seconds, and a group of around two dozen people emerged within the teleportation array.

These people were split up into two roughly equal factions, and the two factions were standing quite far apart from one another.

Chapter 381: Various Powers

Among the two factions of people that had appeared in the teleportation array, one of them were mostly wearing white-robed with golden clouds embroidered upon them, and if Han Li were present, he would've immediately been able to identify their leader as none other than the master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, Xiao Jinhan.

Behind him were four or five other people dressed in Northern Glacial Immortal Palace attire, including Deputy Palace Master Xue Ying and the Golden Immortal, Lu Yue.

Aside from them, there were also three Blaze Dragon Dao dao lords led by Ouyang Kuishan.

As for the other group, they were all dressed in the signature blue robes of the Vast Flow Palace, and they were led by Grand Palace Master Luo Qinghai.

Beside Luo Qinghai stood an effeminate young man who appeared to have been in his early twenties, and even though he was a man, he struck the beholder with the impression that they were looking at a beautiful woman.

As for the rest of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators, most of them had been present during the battle of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

There was an excited look on Lu Jun's face as he stepped forward before extending a respectful salute. "I am the master of Black Wind Island, Lu Jun, and I would like to extend a warm welcome to Palace Master Jin and Grand Palace Master Luo, as well as all other seniors and fellow daoists. It is truly an honor for our Black Wind Island to be hosting all of you."

The man with the Feng surname beside him also stepped forward before extending a respectful salute toward Xiao Jinhan.

Xiao Jinhan merely gave the two a slight nod, then led the way out of the teleportation array.

Meanwhile, Luo Qinghai returned Lu Jun's salute as he said, "You're far too kind, Island Master Lu."

After that, he and the Vast Flow Palace cultivators also emerged from the teleportation array.

Lu Jun's duo immediately stepped aside upon seeing this, and it was as if the two of them were acting as servants, while all of the other Black Wind Island cultivators present were standing respectfully to the side, not daring to make even a single sound.

"So this is the Black Wind Sea. The world's origin qi here is a little sparse, but overall, it's not a bad place," Luo Qinghai remarked as he made his way over to a window of the teleportation pagoda before looking outside.

"I didn't think that we would meet again so soon after we last met in the Blaze Dragon Dao. What a coincidence this is, Fellow Daoist Luo," Xiao Jinhan said as he took a glance at Luo Qinghai.

"I also wasn't expecting to see you again at Wave View City, Palace Master Xiao. May I ask why so many of your Northern Glacial Immortal Palace's cultivators have come to this secluded region on this occasion? If you require the assistance of our Vast Flow Palace, please feel free to tell me, and we'll be happy to do your bidding," Luo Qinghai replied with a smile.

A cold smile appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face upon hearing this, and he took a glance at the Vast Flow Palace cultivators before replying, "Why ask a question you already know the answer to, Fellow Daoist Luo? At the moment, the Vast Flow Palace is truly at the height of its powers.

“Not only does it have the Five Extreme Palace Masters on the Upper Arr Continent, the Seven Vast Flow Disciples are also vastly renowned. Even the young man standing beside you right now possesses exceptional aptitude that I'm extremely envious of. What right do I have to ask all of you to do my bidding?"

Luo Qinghai's smile remained unchanged as he said, "Oh, how rude of me. This is my disciple, Nan Kemeng. Meng'er, pay your respects to Palace Master Xiao. Right now, Palace Master Xiao is the most powerful figure in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region. If you can receive some guidance from him, you'll stand to benefit for the rest of your life."

Nan Kemeng's brows furrowed slightly in reluctance, but he still did as he was told, stepping forward as he cupped his fist in a salute. "Junior Nan Kemeng pays his respects to Palace Master Xiao."

Xiao Jinhan merely nodded in response in an expressionless manner.

Luo Qinghai gestured for Nan Kemeng to step back behind him, then said, "As we both know, that place has descended upon the Black Wind Sea. Given your powers and sources, I'm sure you've already uncovered the location of its entrance, right?"

"You have far too high an opinion of our Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, Fellow Daoist Luo. We've only just received wind of this matter," Xiao Jinhan harrumphed coldly.

"Is that so? If you still haven't uncovered the location, then those people from the Dawn Fall Sect most likely haven't found it, either. In that case, it looks like our Vast Flow Palace still has some chances," Luo Qinghai chuckled.

"Are you saying that there are already members of the Dawn Fall Sect here?" Xiao Jinhan asked.

"I'm not sure, I've only been hearing some rumors. Oh, by the way, I also heard that the grand elders of the Dawn Fall Sect seem to have already come out of seclusion," Luo Qinghai replied in an ambiguous fashion.

"You really do have some exceptional sources, Fellow Daoist Luo," Xiao Jinhan said as his eyes narrowed slightly.

"You're far too kind, Palace Master Xiao. No one's sources can compare with the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace's in this immortal region. Baili Yan had done everything in his power to hide himself in the Blaze Dragon Dao, yet you were still able to find him," Luo Qinghai remarked as he took a meaningful glance at the three dao lords behind Xiao Jinhan.

An awkward look immediately appeared on the faces of Ouyang Kuishan's trio, while Xiao Jinhan's expression also darkened slightly upon hearing this.

"It looks like Island Master Lu still has some matters to report to Palace Master Xiao, so I won't stay here and act as an eyesore any longer," Luo Qinghai said with a smile as he glanced at Lu Jun.

A slightly awkward look appeared on Lu Jun's face upon hearing this, and he said, "Not at all, Grand Palace Master Luo. Both of you are esteemed guests of our Black Wind Sea, so..."

However, he was cut off mid-sentence by Xiao Jinhan, who said in a cold voice, "If you wish to leave, then feel free to do so, Fellow Daoist Luo. I'm sure we'll meet again soon."

Luo Qinghai cupped his fist in a salute toward Xiao Jinhan with a faint smile, following which he quickly led all of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators out of the teleportation pagoda.

They didn't linger in Black Wind City, either, flying directly toward the city gate before quickly vanishing into the distance.

Meanwhile, Xiao Jinhan looked on at their departing figures with a contemplative look in his eyes, but it was unclear what he was thinking.

"Palace Master, he seems to know a lot about the situation," Xue Ying remarked as she approached Xiao Jinhan.

"He's always been renowned for being a sly old fox, so it's no surprise that he's managed to gather some information," Xiao Jinhan replied in a cold voice.

"Do you think he's already ascertained the location of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor?" Xue Ying asked in a slightly hesitant voice.

"That's hard to say, but it doesn't matter even if he has found out the location. While it's true that he's quite slippery and cunning, he doesn't possess sufficient power to pose a significant threat. In contrast, I'm much more worried about the Reincarnation Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect," Xiao Jinhan replied.

"The Reincarnation Palace has always been a formidable foe, but as for the Dawn Fall Sect... Are you referring to their grand elder, Feng Tiandu?" Xue Ying asked.

"That's right. There are only two people who I view as substantial threats in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region. At this point, Baili Yan is no longer worthy of concern, so Feng Tiandu is the only one left," Xiao Jinhan said in a cold voice.

Xue Ying didn't know how to respond to this, so she could only stand off to the side in silence.

Xiao Jinhan also stood in silence for a while before turning to Lu Jun and the man with the Feng surname as he instructed, "Give me a detailed rundown of all of the information that you've gathered thus far."

……

Meanwhile, there was a massive gray flying boat racing through the boundless Soul Stirrin Winds of the Black Wind Sea.

The boat was 2,000 to 3,000 feet in length and had been entirely constructed from some type of gray bone material. It appeared a little old and dilapidated, and there were even some large holes on some parts of the boat, while its surface was riddled with some indistinct patterns.

In the face of the boundless Soul Stirring Winds, the boat was made to resemble a small raft in a turbulent sea, looking as if it could capsize at any moment, but if one were to look closely, they would discover that the indistinct patterns on the boat were releasing a thin layer of gray light that kept the Soul Stirring Winds at bay.

The ghastly wailing and sobbing ringing out from the Soul Stirring Winds were also kept out by the layer of gray light, and that was why the boat was able to travel through the Soul Stirring Winds without any trouble.

Seated with his legs crossed at the bow of the boat was a thin and wizened middle-aged man.

His cheeks were extremely sunken, while his skin was green and purple in color, giving him the appearance of a zombie. Furthermore, there were countless dark azure chains wrapped around all parts of his body, and they were occasionally swaying around in the air of their own accord, presenting a very peculiar sight to behold.

The zombie-like man was looking directly forward with two balls of green flames shimmering in his pupils, and there was a complex gray array engraved onto the boat beneath him, extending in all directions to all parts of the boat.

Right at this moment, a figure emerged from within the boat before arriving beside the zombie-like man.

It was a man who appeared to have been 30 to 40 years of age, and he was dressed in a gray brocade robe.

His left eye was tightly shut, and there was a deep scar on his eyelid, indicating that he had been dealt an extremely severe injury there.

"Can you still keep going, Senior Martial Brother?" the gray-robed man asked.

"I'm fine," the zombie-like man replied.

"It's a good thing that we have this flying boat of yours. Otherwise, there's no way we'd be able to pass through these Soul Stirring Winds," the gray-robed man said with a smile.

"These Soul Stirring Winds are indeed quite formidable, but there are many ways to pass through them," the zombie-like man replied in an indifferent voice.

"I would say that there are no more than three people in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region that can say that. I may be the master of the Dawn Fall Sect, but even I wouldn't dare to make such a bold claim," the gray-robed man said with a smile.

A hint of pride flashed through the zombie-like man's eyes upon hearing this.

"Rest assured, Senior Martial Brother, I'll be sure to do everything in my power to help you obtain the treasures required for you to reach the High Zenith Stage," the gray-robed man vowed with a serious expression.

"You have my thanks, Junior Martial Brother," the zombie-like man replied with a nod.

"There's no need to thank me, Senior Martial Brother," the gray-robed man said as he hurriedly waved a hand in response.

Right at this moment, a thought seemed to have occurred to the zombie-like man, and a cold gleam appeared in his eyes as he said, "There's been too much on my plate lately, so I didn't get a chance to ask, but have we still not managed to uncover the identity of the culprit who killed Fang Pan and Zhong Luan?"

Chapter 382: Backup Plan

"We've already managed to uncover the identity of the culprit. It's a cultivator by the name of Li Feiyu, and he joined the Blaze Dragon Dao several centuries, but before we had a chance to go after him, the event concerning Baili Yan took place in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and in the wake of the chaos, he went missing.

“The Immortal Palace is actively hunting for him, but according to my knowledge, they still haven't been able to capture him," the gray-robed man replied.

"Li Feiyu..." the zombie-like man murmured to himself as he brows furrowed slightly.

"Rest assured, Senior Martial Brother. Once we're finished with what we're doing here, I'll be sure to send out more people to ensure his capture, and once we have him, you can do with him as you please," the gray-robed man hurriedly said.

The zombie-like man was silent for a moment, then said in a solemn voice, "The Origin Separation Law Chains that I bestowed upon Fang Pan and Zhong Luan have most likely fallen into his hands. Those chains must be recovered."

"Yes, Senior Martial Brother," the gray-robed man replied.

With that, the zombie-like man closed his eyes.

The gray-robed man promptly departed upon seeing this, making his way into the cabin, where there were many more people seated inside.

……

On the other side of the Black Wind Sea, a ball of golden light that was several thousand feet in size was flying through the Soul Stirring Winds.

The golden light was extremely radiant, and it contained a massive golden beetle with purple patterns all over its body, giving it a very menacing appearance.

There were also threads of piercing translucent light interspersed throughout the golden light, and they appeared extremely sharp.

The golden beetle's mouth was wide open, releasing a burst of suction force that allowed it to devour all of the Soul Stirring Winds surging toward it, and at this moment, there was a silver-robed woman seated atop the beetle's body.

The woman appeared to have been in her late twenties, and she was wearing a silver crown and a pair of silver earrings. Her feet were bare with two silver rings around her ankles, attached to each of which were several bells.

She was quite a beautiful woman, but her eyes were extremely cold, like a glacier that would remain frozen solid for the rest of eternity, and the ghastly sounds ringing out from within the Soul Stirring Winds seemed to have no effect on her at all.

A pleased look appeared in her eyes at how freely the golden beetle was able to fly through the Soul Stirring Winds, and she murmured to herself, "Not bad. It looks like all of the resources I invested into you were worth it."

The golden beetle immediately let loose a string of screeches in protest while swaying its body violently from side to side in an attempt to shake off the woman sitting on its back.

The silver-robed woman's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and she hurriedly began chanting an incantation while flicking her fingers through the air, sending a series of incantation seals flying into the golden beetle's body.

The golden beetle shuddered as a series of silver threads around it, then transformed into thick silver chains that were embedded deep into its body.

The golden beetle immediately let loose an agonized screech and quickly settled down.

Only then did the silver-robed woman withdraw her hand seal, upon which all of the silver chains faded away.

"Why is it still so violent and untamed even though I've already used the Spirit Imprisonment Technique on it?" the silver-robed woman murmured to herself as her brows furrowed slightly.

After pondering this question for a while, she shook her head as she sighed, "I'll address this matter after this trip."

She then made a hand seal, and her body transformed into a ball of bright silver light that slowly vanished into the body of the golden beetle beneath her.

The golden beetle immediately shuddered, and the golden light radiating from its body became roughly twice as bright, while the speed of its flight was also significantly enhanced.

……

Close to five years passed by in the blink of an eye.

The secret area of the Reincarnation Palace was just as peaceful as usual, and in a hall within the mountain sat two figures across from one another. They were none other than Wyrm 3 and the man with the scar running down his face.

The scar-faced man had a rather grim look on his face, and even though Wyrm 3 was wearing a mask, it was clear from the look in her eyes that he was also feeling quite tense.

"How are things going on the outside?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"Xiao Jinhan came to the Black Wind Sea several years ago, and the same applies to the cultivators of the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect. All of them are led by their respective sect masters, and I've heard that there's a very good chance that Grand Elder Feng Tiandu of the Dawn Fall Sect has also arrived," the scar-faced man replied with a concerned expression.

"It looks like they're all determined to capitalize on this opportunity," Wyrm 3 remarked with a cold smile.

"The current situation has already exceeded our expectations. Should we make a report to our higher-ups as a safety precaution?" the scar-faced man asked.

"There's no need for that. The Northern Glacial Immortal Region, the Vast Flow Palace, and the Dawn Fall Sect are all in opposition against one another, and we can use that to our advantage, pitting them against each other while we complete our mission," Wyrm 3 replied with a shake of his head.

"That would naturally be ideal, but what I'm worried about is that they could come to a secret agreement to join forces against us. If that happens, then we'll be in trouble," the scar-faced man said with furrowed brows.

"The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace took advantage of the incident concerning Baili Yan to take over the Blaze Dragon Dao, and both the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect are aware of this. They may not have openly expressed any discontent, but the chances of them working with the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace are very slim.

“Even if they do come to some type of collaborative agreement, I've already made plans for such an eventuality, so there's nothing to worry about," Wyrm 3 said.

"In that case, I feel a lot more reassured," the scar-faced man replied as his expression eased slightly.

"Have you ascertained the situation on Red Moon Island, Fellow Daoist Chi?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"Rest assured, everything has already been finalized," the scar-faced man replied.

"Good," Wyrm 3 replied with a nod.

"All that's missing now is the Origin Void Pill. The time limit of 15 years that you gave Dragon 5 is already up. Has he managed to refine an Origin Void Pill?" the scar-faced man asked.

Wyrm 3 fell silent upon hearing this, and his expression darkened slightly.

"It appears my concerns about him were justified. We don't have much time left at this point. What do we do now?" the scar-faced man asked with a grim expression.

"We'll have to fall back on our backup plan, but the success rate of that plan will be significantly lower," Wyrm 3 sighed.

"I suppose we have no other choice. As for Dragon 5, I suggest we strip him of his status of Reincarnation Disciple with immediate effect. On top of that, he knows so many of our secrets, so we have to..."

Before the scar-faced man had a chance to finish, the entire surrounding space suddenly began to tremble violently.

The hall that the two of them were situated in also began to quiver and quake, and the two of them exchanged a glance before immediately flying out of the hall, emerging from the belly of the mountain in the blink of an eye.

The sky in the secret area had been bright and clear just a moment ago, yet a dense blanket of dark clouds had suddenly taken shape, and there were countless bolts of black lightning flashing through the clouds, causing a deafening commotion.

An ecstatic look appeared in Wyrm 3's eyes upon seeing this. "Could it be..."

The same expression had also appeared in the scar-faced man's eyes.

All of a sudden, all of the world's origin qi in the entire secret area began to fluctuate violently before converging toward the dark cloud up above.

The black cloud rapidly expanded outward in all directions while revolving on the spot, forming a black vortex directly above Han Li's cave abode.

At this point, several more True Immortal cultivators had flown out from all parts of the secret area, and one of them was none other than Wildcat 16, who had led Han Li to this place.

"Activate the restrictions! Hurry!" Wyrm 3 instructed as he began making a string of hand seals.

Wildcat 16 and the others immediately sprang into action, flying to all parts of the secret area.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 began to chant an incantation, and a burst of dazzling golden light erupted out of his body before shooting up into the sky to form a massive pillar of golden light.

There were countless golden runes flashing over the pillar of light, and bursts of tremendous energy fluctuations were surging through the air, causing the nearby space to tremble incessantly.

The scar-faced man shuddered in the face of these formidable energy fluctuations, and a hint of bewilderment appeared in his eyes as he flew several hundred feet to the side before turning his gaze to Wyrm 3.

At this point, eight more giant pillars of golden light had appeared all over the secret area, amounting to a total of nine pillars of golden light that were erupting into the heavens.

A vast expanse of golden light appeared over the entire secret area before spreading outward like rippling water, forming an enormous golden array that encompassed the entire sky in the blink of an eye.

The black cloud up above was enshrouded within the golden array, and it seemed to have fallen under some kind of restriction that prevented it from growing any larger.

The enormous law aura emanating out the black cloud was also sealed within the golden array, rendering it unable to spread outside of the secret area.

A hint of relief flashed through Wyrm 3's eyes upon seeing this.

Even though the black cloud had been restrained, the surrounding world's origin qi continued to converge toward it, completely unobstructed by the golden array.

As time passed, the black cloud became denser and denser until it almost appeared substantial in form.

Bursts of tremendous law fluctuations were emanating out of the black cloud and sweeping toward the surrounding golden array, causing it to tremble violently, and the section of the array closest to the black cloud suddenly crumbled altogether.

Wyrm 3 was very alarmed by this turn of events, and he made a rapid string of hand seals to release a series of incantation seals, upon which the pillar of golden light around his body instantly became significantly brighter. The other pillars of light also brightened as they surged into the golden array up above.

As a result, countless golden runes surged out of the broken section of the array, and it was quickly restored to its original state and had become even brighter than before.

Meanwhile, the fluctuations erupting out of the black cloud were becoming more and more formidable, and it didn't take long before the golden array was torn open again, only to be quickly mended once again under the collective efforts of Wyrm 3 and the others.

The cycle of destruction and repair continued, and the golden array was shuddering incessantly the entire time, but it was able to confine the black cloud to the secret area.

Chapter 383: Departure

As the black cloud revolved faster and faster, more and more bolts of black lightning appeared within the black vortex at the center of the cloud, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out as a thick pillar of black light came crashing down from the the center of the vortex, plummeting directly toward Han Li's cave abode.

Right at his moment, a burst of bright gray light erupted out of the top of Han Li's cave abode before forming a gray mountain projection in the blink of an eye.

The pillar of black light struck the mountain projection as soon as it took shape, and an earth-shattering boom rang out as the pillar of black light pierced straight through the projection before crashing into the cave abode down below.

The entire secret area shuddered violently as countless cracks appeared all over all of the nearby mountains, and countless rocks came falling down like rain.

After releasing the pillar of black light, the black cloud in the sky rapidly shrank down before vanishing altogether in just a few seconds.

Everything returned to normal in the secret area, and it was as if the black cloud had never even appeared.

After the black cloud faded, the massive golden array that encompassed the entire secret area was also stabilized.

Wyrm 3 made a hand seal, and the pillar of golden light around him vanished.

An anxious look appeared on his face, and he flew toward Han Li's cave abode before the pillar of golden light had even completely faded.

The scar-faced man was just about to join him when a thought seemed to have occurred to him, and he stopped in his tracks.

Wyrm 3 appeared in front of Han Li's cave abode in a flash, but at this moment, the entire cave abode was enshrouded within several light barriers, making it impossible for Wyrm 3 to detect what was happening inside.

He was very anxious to find out what was happening, but he didn't force his way into the cave abode.

Only after a full 15 minutes had passed by did all of the light barriers recede, revealing the gate of the cave abode, which was already wide open.

"Come in, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Han Li invited from within his cave abode.

Wyrm 3 was slightly reassured after hearing the calm tone of Han Li's voice, and he immediately made his way inside.

At this moment, Han Li was standing in the guest hall of his cave abode. His complexion was a little pale, and his aura was also slightly unstable.

There was a black jade box sitting on the table in front of him, and even though the box's lid was tightly shut, there were still faint law power fluctuations emanating out from within.

Wyrm 3's gaze immediately fell upon the jade box.

"What you want is inside the box, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Han Li said with a faint smile as he made an inviting hand gesture.

Wyrm 3 nodded in response, then drew the jade box into his grasp before carefully opening it after taking a deep breath.

Inside the box was a black longan-sized pill that was giving off translucent black radiance, and there was a black dao mark on the pill that was giving off formidable law power fluctuations.

Wyrm 3's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, while Han Li sat down with a faint smile on his face.

"Fantastic! You truly are a man of your word, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5," Wyrm 3 said as he closed the box and stowed it away before raising his head to look at Han Li.

"I was very fortunate to have succeeded. I'm still not very well-versed in the process of refining this Origin Void Pill, so I was only able to refine a single one after exhausting all of the ingredients," Han Li replied with a shake of his head, seemingly not very happy with his own handiwork.

"That's perfectly fine," Wyrm 3 said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

"Thank you for your understanding, Fellow Daoist," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Upon noticing Han Li's pale complexion, Wyrm 3 flipped a hand over to produce a red jade pill before offering it to him. "It looks like the pill refinement process was quite taxing on you. Here's a vial of Vast Heaven Pills. They have exceptional restorative effects, and I'm sure they'll be useful to you."

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist," Han Li said with a nod as he accepted the jade pill.

Through his spiritual sense, he could detect that there were several crimson pills inside the vial, every single one of which was enveloped in a layer of bright crimson light, and they were giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations, indicating that they were very precious pills.

"You're very much welcome, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5. You've done me a huge favor here, so if anyone should be saying thanks, it should be me. This also serves as a test before you get to officially join the Reincarnation Palace, so congratulations on passing," Wyrm 3 said with a smile, then flipped a hand over to produce a crimson jade badge, out of which flew a streak of read light that vanished into the mask on Han Li's face.

The Earthly List projection then emerged from Han Li's mask, and the number contribution points on the bottom now read "60".

This was 10 more than the compensation that he had been promised, so it was a pleasant surprise.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Han Li said. "Now that I've completed the mission, I'll be free to do whatever I please for the next 1,000 years, right?"

"Of course. Do you have any plans, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"I just obtained the fourth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, so I naturally plan to return to my cave abode to cultivate," Han Li replied in a candid fashion.

"If you insist on leaving, then I won't stop you. This is a secret base of our Reincarnation Palace, and I can assure you that it's a safe location. If you ever need to take shelter from something or someone, you can come here at any time. This is the access badge," Wyrm 3 said as he offered a black badge to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the badge, but a wry smile then appeared on his face as he said, "Unfortunately, I still don't possess the ability to pass through the Soul Stirring Winds on my own."

"My apologies, I should've considered that. Here is a Wind Shelter Bead for you. This will allow you to travel safely through the Soul Stirring Winds, and you can have my personal communication array plate as well. If you encounter any problems, you can contact me directly, and I'll be sure to lend you my assistance as long as your request is within the realm of my capabilities," Wyrm 3 said as he offered a black bead and a black array plate to Han Li.

The bead was identical in appearance and aura to the one that Wildcat 16 had used, while the black array plate was giving off rings of black light with countless black runes surging over its surface like stars in the night sky.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist," Han Li said as he stowed the two items away.

Shortly thereafter, a streak of azure light flew out of the secret area.

A spatial exit appeared amid a flash of black light, and the streak of azure light flew into it before vanishing without a trace.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 stood on the black mountain, watching as Han Li departed with a contemplative look on his face.

Right at this moment, the scar-faced man emerged behind him amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

"Are you not planning to bring him along on this trip into the immortal abode? Perhaps his ability to refine Origin Void Pills will be useful to us," the scar-faced man said.

"He's only just become a Reincarnation Disciple, so we still don't know if he's completely reliable. This is a very important mission, and it's best to be more cautious," Wyrm 3 replied.

"While we do have a Void Origin Pill now, we still have a severe shortage of capable personnel. Baili Yan and Daoist Hu Yan have both gone missing, so we don't even have anyone that can directly oppose Xiao Jinhan," the scar-faced man said with a concerned expression.

"According to my knowledge, Baili Yan should still be alive. Now that the emergence of the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace is imminent, he'll be sure to appear as long as he still harbors ambitions of reaching the High Zenith Stage. As for Xiao Jinhan, let's do our best to avoid direct confrontation with him and have the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect deal with him," Wyrm 3 said.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to the scar-faced man, and he said, "By the way, I've just received word that a strange person has appeared near Red Moon Island."

"Who is it?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"It's a silver-robed woman with a giant golden beetle steed. We don't know who she is, but she appears to be a Golden Immortal," the scar-faced man replied.

"A silver-robed woman with a golden beetle... I don't recall anyone of that description in the top three sects of our immortal region. If she's appeared near Red Moon Island, then she's most likely targeting the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor as well," Wyrm 3 mused.

"I've already sent some people to follow her as a safety precaution, but I'm sure she won't be able to have any substantial impact on her own. Now that we have an Origin Void Pill, we can proceed with our original plan, so I have to go and make some preparations," the scar-faced man said.

Before Wyrm 3 had a chance to reply, a vast expanse of black light erupted out of the scar-faced man's body, following which he vanished into thin air.

Wyrm 3 didn't linger much longer, either, flying away as a streak of light.

……

Meanwhile, Han Li had already left the secret area, and he was faced with a boundless expanse of Soul Stirring Wind.

Instead of immediately summoning the Wind Shelter Bead, he raised a hand to conjure up an azure light barrier around his body, keeping out the surrounding Soul Stirring Winds.

Even though the Soul Stirring Winds were kept at bay, the ghastly noises they produced were still able to seep in through the azure light barrier.

Han Li stood with his hands clasped behind his back, and he listened to these harrowing sounds for a while before giving a slight nod.

At the moment, his spiritual sense was extremely stable, completely unaffected by the sounds outside, so it appeared that the spiritual sense crisis was well and truly behind him, at least for the time being.

In the next instant, he swept a sleeve through the air, and a miniature gray mountain flew out of his sleeve.

This was none other than the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain, and he swept his spiritual sense over it momentarily before giving a pleased nod.

He had only attracted a single pill tribulation following his successful refinement of the Origin Void Pill, and the mountain had been able to withstand it with ease.

This served as further confirmation to him that this treasure was indeed able to ward off pill tribulations better than all other immortal treasures.

As for the pale complexion and unstable aura he had displayed at the end, that had merely been a facade to fool Wyrm 3.

On top of that, what he had said about using up all of the pill refinement ingredients was also untrue.

There were still seven batches of ingredients left in his storage bracelet, and he was planning to use them to refine some more Origin Void Pills so that he could study them.

He couldn't shake the feeling that these Origin Void Pills were somehow connected to dao pills, and perhaps uncovering the nature of this connection would help him in his future pill refinement.

Chapter 384: Abnormalities

Having already successfully refined one Origin Void Pill, Han Li was quite confident that he would be able to refine at least one more with the remaining ingredients in his possession.

This time, he was going to see exactly what was so special about these pills.

Having decided on this course of action, he flipped a hand over to summon the Wind Shelter Bead, then injected some immortal spiritual power into it, and it immediately released a burst of black ripples that spread outward in all directions to scatter the surrounding Soul Stirring Winds.

He turned and cast his gaze deep into the Soul Stirring Winds as a contemplative look appeared in his eyes.

He was quite curious about what laid deep within the Soul Stirring Winds, and now that his spiritual sense crisis was behind him, he was considering exploring the area.

However, he then quickly shook his head to rid himself of that idea as he flew away toward the Black Wind Sea as a streak of azure light.

A day and a night later, Han Li reappeared in the sky above a certain region of the Black Wind Sea, and he stowed his Wind Shelter Bead away as he heaved a faint sigh of relief.

Even though the Soul Stirring Winds were no longer able to affect him thanks to the Wind Shelter Bead, it was still quite an uncomfortable experience flying through them for an extended period of time.

Right at this moment, a thought seemed to have occurred to him, and he flipped a hand over to produce his crimson mask before putting it on.

After that, he made a hand seal, and a projection of the missions platform emerged from the mask.

After taking a moment to inspect the missions that he had released, an elated look appeared on his face, and he summoned a small pouch of Immortal Origin Stones that he placed onto the vortex at the center of the missions platform while making a hand seal.

Moments later, those Immortal Origin Stones had turned into seven or eight different types of materials, namely two spirit plants, two demon beast materials, and the rest were all crystals of different colors.

These were all ingredients required to refine the Golden Soul Pill, and he wasn't expecting to gather all of them so quickly.

Han Li carefully examined these materials, and after ensuring that there was nothing wrong with them, he categorized them before stowing them away one by one.

The Golden Soul Pill refinement process wasn't very complex, and given his current pill refinement skills and the trump card that was the Mantra Treasured Axis, one batch of ingredients was sufficient.

After doing all of that, Han Li flew away as a streak of azure light in an unhurried fashion.

Even though he had told Wyrm 3 that he was going to begin cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique, he wasn't actually planning to begin right away. Now that he had temporarily overcome his spiritual sense crisis, his top priority was naturally to make a breakthrough to the Golden Immortal Stage.

Even though he had joined the Reincarnation Palace and become a so-called Reincarnation Disciple, he was still being hunted by the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and his new status as a Reincarnation Disciple would most likely only make him even more of a wanted fugitive in the Immortal Palace's eyes.

In order to weather this storm, he had to do everything in his power to advance his own cultivation base before he considered anything else.

With the Golden Soul Pill all but obtained, he would have no problems undergoing the spiritual evolution process, so the only obstacle in his way right now was that final immortal acupoint.

It certainly sounded simple, but this was the very same hurdle that had stood firm in the face of countless late-True Immortal cultivators in the past.

Han Li couldn't help but heave a faint sigh as this thought occurred to him.

He had been constantly searching for ways to make breakthroughs to the Golden Immortal Stage, and that included trying to find the complete cultivation art for the Great Universe Origin Arts.

He had released multiple missions in the Transient Guild alone, searching for any methods that could help him make a breakthrough or open that final immortal acupoint, and the rewards offered for those missions were all quite substantial, but there had been no responses thus far.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as a determined look appeared on his face, and he made a hand seal, upon which the crimson mask on his face released a layer of crimson light to envelop his entire body.

In the next instant, the crimson light faded, and he had taken on the form of a square-faced middle-aged man with bushy brows.

Immediately thereafter, he made a hand seal, and the speed of his flight increased by roughly twofold as he flew directly toward Black Wind City.

However, he had only flown less than 100,000 kilometers when he suddenly stopped in his tracks.

A burst of thunderous rumbling rang out from the sea down below, and the calm surface of the sea suddenly began to churn violently as enormous waves swept forth in all directions, clashing against one another to cause a deafening commotion.

Additionally, the surrounding space had also begun trembling slightly, and Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this.

What's going on?

This earthquake-like disturbance felt like an eruption of energy that had been accumulating for a long time, and it was certainly not a commonplace occurrence in the Black Wind Sea.

Han Li looked down at the sea for a while longer before withdrawing his gaze and continuing onward.

……

In a region of the sea near Black Wind Island, the area was littered with coral, upon which grew a type of crimson seaweed. Looking down from above, it was as if this area were a massive go board that was riddled with countless crimson go stones.

This area had been named the Go Board Sea, and it was millions of kilometers away from Black Wind Island. On top of that, it deviated away from all of the main waterways, so it was also a very sparsely populated area.

The world's origin qi here was quite rich, and there was also an abundance of ore resources on the seabed. On top of that, there were many demon beasts residing in the area, several species of which possessed very precious demon cores and materials, so there were many cultivators who frequently visited the area on hunting trips.

There were similar places all over the Black Wind Sea, so this wasn't a rare sight.

After all, in the context of the entirety of the vast Black Wind Sea, the islands that were inhabited by cultivators only made up a tiny area, while the rest of the region was still predominantly inhabited by demon beasts.

While it was a common occurrence for cultivators to hunt for demon beasts, it was also not uncommon to see cultivators being slain and devoured upon encountering demon beasts too formidable for them to handle.

At this moment, there were several human cultivators on the Go Board Sea that were at risk of suffering this exact grisly fate.

It was a group of three cultivators consisting of a middle-aged man with a coarse beard, a red-robed young woman, and a black-robed young man controlling an azure flying boat treasure that was racing through the air.

They were being pursued by a ball of blue light, and it was unclear what type of demon beast the ball of light contained, but there were arcs of blue lightning flashing over its surface.

All three cultivators were at the Deity Transformation Stage, and the azure flying boat was riddled with complex spirit patterns while moving at a decent speed, indicating that it was an outstanding treasure.

However, the ball of blue light was slightly faster than the azure flying boat, and it was gaining on the three human cultivators with each passing second. Before long, the distance between them had been reduced to less than 10 kilometers.

"We won't be able to get away at this rate!" the man with the coarse beard said in an urgent voice.

"What do we do then? This is already as fast as the flying boat can go!" the red-robed young woman said in a panicked voice.

There was also an urgent look on the black-robed young man's face, but he appeared relatively calm and collected in contrast with his two companions.

"Fellow Daoist Mu, I recall that you possess a True Lightning Talisman. Use that to attack this LIghtning Worm Beast and I'll simultaneously unleash my Extreme Yin Dome to trap it. Perhaps that'll buy us enough time to get away," the man with the coarse beard urged.

"That won't work," the red-robed young woman immediately said with a shake of her head. "Your Extreme Yin Dome is a yin-attribute treasure that's completely suppressed by this Lightning Worm Beast's lightning power, so you won't be able to buy much time at all."

"I know, but we have no other alternatives right now. The longer we manage to keep that thing at bay, the greater our chances of survival will become. If we let that thing catch up to us, we'll be torn to shreds in an instant! Hurry, Fellow Daoist Mu!" the man with the coarse beard urged.

The black-robed young man gritted his teeth as he flipped a hand over to produce a purple talisman.

There were arcs of purple lightning flashing over the talismans, and even though it hadn't been activated yet, the black-robed young man's two companions were already shuddering in the face of its power.

The black-robed young man swept a hand through the air, and the purple talisman immediately shot forth as a bolt of purple lightning that hurtled directly toward the ball of blue light.

A burst of thunderous rumbling rang out as the purple talisman exploded into around a dozen bolts of purple lightning, all of which were as thick as water vats, and they were converging toward the ball of blue light with astonishing power.

The ball of blue light instantly fell away to reveal the demon beast inside, and it was a blue demon beast that was over 100 feet in length and resembled a giant python.

However, there wasn't a single scale on its body. Instead, its body was split up into numerous segments, giving it the appearance of an enormous blue worm.

After shattering the ball of blue light, the thick bolts of lightning struck the Lightning Worm Beast's body with tremendous force, causing it to let loose a sharp screeching sound akin to the crying of an infant.

A series of wounds were inflicted onto its body, and blue blood came pouring out from within, but the wounds weren't very deep at all and were only minor injuries.

However, the Lightning Worm Beast was infuriated by the attack, and a series of thick bolts of blue lightning instantly emerged over its body to keep the bolts of purple lightning at bay.

Right at this moment, a huge black dome-shaped net appeared in the sky above the Lightning Worm Beast, then descended upon it.

The net was glittering and translucent in appearance with wisps of black flames on its surface, but it was giving off an extremely cold and forbidding aura.

The net descended upon the Lightning Worm Beast before tightening forcefully to bind the beast, and a series of black gashes instantly appeared all over its body.

Plumes of smoke rose up out of the gashes, and the Lightning Worm Beast's screeching instantly became even more shrill and high-pitched as it stopped in its tracks.

"We have to go! Hurry!" the man with the coarse beard yelled.

The red-robed young woman hurriedly made a hand seal while opening her mouth to release a ball of crimson light, which vanished into the azure flying boat.

All of the spirit patterns on the flying boat lit up in unison, releasing bursts of azure light as it shot forward through the air at an incredible speed.

Meanwhile, the Lightning Worm Beast was thrashing around violently inside the black net.

At the same time, a gash appeared on the front of its body, then opened up to reveal a terrifying mouth, inside of which were two rows of sharp white fangs.

Immediately thereafter, all of the blue lightning all over the Lightning Worm Beast's body converged toward its mouth, forming an enormous ball of blue lightning in the blink of an eye before being blasted forward with tremendous force.

A string of earth-shattering explosions rang out as blue lightning erupted in all directions, instantly tearing the black net apart.

The man with the coarse beard let loose an involuntary groan, and blood began to trickle down from the corner of his lips as his complexion turned as pale as a sheet.

"Uncle!" the red-robed young woman exclaimed in a concerned voice.

"I'm fine, don't worry about me! Hurry, we need to get out of here!" the man with the coarse beard yelled.

Chapter 385: Chance Encounter

The red-robed young woman gritted her teeth as she shifted her gaze away from the man with the coarse beard, and she began making a rapid string of hand seals to further accelerate the flying boat.

Meanwhile, the black-robed young man beside her swept a sleeve through the air, sending a burst of gentle azure light flying into the body of the bearded man.

The bearded man's complexion instantly improved slightly, and he gave the black-robed young man a grateful nod.

Right at this moment, the vast expanse of blue lightning faded to reveal the Lightning Worm Beast once again.

The injuries on its body seemed to have worsened a little, and many parts of its body were charred black and stained with blue blood.

However, it then let loose a loud roar, and arcs of blue lightning reappeared over its body.

At the same time, all of the blue blood on its body was set alight, transforming into a burst of blue flames.

The flames and lightning intertwined to form a vast expanse of dense blue mist that surged around the beast's giant body, and in the next instant, the blue mist abruptly exploded before vanishing into thin air along with the Lightning Worm Beast itself.

The black-robed young man had been paying close attention to the Lightning Worm Beast this entire time, and his expression instantly changed drastically upon seeing this. "Be careful!"

The red-robed young woman and the bearded man had also been keeping tabs on the beast with their spiritual sense, and they were quite alarmed by its sudden disappearance as well.

Before the three of them had a chance to do anything, a burst of spatial fluctuations suddenly emerged in front of the flying boat, following which a vast expanse of blue mist appeared, then swooped down upon the flying boat, instantly inundating the trio onboard.

As soon as the flying boat fell into the sea of blue mist, it was immediately stopped cold in its tracks as if it had flown into a swamp.

The three cultivators onboard also felt a tremendous burst of invisible force constricting around them, and they weren't completely immobilized, but much to their alarm, their movements were severely restricted.

Immediately thereafter, the giant Lightning Worm Beast appeared in front of them, and its body had swelled even further, resembling a small mountain.

At the same time, it was giving off an immense Spatial Tempering Stage aura.

A hint of despair appeared in the eyes of both the red-robed young woman and the bearded, and a grim look had also appeared on the black-robed young man's face.

The Lightning Worm Beast opened its cavernous mouth, releasing around a dozen thick bolts of blue lightning that surged toward the flying boat at an astonishing speed.

At the same time, the surrounding sea of blue mist churned violently as it enveloped the trio of cultivators onboard.

The sea of blue mist then transformed into an enormous ball of mist that churned and swirled with tremendous force while arcs of lightning flashed within it, and it was unclear what was happening inside.

Right at this moment, the ball of blue mist abruptly fell still, then bulged outward before exploding with a resounding boom to reveal the trio of cultivators inside.

At this moment, the black-robed young man was holding a giant fiery crimson sword that was several dozen feet in length. The sword was burning with scorching crimson flames and giving off terrifying spiritual power fluctuations.

His face had turned as pale as a sheet, while his clothes were in tatters, and blood was trickling down from the corners of his lips.

The bearded man and the red-robed young woman were in even worse condition. Both of them had had their clothes torn to shreds, while their faces had turned deathly pale. In particular, the bearded man's body was soaked in blood, and his left arm had been severed at the elbow.

The azure flying boat was nowhere to be seen, and the wreckage of a spirit boat could just barely be made out within the sea of mist behind the trio.

The flames on the surface of the giant fiery sword that the black-robed young man was wielding flashed momentarily before rapidly shrinking down, transforming into a crimson spirit talisman that was around half a foot in size with a fiery sword design emblazoned on its surface.

The talisman was giving off formidable fier-attribute spiritual power fluctuations, but they were extremely unstable.

All of a sudden, the talisman burst into flames and was incinerated into ashes in the blink of an eye.

A pained look appeared in the black-robed young man's eyes upon seeing this, but there was no time to grieve over the talisman as he yelled, "Run!"

Immediately thereafter, he flew away into the distance as a streak of azure light, and the bearded man and the red-robed young woman also mustered what little remained of their strength as they flew away as quickly as they could.

However, they weren't able to make it very far before the Lightning Worm Beast re-emerged from the blue mist behind them.

A long gash had appeared on its lower abdomen, and the wound was bleeding profusely. It was not an injury to be scoffed at, but over all, the beast was in far better condition than the trio of human cultivators.

Even though its prey was getting away, the Lightning Worm Beast didn't appear to be worried at all, and a hint of mockery appeared in its eyes.

All of a sudden, the surrounding blue mist enveloped its entire body, and it set off in pursuit of the trio of the cultivators at an incredible speed.

All three of the human cultivators were carrying severe injuries, so they were flying far slower than before, but the speed of the Lightning Worm Beast hadn't diminished in the slightest, and the distance between them quickly began to shrink.

The trio of cultivators were extremely anxious, but there was nothing that they could do.

Before long, the gap between them had already been closed down to less than five kilometers.

At this point, their magic power reserves were close to running dry, and none of them had any more powerful treasures up their sleeves, so the situation was looking very dire.

Right at this moment, a streak of azure light suddenly appeared on the distant horizon out of nowhere, and it was approaching them at a rapid speed.

The enormous aura emanating out of the streak of azure light far exceeded that of the trio of cultivators and the Lightning Worm Beast behind them.

The despair on the faces of the three cultivators instantly turned to hope and elation, and the three of them yelled out in unison, "Save us, Senior!"

The streak of azure light slowed down slightly, and the trio of cultivators were ecstatic to see this.

A hint of fear flashed through the Lightning Worm Beast's eyes at the sight of the streak of azure light, but as it turned its gaze back to its prey, the fear in its eyes was instantly replaced by a vicious gleam.

All of a sudden, it stopped cold in its tracks before opening its mouth, and countless arcs of blue lightning appeared within the sea of mist before converging rapidly toward its mouth, forming a giant ball of lightning that was several hundred feet in size in the blink of an eye.

The ball of lightning then shot forth toward the trio of cultivators, while the Lightning Worm Beast turned and fled toward the distance with the sea of blue mist surging around it.

The ball of lightning was extremely fast, and it looked as if it were about to swallow up the trio of cultivators in the blink of an eye.

A cold harrumph rang out from within the streak of azure light, immediately following which a pillar of azure light that was as thick as a bucket descended out of the heavens to strike the ball of lightning.

The pillar of azure light pierced through the ball of lightning with ease, and the Lightning Worm Beast was terrified to see this.

The sea of mist around it churned violently as it fled into the distance at even faster speed, only for another pillar of azure light to shoot out of the streak of azure light.

The pillar of azure light was far faster than the Lightning Worm Beast, catching up to it in a flash before transforming into a giant streak of azure sword qi that was several thousand feet in length.

The sea of blue mist was instantly torn apart to reveal the Lightning Worm Beast inside.

The beast had stopped cold in its tracks, and a gash was running all the way down its body.

In the next instant, its enormous body split up into two halves, and a vast expanse of blue blood interspersed with internal organs rained down onto the sea below.

The trio of cultivators had all stopped in their tracks and were observing the unfolding situation with awestruck expressions.

Only then did the streak of azure light in the air fade to reveal a square-faced middle-aged man.

The trio of cultivators exchanged a glance with one another, then hurriedly flew toward the middle-aged man before extending deep, respectful bows. "Thank you for saving our lives, Senior!"

The fact that he was able to slay the Lightning Worm Beast so easily indicated that he was at least a Body Integration cultivator, and he could even be a Grand Ascension cultivator, so they had to treat him with the utmost respect.

The middle-aged man took a glance at the trio, and his gaze lingered momentarily on the black-robed young man as he asked, "Are you all cultivators of Black Wind Island?"

"That's right. We reside on Black Wind Island, and I grew up in Black Wind City, so I'm very familiar with everything there. If you need anything, I'd be happy to be of service, Senior," the black-robed young man immediately replied.

"You sound like a guide," the middle-aged man remarked with a faint smile.

"Truth be told, I did work as a guide for some time in the past," the black-robed young man replied with a slightly embarrassed smile.

"What's your name?" the middle-aged man asked.

"My name is Mu Xue. These two are Fang Xi and Fang Wei," the black-robed young man replied in a respectful manner.

The middle-aged man raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and he didn't say anything in response.

The man was none other than Han Li, who had finally arrived near Black Wind Island after around a month of travel.

He was certainly not expecting to meet Mu Xue here, and if it weren't for the fact that they were acquaintances, he wouldn't have stopped to save them. After all, it was very common for cultivators to perish during battles against demon beasts.

Back when they parted ways, Mu Xue had only been at the Core Formation Stage, yet he was had since reached the Deity Transformation Stage, and even though he had benefited from the spirit stones and cultivation arts bestowed upon him by Han Li, this was still quite an impressive rate of improvement.

Mu Xue naturally hadn't identified him, and he had no intention of revealing his identity to Mu Xue, either.

Mu Xue's trio was rather puzzled by Han Li's silence, but they didn't dare to interrupt him, so they could only stand together in silence.

"This place is not very safe. I just so happen to be on my way to Black Wind City, so I'll take you there," Han Li said.

He patted his storage pouch as he spoke, and a ball of azure light flew out from within, forming an intricate palm-sized spirit boat that resembled an azure bird.

The flying boat then rapidly swelled to over 100 feet in length, and four furry azure wings appeared on either side of the boat amid a flash of azure light. They resembled the wings of a fledgling, and they were flapping rapidly to keep the flying boat aloft.

"Wow, it's so adorable!" the red-robed young woman couldn't help but exclaim.

The bearded man was currently attending to his own injuries, and he immediately turned to the young woman with a warning glare upon hearing this.

The red-robed young woman immediately realized her mistake. It would've been appropriate for her to praise this senior's flying boat as profound, but calling it adorable was not very appropriate at all, and she hurriedly lowered her head as a faint blush appeared on her face.

"It's alright. Come onboard," Han Li said with a warm smile.

Mu Xue and the red-robed young woman immediately obliged, flying onto the boat, while the bearded man took a hesitant glance at Han Li, then looked back at the demon beast carcass down below as he said, "Please pardon me for my rudeness, Senior, but this Lightning Worm Beast carcass..."

"It's fine. I have no use for this carcass, so if you want it, then you can have it," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

Chapter 386: Warning Signs

"Thank you, Senior!"

The bearded man was ecstatic, and he extended a respectful salute toward Han Li, then flew down before dismembering the Lightning Worm Beast's carcass in a well-rehearsed fashion.

He didn't dare to delay for too long, so he only harvested several important materials before flying back.

Han Li made a hand seal, and he was just about to spur the flying boat into action when the surrounding sea suddenly began to tremble.

He cast his gaze downward to discover massive waves sweeping over the nearby sea amid bursts of loud rumbling.

At the same time, dense smoke began to rise up from an uninhabited island hundreds of kilometers away, and a thick pillar of crimson magma erupted into the heavens.

Mu Xue's trio were quite alarmed to see this, but Han Li remained calm and collected, so they didn't dare to say anything.

Despite Han Li's lack of reaction, he was feeling rather intrigued.

On the way to Black Wind Island, he had run into disasters like tsunamis and earthquakes quite frequently. Such disasters had taken place in the Black Wind Sea in the past as well, but definitely not this frequently.

After observing the situation for a while, he withdrew his gaze before making a hand seal, and the flying boat began to radiate dazzling azure light, while the wings on either side of it swelled to several times their original size.

Immediately thereafter, the flying boat shot forth as a streak of azure light at an incredible speed, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

"Do you know what the situation on Black Wind Island is like at the moment? Is the conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island still ongoing?" Han Li asked in a casual manner.

"Ever since these natural disasters began taking place all over the Black Wind Sea, a temporary truce was called between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island," Mu Xue replied.

"Are you referring to disasters like this tsunami?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's correct," Mu Xue replied with a nod.

Han Li nodded with a contemplative expression upon hearing this, but he didn't say anything, and Mu Xue's trio didn't dare to speak without being spoken to, so the four of them traveled in silence.

It didn't take long for them to reach Black Wind City, and they stopped somewhere outside the city.

"Thank you for saving our lives, Senior. May we have the honor of knowing your name? We'll be sure to remember it for as long as we live," Mu Xue said in a grateful manner on behalf of the trio as they disembarked from the flying boat.

"There's no need for that, I just so happened to be passing by, so I didn't have to go out of my way to save you. Cultivation is important, but always remember that you only have one life," Han Li said.

After that, he didn't wait for the trio to say anything before flying toward Black Wind City.

The three of them watched as Han Li departed, and after he had disappeared out of sight, the bearded man turned to Mu Xue as he said, "Fellow Daoist Mu, it was all thanks to those two talismans of yours that we were able to survive until that senior came to save us, so rest assured, we'll split the spirit stones from selling the Lightning Worm Beast's materials evenly among the three of us."

Mu Xue nodded in response, then cast his gaze in the direction that Han Li had departed in with a contemplative look in his eyes.

"What is it, Fellow Daoist Mu?" the red-robed young woman asked.

"It's nothing. Let's go," Mu Xue replied with a smile, then began flying toward the city.

At the same time, he was thinking to himself that the senior from earlier struck him with a sense of familiarity.

However, he was unable to recall where he had met this senior before.

The protective array of Black Wind City had already been activated, and Han Li was quickly granted entry into the city after submitting an entrance fee.

He didn't linger on the outskirts of the city, instead flying directly toward the center of the city.

He stopped on a main street in Black Wind City, at the end of which was a huge plaza where the Black Wind City teleportation pagoda was situated.

He cast his gaze toward the surrounding shops, upon which his brows furrowed slightly.

This was already the most prosperous area in Black Wind City, but there still weren't many people on the streets. Business in the shops that lined the streets was also suffering as a result, and this was very different from how the city had been during his last visit.

He thought back to what Mu Xue had told him about the frequent occurrence of natural disasters of late, and with that in mind, he made his way into a nearby shop.

The shopkeeper immediately approached Han Li with a warm smile as he said, "Welcome, esteemed customer. How can we help you today? Our shop may not be very large, but we have a huge range of wares, and you definitely won't be disappointed."

The shopkeeper was a short and portly golden-robed man, and Han Li casually purchased several rare spirit plants from the shop.

After paying for the spirit plants, he struck up a conversation with the shopkeeper.

"I've been to Black Wind City several times in the past, and on those occasions, the city had been quite prosperous. Why is it that it seems to have fallen into a recession since then?"

"It's because of all of the recent natural disasters. For some reason, there's been a great deal of unrest in the entire Black Wind Sea of late, and I've heard that many islands have been destroyed outright.

“Nowadays, all islands are beginning to go into lockdown, and even though people are still free to come and go from Black Wind Island, business has naturally suffered as a result of the current social climate," the shopkeeper replied with a resigned expression.

"Why have the natural disasters suddenly become so frequent?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"No one seems to know the reason why. There are some rumors that say this is caused by unrest in the marine spirit veins, and some have also said that an astonishingly powerful treasure is about to emerge. There are even some who speculate that this is a sign that the Black Wind Sea is about to meet its destruction, but it's impossible to say if any of these theories have any degree of truth to them," the shopkeeper replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. All of these theories sounded quite absurd.

"Setting that aside for now, do you know when the teleportation array connected to the outside world will be running next?" Han Li asked.

His primary objective for coming to Black Wind City this time was to leave the Black Wind Sea and try his luck in the outside world. After all, he had determined that it appeared implausible for him to stay in the Black Wind Sea and wait for a way to reach the Golden Immortal Stage to fall onto his lap.

"If you want to go to the outside world, then I'm afraid you're going to be disappointed. After the last time the teleportation array was used over 10 years ago, Island Master Lu Jun declared that it was going to be closed to 1,000 years," the shopkeeper replied with a shake of his head.

"1,000 years? What is the reason for this?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I don't know, but I'm sure Island Master Lu has his reasons," the shopkeeper replied with a resigned shrug.

"I see," Han Li mused as he cupped his fist in a parting salute toward the shopkeeper, then turned to make his way out of the shop.

After emerging from the shop, he walked along the street for a while before stepping into another shop.

There was no reason for the shopkeeper to lie to him, but he had to confirm that what he had been told was true.

Before long, he emerged from this shop as well with a grim expression, then made his way into another shop.

Close to an hour later, Han Li was standing on a certain street.

He had visited around a dozen shops of different sizes, and the information that he had received was identical. The teleportation array couldn't be used anytime soon, and Lu Jun had made this decision very abruptly without providing any explanation.

Han Li stood still for a moment with a dark look on his face before flying away in the direction of the island master's manor.

The island master's manor hadn't changed much compared with before, consisting of a series of black buildings that resembled a pack of giant black beasts.

All of the buildings were enshrouded within restrictions of different colors, and these restrictions were interconnected with one another.

These restrictions had become even more formidable than before, and together, they formed a giant ball of light that made it impossible to see what was inside from the outside.

The Talisman Letter Palace outside the manor was still standing, but at this moment, there were only several cultivators inside, in stark contrast with how lively and bustling it had previously been.

Han Li was standing at the entrance of the Talisman Letter Palace as he took a glance up at the island master's manor.

There didn't appear to have been anything out of the ordinary here, but Han Li could sense many pairs of eyes and bursts of spiritual sense constantly scouring the area, keeping close tabs on anyone approaching the scene.

Han Li was rather taken aback by this as he strode toward the Talisman Letter Palace.

The security here was tighter than ever, and it clearly wasn't just because of the increased frequency of natural disasters in the Black Wind Sea.

Right as he stepped into the palace, two more streaks of light approached from afar, then landed in front of the island master's manor in the blink of an eye to reveal a pair of figures.

One of them was a young woman who appeared to be around 30 years of age. She was wearing a daoist robe, but her head wasn't shaved.

She was accompanied by a white-robed man with a longsword on his back and a sharp look in his eyes.

Instead of immediately entering the manor, the white-robed man suddenly took an alert glance at his surroundings.

"What is it, Elder Lu?" the young woman asked.

"Nothing..." the man replied as he continued to sweep his gaze across the surrounding area with slightly furrowed brows.

Just now, his spiritual sense had detected that there seemed to be someone observing him from the shadows.

However, this feeling had only appeared for an instant before fading, and he couldn't be certain whether it was just a figment of his imagination.

In order to lay his suspicions to rest, he released his spiritual sense over the surrounding area, but was still unable to detect anything, and his brows furrowed even tighter.

"Let's go. Time is of the essence," the young woman urged in a low voice.

The man nodded in response, and the two of them made their way into the island master's manor together, encountering no resistance from the guards at the entrance.

Only after a long while did Han Li emerge from the Talisman Letter Palace before departing without even taking a glance at the island master's manor.

He appeared quite calm and collected on the outside, but he was reeling internally.

He didn't recognize that woman, but that white-robed man was familiar to him. It was one of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace's Golden Immortals, Lu Yue.

Why is he here in the Black Wind Sea? Could it have something to do with me?

As soon as this thought occurred to him, his heart immediately sprang up into his throat. He continued to walk away in an unhurried manner, but his spiritual sense was focused firmly on the island master's manor behind him the entire time.

At the same time, he was discreetly channeling his immortal spiritual power, ready to unleash an all-out attack at the first sign of any disturbance.

Only after he was several dozen kilometers away from the island master's manor did he feel slightly more reassured, but he still didn't dare to let down his guard as he picked up the pace and continued onward into the distance.

Two hours later, a streak of azure light flew out of Black Wind City before hurtling toward the distant sea.

After flying for tens of thousands of kilometers, arcs of golden lightning abruptly emerged from the streak of azure light before forming a lightning array with countless golden runes flashing within it.

Before long, Han Li had vanished out of thin air alongside the lightning array.

Chapter 387: Chaotic State of Affairs

Millions of kilometers away, a rumbling thunderclap suddenly rang out in the sky above the sea, immediately following which arcs of golden lightning sprang forth before intertwining to form a profound lightning array.

The golden array then faded in a flash to reveal Han Li, and as soon as he appeared, he immediately released his spiritual sense throughout the surrounding area.

Only after confirming that there was no one else within a radius of thousands of kilometers did he finally feel a little safer, and he cast his gaze in the direction of Black Wind Island with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Lu Yue had to have come to the Black Wind Sea for a reason, but it most likely wasn't to hunt for him. Even though he was a wanted fugitive of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, he was still only a True Immortal cultivator, so it would've surely been considered overkill to send a Golden Immortal after him.

Even so, he still didn't dare to drop his guard. He was confident that he would be able to at least ensure self-preservation in the face of a Golden Immortal, but it would still be quite troublesome for him if Lu Yue were to find out that he was in the Black Wind Sea.

On top of that, the fact that Lu Yue was able to enter the island master's manor so easily indicated that he had some ties with Black Wind Island.

With that in mind, Han Li thought back to the strange group of people that he had encountered back when he first returned to the Black Wind Sea. Those people seemed to have had close ties with Black Wind Island as well.

Could it be that they were also cultivators of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace?

With that in mind, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a black array plate, then cast an incantation seal into it, and the array plate immediately began to release balls of black light that came together to form a voice transmission array.

After that, Han Li sent out a voice transmission message through the array, but even after waiting for a full 15 minutes, the array was still displaying no reaction.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

This array plate had been given to him by Wyrm 3 prior to his departure from the secret area, and he was planning to ask Wyrm 3 about the current state of affairs in the Black Wind Sea, but he wasn't receiving any response.

Han Li shook his head as he stowed the array plate away, then cast a contemplative gaze toward the sea down below.

At the moment, the Black Wind Sea resembled the sea beneath him. It appeared calm and placid on the surface, and even the conflict between Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island had temporarily subsided, but there were undercurrents churning beneath the surface.

First, there was the Reincarnation Palace. This mysterious power that was a sworn enemy of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace had suddenly appeared in the Black Wind Sea for some reason, and he had essentially been coerced to join them and refine that strange pill for an unknown purpose. Now, cultivators from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace had also appeared here,

Given the chaotic nature of the situation, it simply didn't make sense for him to stay here, and he should leave this place as soon as possible.

However, the teleportation array leading to the outside world was inaccessible, so the only way out was through the Soul Stirring Winds, and he was confident that he would be able to complete the journey with the help of the Wind Shelter Bead.

He was quite curious about what was deep inside the Soul Stirring Winds to begin with, so this was a good opportunity for him to satisfy his curiosity.

With that in mind, Han Li was just about to fly away as a streak of azure light when he suddenly stopped in his tracks before turning toward a certain direction.

After a brief hesitation, he flew in that direction instead.

Meanwhile, in a dimly-lit hall in the island master's manor in Black Wind City.

The hall was only around 40 to 50 feet wide, but it was 200 to 300 feet deep, and there were two rows of wooden shelves on either side of the hall. The shelves were laden with lit candles that were giving off a peculiar aroma, but they weren't shedding much light on the hall.

At the end of the hall was a three-tiered platform, atop which sat none other than Xiao Jinhan.

His eyes were tightly shut, and he seemed to have been cultivating with wisps of black mist rising up from his body to encompass an area in a radius of roughly 30 feet around him.

There was a peculiar, suffocating aura that enshrouded the entire hall, as if an invisible beast were prowling the hall, and standing at the foot of the platform were Lu Yue and the young woman in the daoist robe.

The two of them had faint sheens of sweat glistening on their foreheads, and both of them remained completely silent.

A long while later, Xiao Jinhan opened his eyes, and the surrounding black mist instantly vanished into his body, while the peculiar atmosphere in the hall also faded.

Lu Yue and the young woman's expressions eased slightly upon sensing this, while Xiao Jinhan asked, "How did it go?"

"Rest assured, Palace Master, everything has been arranged according to your instructions. The Distant Displacement Array has also been reinforced, so there's no way that the people of the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect will be able to detect the location of the entrance," Lu Yue replied in a respectful voice.

"Our main enemy is the Reincarnation Palace," Xiao Jinhan said as his eyes narrowed slightly.

Lu Yue immediately felt a tremendous burst of pressure weighing down upon him, and his complexion paled slightly as he hurriedly replied, "Yes, Palace Master. Right now, the people of the Reincarnation Palace definitely won't be able to find the entrance, either."

Xiao Jinhan gave a slight nod upon hearing this, and he said in an authoritative voice, "This is a very important matter, so you must make sure that nothing goes wrong!"

"Rest assured, Palace Master!" Lu Yue immediately replied.

Xiao Jinhan's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he gave a dismissive wave.

Lu Yue and the young woman extended a parting salute, and only after they were far away from the hall did they heave a collective sigh of relief.

"The palace master's powers are becoming more and more unfathomable. As long as this mission is a success, he shouldn't be far away from reaching the High Zenith Stage," the young woman said.

"It's exactly because of this that failure is not an option," Lu Yue replied.

"I'm well aware of that," the young woman replied with a nod, and the two of them quickly faded into the distance.

Meanwhile, Lu Jun and Lu Yuqing were standing beside a window of a distant pavilion.

"Father, the Immortal Palace..."

Lu Jun hurriedly glared at Lu Yuqing to cut her off, then closed the window before turning and making his way deeper into the pavilion.

Lu Yuqing stuck out her tongue with a slightly disgruntled expression before trailing along behind him.

Lu Jun stopped in a room deep within the pavilion, then swept his sleeves through the air to release a series of incantation seals.

Seven or eight restrictions instantly appeared in the room in quick succession, following which Lu Jun thrust his palm into a nearby wall, and a secret opening appeared on the wall.

The two of them made their way inside, and the secret opening immediately closed itself.

Beyond the secret opening was a small room with walls that were constructed from a type of black crystal that was giving off a layer of faint black light.

As soon as they entered this room, it was as if they had entered a separate space that was completely isolated from the outside world.

"How many times do I have to tell you, Qing'er? There's no telling how formidable the spiritual sense of those people are, so we have to exercise the utmost caution in everything that we say and do. This is perhaps the only safe place in the entire manor," Lu Jun said in a stern voice.

"I understand, Father," Lu Yuqing replied with a nod.

Only then did Lu Jun's expression ease slightly as he patted Lu Yuqing on the shoulder in a doting fashion, then sat down beside a table in the room.

"Father, we've been constantly working for the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace. Even if we set aside everything else, just the conflict against Azure Feather Island alone has resulted in close to half of our 36 subsidiary islands falling into ruin. Now that the immortal manor is about to emerge, can they really not spare us even a single spot?" Lu Yuqing asked with a slightly indignant expression.

A wry smile appeared on Lu Jun's face as he sighed, "The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace is too far above us for us to question its decisions."

The indignation on Lu Yuqing's face became even more pronounced upon hearing this.

"We can't ask for too much. All we can hope for now is that after all of this is over, the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace will abide by its promise not to meddle in the affairs of our Black Wind Sea any longer," Lu Jun sighed.

……

Half a month later.

A flurry of golden lightning emerged in the sky tens of thousands of kilometers away from Dark Veil Island, following which Han Li appeared.

He took a brief glance at his surroundings before flying toward Dark Veil Island, and upon arriving near the island, he was quite relieved to find that it appeared untouched by the frequent natural disasters.

The entire island was still in a state of lockdown, and all of the restrictions were still activated.

Han Li pulled out a storage bracelet, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that enveloped the storage bracelet, following which it vanished in a flash.

Inside a secret chamber on Dark Veil Island, Luo Feng was seated with his legs crossed, and his body was enshrouded within a cloud of mist.

He seemed to have been cultivating some type of secret technique, and right at this moment, a ball of azure light containing a storage bracelet appeared in front of him without any warning.

The azure light faded, and the bracelet fell onto the ground.

The mist around Luo Feng immediately receded as he opened his eyes, and he faltered slightly at the sight of the storage bracelet on the ground, immediately following which Han Li's voice rang out beside his ears.

"The island is to remain in lockdown for the next century."

Luo Feng hurriedly rose to his feet, then cupped his fist in a respectful salute as he said, "Yes, Ancestral God Liu Shi!"

That was the only instruction issued to him, and Luo Feng waited for a moment before picking up the storage bracelet from the ground.

He then injected his spiritual sense into it, and an elated look immediately appeared on his face.

The storage bracelet contained a large batch of spirit stones and materials that was sufficient to support the island's operation for several centuries.

Meanwhile, Han Li had arrived at the place where his Earthly Deity Avatar was cultivating.

Checking on the state of the island was only the secondary objective for his visit, while his primary objective was to take the heavy water that his Earthly Deity Avatar had refined over the past years.

At this moment, Han Li was hovering in mid-air, looking down at the massive rumbling vortex on the surface of the sea down below with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

The vortex was several hundred kilometers in size, and it was raising enormous waves that were over 1,000 feet tall in all directions.

The vortex had never been this formidable before, and a thought suddenly occurred to Han Li as he swooped straight down into it.

On a platform on the seabed, the Earthly Deity Avatar was seated with dazzling blue light radiating from its entire body, forming a giant ball of blue light that was several hundred feet in size around it.

Additionally, there was also a thread of blue light hovering above its head, and it had become roughly twice as thick as before with countless blue runes dancing around it.

An enormous aura was emanating from its body, indicating that it had already reached the late-True Immortal Stage.

Han Li was very pleased to see this, but not overly surprised.

This avatar had already previously reached the pinnacle of the mid-True Immortal Stage, and even though he had been quite busy with his own cultivation, he still occasionally manifested some time crystals to send to the Earthly Deity Avatar. With a sufficient supply of time crystals, it was never going to be that difficult for it to make a breakthrough.

After all, in just the span of a few centuries, it had already managed to derive as much heavy water as the average cultivator would've done in several million years.

All of a sudden, the blue light around the Earthly Deity Avatar's rippled before quickly vanishing into its body, following which it rose to its feet before casting its gaze toward Han Li.

"Give me all of your heavy water," Han Li instructed.

The Earthly Deity Avatar flipped its hands over to produce a pair of Heavenly Water Pouches, then offered them to Han Li.

Han Li inspected the contents of the two pouches with his spiritual sense, and his eyes immediately lit up.

One of the pouches was already full, while the other one was also close to halfway filled. It seemed that with the increase in its cultivation base, the Earthly Deity Avatar's rate of heavy water derivation had also improved significantly.

He made a hand seal, and a layer of starlight appeared over his body as he reached out to grab the two pouches.

Even though he was already prepared this time, his arms still sank down slightly upon receiving the pair of pouches, and only as all of his 18 profound acupoints lit up was he able to bear the collective weight of the two pouches with ease.

A pleased look appeared on his face upon seeing this.

These two pouches of heavy water, in addition to the one from before, were already enough for him to use in battle.

He stowed the pair of Heavenly Water Pouches away, then flipped a hand over to produce three empty ones before handing them to the Earthly Deity Avatar. He then instructed it to continue producing more heavy water before promptly departing.

After flying for some time, Han Li arrived in a deserted area before unleashing his lightning teleportation array.

He had also already packed up the Lightning Restraining Wood teleportation array on the way back to Dark Veil Island.

Close to a month later, a streak of azure light shot forth from afar on the outskirts of the Black Wind Sea, then faded to reveal Han Li.

Up ahead were the Soul Stirring Winds that spread as far and wide as the eyes could see.

Han Li took a glance at the boundless Soul Stirring Winds, then flipped a hand over to produce his Wind Shelter Bead before flying directly forward.

The surrounding Soul Stirring Winds instantly converged toward him, but they weren't able to have much of an impact on him thanks to the Wind Shelter Bead.

After taking a moment to acclimate himself to the environment, Han Li began to gradually accelerate in his flight.

Due to the fact that the world's origin qi was obstructed here, his immortal spiritual power recovery was severely inhibited, but prior to coming here, he had already spent quite a large sum of Immortal Origin Stones to purchase a batch of recovery pills from the Transient Guild.

Time slowly passed by, and in the blink of an eye, Han Li had already been flying through the Soul Stirring Winds for four or five days.

The Soul Stirring Winds here were already far more formidable than the ones around the secret area of the Reincarnation Palace.

Instead of their previous scattered state, the Soul Stirring Winds here had gathered together to form huge pillars of black wind that were hundreds, even thousands of feet tall, resembling countless giant black tornadoes wreaking havoc over the landscape.

The tremendous force being released by these giant pillars of wind were severely diminished by the Wind Shelter Bead, but it was still extremely formidable, comparable to an all-out attack from a Grand Ascension cultivator.

At this moment, Han Li had already conjured up his True Extreme Film, which was keeping the formidable power being released by the pillars of black wind at bay with ease.

While the power of the Soul Stirring Winds posed no threat to him, the ghastly sounds ringing out from within them had become more than 10 times as formidable as compared when he first entered the Soul Stirring Winds, and even though these sounds were also being buffered by the Wind Shelter Bead, they were still a huge pain to deal with.

As a result, Han Li had no choice but to slow down while using his Spirit Refinement Technique to ward off the effects of those horrific sounds.

At this moment, he was flying through the boundless Soul Stirring Winds at a rapid speed like a tiny raft.

Chapter 388: Venturing Deep Into the Soul Stirring Winds

Time slowly passed by, and several days later, all of the surrounding Soul Stirring Winds had already formed massive black tornados that resembled enormous pillars connecting heaven and earth.

These pillars of wind were constantly moving, occasionally overlapping with one another before separating again, and it was impossible to see anything through the suffocating darkness.

Han Li flew through the giant pillars of wind with his body encompassed within the black barrier released by the Wind Shelter Bead, and he was doing his best not to come into direct contact with these pillars of wind while also protecting his own consciousness as much as possible.

He could clearly sense the formidable glacial aura emanating from these pillars of wind, something that he certainly didn't want to be directly exposed to.

He was still advancing onward, but at a far slower rate than before.

The ghastly sounds here had become significantly louder once again, and he was still able to withstand it, but he didn't dare to release his spiritual sense out of his body anymore.

One's spiritual sense was an extension of one's soul, so if he were to release his spiritual sense to come into contact with the surrounding Soul Stirring Winds, then the effects of the ghastly sounds ringing out from within them would be exacerbated.

Thankfully, he still had his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, which allowed him to see the movement of the pillars of Soul Stirring Winds around him even without the use of his spiritual sense. Otherwise, it would've been extremely difficult to make any meaningful progress.

All of a sudden, a giant pillar of wind surged toward Han Li at an astonishing speed, but he was able to evade it by twisting to the side like an agile fish.

However, right at this moment, a black shadow shot out of the pillar of wind like a bolt of black lightning.

Thankfully, Han Li was able to react in a timely fashion, sweeping his joined index and middle fingers through the air to release a streak of azure sword qi that struck the black shadow with unerring accuracy.

A dull thump rang out as the black shadow was sliced into two, and the black qi on its surface dissipated to reveal an inky-black snake inside.

The snake was around 10 feet in length with three horns on its head along with a pair of dark red eyes, and it was giving off an extremely forbidding glacial aura.

Even after being sliced into two, it didn't perish. Instead, it was able to instantly fuse its body back together, and it was as if it hadn't been wounded at all, but the glacial aura that it was giving off had diminished significantly.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and instead of fleeing the scene, the black snake hissed at Han Li in a menacing fashion, indicating that it wasn't a very intelligent creature.

All of a sudden, it shot forth as a blurry shadow, vanishing without a trace before reappearing behind Han Li and pouncing viciously at his back.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he reached out with one hand, conjuring up a large azure palm projection that caught the black snake in a flash.

The black snake writhed and struggled with all its might, but was unable to break free.

The large azure hand brought the snake closer to Han Li, and began to inspect it with slightly furrowed brows.

This snake seemed to have been formed by the yin qi here, and unlike normal demon beasts, it had no physical body.

In order to prepare for this trip, Han Li had read many scriptures related to Soul Stirring Winds, and one of them had mentioned that there were some yin beasts residing deep within the Soul Stirring Winds that were very difficult to deal with.

This snake was undoubtedly one such yin beast.

Han Li made a clenching motion with his hand, and the large azure hand immediately constricted around the black snake, crushing it into a cloud of black qi.

However, instead of dissipating, the black qi began to writhe like a living creature, looking as if it were about to come together again.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly as he flicked a finger through the air, releasing a bolt of Divine Devilbane Lightning that struck the cloud of black qi in a flash.

The black qi instantly scattered as if it had met the bane of its existence, and an anguished screech rang out from within it before it completely faded away.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, and he continued onward.

It seemed that the black snake was a precursor for things to come, and Han Li was attacked by more and more yin beasts as he flew onward.

These yin beasts weren't very powerful, but their insubstantial bodies made them rather difficult to deal with.

Thankfully, Han Li's Divine Devilbane Lightning was perfect for dealing with these creatures, so he was able to dispatch them with ease.

As he continued to fly onward, a hint of surprise suddenly appeared on his face.

The number of pillars of Soul Stirring Wind around him had suddenly decreased, becoming far sparser than before, and the few pillars of wind that remained were also significantly smaller than before.

Han Li was rather taken aback by this, but he continued to fly onward, and as he did so, the number of pillars of Soul Stirring Wind continued to decrease until they disappeared altogether.

All that was left in the place of the Soul Stirring Winds was a boundless expanse of black mist. The glacial aura in the air had diminished significantly, and all of the yin beasts had also vanished without a trace.

The disappearance of the Soul Stirring Winds meant that the ghastly sounds they produced had mostly subsided as well, and it seemed that he had arrived in a peaceful area of black mist.

Have I already passed through the Soul Stirring Winds? Han Li thought to himself, but then immediately shook his head.

He had only been traveling through the Soul Stirring Winds for less than half a month, so there was no way that he had already passed through them.

He was definitely still situated within the Soul Stirring Winds, but he seemed to have arrived in a special area.

Unfortunately, he wasn't able to find many scriptures containing information on the Soul Stirring Winds, and there were no records of areas like this.

After a brief moment of hesitation, Han Li continued onward, but he had slowed down even further and was carefully observing everything around him with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

After flying for close to an entire day, there was still nothing but black mist around him. In fact, the black mist had become denser and denser, until it was also substantial in form.

At this point, his visibility was very limited even with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

Furthermore, the mist was no longer as peaceful as before. Instead, some strange high-pitched sounds had begun ringing out within it, resembling the sound of an infant's crying.

The sound wasn't very loud, and at times, it was barely audible at all, but it was even more formidable than the ghastly sounds from before.

He slowed down once again, and two beams of blue light that were each around a foot in length shot out of his eyes as he inspected his surroundings.

After advancing through the black mist for a while, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he stopped in his tracks before casting his gaze forward.

A burst of rumbling was ringing out up ahead, and the previously peaceful mist had suddenly begun to churn violently.

The sound was becoming louder and louder, while the disturbance in the surrounding mist was becoming more and more violent, until it resembled a pot of boiling water.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed, and he was considering whether to continue straight ahead or skirt around the disturbance when all of the black mist around him suddenly began to revolve in a frenzy, forming an enormous vortex.

The vortex was so massive that he wasn't even able to see it in its entirety. In fact, he wasn't even able to ascertain where its center was, and it was releasing tremendous suction force that enveloped his entire body, forcibly drawing him toward the center of the vortex.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly as the azure light radiating from his body brightened significantly, and only then was he able to stabilize himself.

At the same time, a black shadow shot out of the black mist up ahead.

It was a giant black toad-like yin beast that was around the size of a house with lumps growing all over its body, presenting a horrific sight to behold.

The black toad opened its mouth up wide to release a pillar of dense black light that hurtled directly toward Han Li, seemingly attempting to prevent him from leaving.

The pillar of black light was giving off astonishing glacial power fluctuations, and it seemed to be capable of freezing the very space in its wake.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing an azure flying sword that instantly transformed into a giant azure sword that was over 100 feet in length with arcs of golden lightning flashing over its surface.

The giant azure sword struck the pillar of black light, destroying it with ease before appearing above the toad yin beast's head and slashing down upon it.

The yin beast's body was instantly cleaved into two with Divine Devilbane Lightning spreading over the two halves of its body, causing them to explode into two clouds of black qi.

Even though Han Li had managed to slay the yin beast, it had managed to delay him a little, and the giant vortex behind him had gotten closer to him, while the suction force that it was releasing had become even more formidable.

Han Li was just about to unleash a secret technique to fly away from the area when a giant black tentacle shot out of the vortex at an incredible speed before wrapping itself around him.

However, thanks to his True Extreme Film, the tentacle wasn't actually able to make contact with his body.

His expression changed slightly upon seeing this, but he then gave a cold harrumph as he made a hand seal, and two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly flew out of his body before striking the black tentacle.

However, the tentacle was extremely resilient, and the pair of Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were only able to slice slightly into it before being brought to a halt.

A surprised look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and before he had a chance to do anything else, the black tentacle abruptly pulled back with tremendous force, catching him off guard and dragging him into the huge vortex.

In the next instant, he appeared in the eye of a rapidly revolving storm with deafening rumbling akin to the sound of countless thundering horse hooves ringing out around him.

Bursts of tremendous suction force converged toward him from all directions, while the black tentacle remained wrapped around his body.

Furthermore, it was rapidly constricting, but Han Li's True Extreme Film remained firm.

Even though Han Li had been dragged into the vortex, he remained calm and collected, paying no heed to the black tentacle around him as he inspected his surroundings with slightly furrowed brows.

Right at this moment, a low roar rang out from deep within the vortex, following which another tentacle shot out of the darkness before also wrapping itself around Han Li's body.

Han Li withdrew his gaze before peering deep into the vortex, and a cold gleam flashed through his eyes as he made a hand seal.

Chapter 389: Boundless Mist

A loud crackling sound rang out, and arcs of golden lightning suddenly appeared over the surface of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that had sliced into the black tentacle. Immediately thereafter, the pair of swords swelled to over 100 feet in size while rapidly revolving like lightning, slicing the two tentacles around Han Li into several pieces, all of which dissipated into clouds of black qi.

A slightly raspy roar of pain rang out from deep within the vortex, and Han Li took a moment to steady himself before peering deep into the vortex with blue light flashing in his eyes.

Deep inside the vortex was a huge black shadow that was currently rapidly approaching him.

Han Li made no attempt to retreat or take evasive measures upon seeing this. The suction force in the surrounding space was still acting upon him, and while the force wasn't strong enough to immobilize him, it was certainly inhibiting his movements.

He made a beckoning motion, and a flash of golden lightning appeared nearby, following which the flying sword that had just slain the toad yin beast also flew back to his side.

The three golden lightning swords were hovering around him while slowly revolving through the air.

In the next instant, a huge black shadow flew out of the vortex up ahead, revealing itself to be a massive octopus that was several hundred feet in size.

The giant beast had a pair of flashing red eyes that were the size of water vats, and they were filled with fury and resentment.

There were around a dozen tentacles dancing behind the octopus, sweeping up gusts of fierce wind. The two tentacles that had just been severed were rapidly healing at a rate that was discernible to the naked eye, and the tremendous glacial aura emanating from the beast's body was comparable to that of a late-True Immortal cultivator.

As soon as the beast revealed itself, all of its tentacles instantly intertwined to form a huge black next that swept toward Han Li.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

This yin beast was quite formidable, but it didn't seem to possess a high level of intelligence. It was solely driven by its bloodlust and acted almost entirely on instinct. Han Li had learned a couple of secret techniques that could allow him to engage in basic communication with spirit beasts, but those spirit beasts had to possess a certain level of intelligence.

He had originally planned to capture this beast and use one of those secret techniques to ask it some questions about this area, but it seemed that plan wasn't going to work.

With that in mind, he shook his head as he made a hand seal, and the three giant lightning swords arranged themselves into a triangular formation at his behest before hurtling directly toward the giant octopus yin beast.

The golden lightning on the three giant swords then reared up before intertwining to form a golden lightning net with countless thick arcs of golden lightning erupting from its surface to clash against the huge net formed by the octopus's tentacles.

A string of dull thumps rang out as black qi and golden light erupted in all directions.

As soon as the black qi on the surface of the tentacles came into contact with the Divine Devilbane Lightning, it was instanty eradicated, while the arcs of golden lightning spread over the tentacles to inflict a series of wounds.

Even though the black tentacles were inherently vulnerable to Divine Devilbane Lightning, they were formed by such dense black qi that even the Divine Devilbane Lightning was unable to eradicate them with just a single strike.

An agonized roar rang out from the octopus yin beast's mouth, and only then did a hint of fear appear in its eyes as it occurred to the beast that this was an insurmountable opponent.

It immediately swiveled around with the intention of fleeing the scene, but Han Li certainly wasn't going to allow it to get away.

A sharp gleam flashed through his eyes as he made a hand seal, and the three giant swords instantly released a barrage of golden sword projections that surged rapidly toward the octopus's tentacles.

Those tentacles had already been severely weakened, and they were instantly torn to shreds by the barrage of sword projections.

The octopus yin beast let loose another agonized roar, and it paid no heed to its own severed tentacles as it opened its mouth to release a ball of inky-black liquid.

As soon as the liquid emerged, it immediately swelled to form a giant black cloud that was around an acre in size to inundate the three giant golden swords and all of the sword projections.

The three giant swords were instantly immobilized by a burst of restrictive force within the cloud, while the severely wounded octopus yin beast fled into the distance at an incredible speed, seemingly completely unaffected by the suction force from the vortex.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as he made another hand seal, and the three golden swords instantly fused as one to form a massive sword that was around 1,000 feet in size.

Thick arcs of dazzling golden lightning then appeared over its surface, giving off an astonishingly formidable aura.

The enormous sword swiveled around slightly, then released a burst of tremendous power, and the surrounding black cloud was instantly torn apart.

Immediately thereafter, the huge sword vanished amid a flash of golden lightning, and in the next instant, it appeared directly above the octopus yin beast's head before swooping down upon it with unstoppable force.

The octopus yin beast was completely powerless to resist as its body was sliced into two, following which the two halves of its body exploded into two vast clouds of black qi.

The giant golden sword then shot back to Han Li at his behest before splitting back up into three azure flying swords that flew back up his sleeve.

However, in the next instant, a hint of blue light flashed through his eyes, and he swept a hand through the air to release a burst of azure light into the black qi.

The burst of azure light quickly returned to him, bringing with it a dark green ball.

It was a fist-sized ball enveloped within a layer of green light, and it appeared very similar to a wood-attribute spirit stone, except the glacial energy fluctuations emanating from the object were completely different from wood-attribute spiritual qi.

Could this be a demon core?

All of a sudden, he recalled the soul stones that he had gathered in the Umbra Realm back when he was still in the Mortal Realm. [1]

The aura emanating from this green bead was very similar to that of soul stones, except this bead's aura was countless times more powerful.

Han Li flipped a hand over to stow the green bead away, then began inspecting his surroundings with a contemplative look in his eyes.

This area in the Soul Stirring Wind really was rather similar to that of Stormwind Mountain in the Umbra Realm. [2] Could it be that these two places were somehow related?

Han Li only considered this matter for a moment before shaking his head and casting his gaze out of the vortex.

Right now, his top priority was to leave this vortex, so he had no time to ponder such trivial matters.

The suction force being released by the vortex was quite formidable, but it wasn't enough to inflict any substantial harm upon his body.

However, it was going to make it rather difficult for him to leave.

After a brief moment of contemplation, a burst of azure light appeared over his body alongside arcs of golden lightning, and he transformed into a streak of golden and azure light as he flew toward the mouth of the vortex.

As soon as he left the central area of the vortex, the surrounding storm instantly became more powerful.

Han Li felt the surrounding air constrict around him, following which his body was swept up involuntarily by the storm.

He gave a cold harrumph as the light radiating from his body brightened, yet instead of forcibly going against the rotational force of the storm, he went along with it while simultaneously flying outward.

Moments later, Han Li emerged from the churning black mist on the outskirts of the vortex.

His complexion was a little pale, and he continued flying until there was some distance between himself the vortex before he finally drew to a halt and heaved a sigh of relief.

The vortex had been more powerful than he imagined, and it had cost him a significant amount of immortal spiritual power to break out of it.

After taking a recovery pill, he reverted back to his true appearance as he removed his Reincarnation Palace mask.

After stowing the mask away, he continued to fly onward as a streak of azure light, and before long, he had been flying for several days once again.

There were no other hazards within this sea of black mist aside from the occasional giant vortex, and these vortexes came in a diverse range of sizes, but the vast majority of them were larger than the one that he had first encountered, with some of them even several times larger.

He could tell that the suction force that the largest ones of those vortexes was releasing was too formidable even for him to deal with, and if he were to get too close, he would most likely be sucked in and trapped inside indefinitely.

However, whenever he encountered a smaller vortex, he would slay the yin beast residing inside, and as a result, he ended up with quite a few more of those green beads.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out, and the sea of mist behind Han Li suddenly began to churn violently.

He stopped in his tracks as blue light flashed within his eyes, and immediately thereafter, he hurriedly flew away to the side.

Not long after he did so, an enormous vortex surged rapidly through the sea of mist behind him before quickly vanishing out of sight.

Han Li remained still on the spot for a moment longer before continuing onward.

During the past few days, he had gradually become more and more proficient at avoiding these vortexes.

Shortly thereafter, a strange sound suddenly rang out from within the mist up ahead, and a cold look appeared on Han Li's face as he immediately swept a sleeve through the air.

An azure flying sword shot out of his sleeve, then rapidly swelled to over 1,000 feet in size, and it was radiating dazzling azure light as it flew into the churning mist up ahead.

As soon as the giant sword flew into the mist, a resounding boom rang out, and the azure sword was sent flying back, while the azure light on its surface was thrown into a state of disarray.

A burst of tremendous force was transmitted to Han Li through the giant sword, and he shuddered as he took an involuntary step backward while sweeping his sleeve through the air once again at the same time.

Around a dozen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew out before also swelling to over 1,000 feet in size each, then plunged viciously into the mist up ahead.

Even though Han Li still hadn't yet caught a glimpse of the yin beast up ahead, he could tell that it was more formidable than any that he had previously encountered.

Streaks of azure sword qi shot out of the mist up ahead, causing it to rumble and churn violently.

Immediately thereafter, all of the giant azure swords were sent flying back with a deafening boom.

On top of that, a thick layer of black ice crystals had appeared over the blades of all of the swords, and the azure light that was emanating from them had dimmed significantly.

[1]. For more information on soul stones, please refer to RMJI Chapter 681: Soul Stone.

[Back]

[2]. For more information Stormwind Mountain, please refer to RMJI Chapter 593: Stormwind Mountain.

[Back]

Chapter 390: Ghostly Head

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he pointed a finger forward.

Arcs of golden lightning sprang out of all of the giant azure swords once again, instantly shattering the black ice crystals clinging to the swords to restore them to their former state.

However, instead of unleashing more attacks, Han Li drew to a halt as he cast his gaze forward with a grim look on his face.

Right at this moment, the vast expanse of black mist up ahead churned violently, following which a massive black shadow flew out from within.

It was traveling at an incredible speed, yet it wasn't making any sound at all, and it arrived near Han Li in the blink of an eye.

Before Han Li had a chance to react, a giant trident with black mist swirling around it emerged from the black shadow before being swung down at him with mountainous force.

Is it not a yin beast?

Han Li hurriedly made a hand seal, and the dozen or so giant azure swords around him instantly rose up into the air to form a uniform net above his head.

At the same time, a series of thick arcs of golden lightning appeared over the swords.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the trident struck the net of swords with astonishing power, almost shattering the sword net in a single blow.

Arcs of Divine Devilbane Lightning erupted out of the swords to strike the trident, scattering much of the black mist around it, but the trident itself remained completely unmoved.

Han Li let loose a low roar as he prepared to make another hand seal, but right at this moment, the trident shuddered before releasing three bursts of inky-black flames out of its three tips, and those flames instantly spread through the air to envelop the sword net while giving off a glacial aura.

Black ice crystals instantly began to appear on the giant azure swords once again, and even the arcs of golden lightning surging over the swords were frozen solid, presenting a peculiar sight to behold.

All of a sudden, the trident swiveled around with tremendous force, instantly shattering the sword net and sending the dozen or so giant azure swords flying in all directions.

The trident then pierced viciously toward Han Li as fast as lightning, and it was upon him in the blink of an eye.

A vast expanse of black flames erupted out of the trident, forming a giant black draconic head the size of a house, and it opened its mouth up wide in an attempt to swallow Han Li whole.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and it was already too late for Han Li to take evasive measures.

In this dire situation, he let loose a low roar as 18 specks of starlight appeared over his chest and abdomen, and at the same time, he thrust both fists upward with all his might.

Two starry fist projections that were several dozen feet in size erupted into the heavens to clash against the trident with another earth-shattering boom, sending violent tremors surging through the surrounding space.

Han Li's entire body shuddered, and he was sent flying back over 1,000 feet before managing to steady himself. He then turned to discover that the fiery black draconic head had faded, revealing the trident inside, which had also fallen still.

The massive black shadow controlling the trident also shuddered slightly, seemingly having been struck by some recoil from the clash.

Han Li took a deep breath to suppress the churning blood and energy in his body, and an extremely grim look had appeared on his face.

Up to this point, he still hadn't even managed to catch a clear glimpse of what the black shadow was, but its powers weren't inferior in the slightest to any of the Golden Immortals that he had encountered in the past.

At this point, he was already very deep in the Soul Stirring Winds, and even though he had encountered some perils along the way, nothing had posed a substantial threat to him. Prior to encountering this black shadow, he was even beginning to suspect that the rumors about this place were overstated.

As these thoughts were running through Han Li's mind, the black shadow began to fly toward him once again.

Han Li was already prepared for this, and a burst of azure light interspersed with arcs of golden lightning appeared over his body as he shot back like a speeding arrow.

However, he was being outsped by the black shadow, and the gap between them was rapidly shrinking.

Han Li made a hand seal, and a sharp screeching sound rang out from within his body as a series of azure flying swords emerged before converging to form a ball of azure light in front of him.

The dozen or so azure giant swords that were encased in black ice crystals also shattered the ice crystals around them once again before flying back and fusing into the ball of azure light.

In the blink of an eye, the ball of azure light transformed into an azure sword lotus flower that was around an acre in size.

At the same time, a vast expanse of black flames emerged over the black shadow, instantly transforming it into a giant ghostly head with a pair of crimson eyes, and it was certainly very menacing in appearance.

After taking on this form, the black shadow's speed was significantly enhanced, and it caught up to Han Li in just a few seconds.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he made a hand seal, and the azure sword lotus flower bloomed as it released countless giant streaks of azure sword qi with arcs of golden lightning flashing over them.

The barrage of sword qi shot into the black mist around the ghostly head, but much to Han Li's alarm, they were seemingly unable to inflict any damage upon the ghostly head at all.

The giant ghostly head abruptly swelled in size before opening its cavernous mouth to let loose a thunderous roar, sending black soundwaves sweeping through the air to encompass the entire azure sword lotus flower.

The sword lotus flower instantly began to tremble violently before being forcibly split up into 72 small azure swords that fell out of mid-air in an unstable fashion.

Han Li's body also began to tremble involuntarily within the soundwaves, and it was as if there were countless tiny daggers twisting in his internal organs.

Additionally, his soul was also shuddering uncontrollably, and he couldn't help but give a muffled groan.

These black soundwaves contained some type of strange energy, and if an ordinary late-True Immortal cultivator that wasn't a Profound Immortal was in his place, they would've most likely already been reduced to a pile of mincemeat.

The giant ghostly head let loose a low roar, and black light flashed within its mouth as the trident reappeared with black light radiating from its tips.

An ear-splitting screech rang out as three thin streaks of black light shot out of the tips of the trident before vanishing into thin air in a flash.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he hurriedly made a hand seal to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis.

As soon as the axis appeared, it began to rapidly revolve while releasing waves of golden ripples in all directions.

At the moment, only fewer than 20 of the Time Dao Runes on the axis were lit, so the golden ripples were rather lackluster in appearance.

As soon as the golden ripples appeared, the space not far ahead of Han Li shuddered, following which three black threads emerged before hurtling toward his chest at an extraordinary speed.

The black threads were slowed down significantly by the Mantra Treasured Axis, but they were still flying through the air like lightning.

Han Li immediately took evasive measures, but the black threads were too fast, and a small gash was inflicted onto his shoulder.

However, not a single drop of blood flowed out of the gash. Instead, wisps of black qi emerged instead.

Han Li immediately made a beckoning motion to draw one of the nearby Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords back to himself, following which the sword cut viciously into his shoulder, severing the gash along with a large chunk of the flesh connected to it.

As soon as the chunk of flesh was severed, the black qi instantly transformed into black flames that incinerated the piece of flesh into ashes.

Han Li's expression darkened even further upon seeing this.

If he had reacted even just a little slower than he had just now, the injuries that he sustained would've most likely been far more severe.

Meanwhile, the black flames around the giant ghostly head churned, indicating that it was about to unleash some other type of attack, but before it could do so, Han Li made a hand seal, and all of the scattered Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords nearby immediately began to glow radiantly again.

At the same time, thick arcs of lightning sprang out of the swords, then intertwined to form a giant golden lightning net in front of the ghostly head.

Right at this moment, around a dozen huge tentacles suddenly shot out of the black mist around the giant ghostly head before sweeping toward the golden lightning net up ahead.

However, as soon as these misty tentacles came into contact with the lightning net, they immediately disintegrated into plumes of black smoke.

The ghostly head let loose a furious roar, but it was unable to break through the lightning net in a short time.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this. He had unleashed all of the Divine Devilbane Lightning in his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once, and that was finally enough to keep the ghostly head at bay for now.

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air to stow away all of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, following which he transformed into a giant silver bird with arcs of silver lightning flashing all over its body.

This was none other than his Lightning Bird transformation, and as soon as he adopted this form, a second pair of translucent wings appeared on his back.

Those were none other than his Thunderstorm Wings, and with a flap of all four wings at once, Han Li instantly vanished from the spot amid a flash of lightning.

There were unknown dangers littered throughout the Soul Stirring Winds, so he didn't dare to unleash his lightning movement techniques prior to this, but in the face of an insurmountable enemy like this one, he had no choice but to take the risk.

The giant ghostly head let loose a furious roar, and the surrounding black mist instantly converged toward it, causing the black flames around its body to rear up violently.

All of a sudden, the ghostly head also vanished into thin air.

Meanwhile, the Lightning Bird had only just appeared somewhere far away amid a flash of lightning when a burst of spatial fluctuations emerged not far behind it, following which the giant ghostly head appeared, enshrouded within a vast expanse of black flames.

As soon as the ghostly head appeared, it immediately opened its mouth to release three more black threads that shot forth toward the Lightning Bird at an astonishing speed.

The Lightning Bird hurriedly flew through the air as a bolt of silver lightning, just barely evading the black threads before vanishing once again.

The giant ghostly head began cackling with glee, like a predator stalking its prey, as it also vanished into thin air.

After that, Han Li continued to flee through the Soul Stirring Winds while the giant ghostly head gave chase, and no matter what Han Li did to try and escape, even resorting to his lightning teleportation array at one point, the giant ghostly head remained hot on his heels.

Chapter 391: Saved

Some time later, the Lightning Bird appeared somewhere within the Soul Stirring Winds amid a flash of silver lightning, but the arcs of silver lightning around its body had already diminished significantly.

All of a sudden, the Lightning Bird retracted its wings before reverting back to its human form.

Right at this moment, the space no more than 10,000 feet away shuddered, immediately following which the giant ghostly head emerged amid a vast expanse of black flames.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Continuing to run away like this was simply going to be futile, and even though he didn't want to use Daoist Xie, he had no choice but to do so.

With that in mind, arcs of golden lightning emerged over his body, and Daoist Xie was getting ready to strike at any moment.

The giant ghostly head seemed to have also sensed something, and a serious look appeared in its eyes.

Right at this moment, the black mist behind it was abruptly stirred up into a frenzy, following which a ball of dazzling yellow light shot out from within.

It was an ovular burst of yellow light that was over 100 feet in size, and it was revolving rapidly as it hurtled through the air.

Furthermore, the yellow light was very dense, making it impossible to clearly identify what was inside it, and it was giving off formidable energy fluctuations.

As soon as the burst of yellow light appeared, a streak of crimson light with countless crimson runes flashing within it immediately shot forth.

All of the crimson runes then converged to form a translucent crimson thread that shot into the giant ghostly head at an astonishing speed, piercing through the black flames around it with ease.

The crimson thread was so fast that only after it had flown into the giant ghostly head did it realize what had happened, upon which it instantly swung around.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom suddenly rang out from within the ghostly head, and it immediately stiffened, following which the black flames around it began to churn violently.

Another resounding boom rang out as a pillar of crimson flames exploded out of the ghostly head like a volcanic eruption, sending waves of scorching heat sweeping in all directions.

In the span of just a few seconds, the entire ghostly head disintegrated into a vast expanse fo black flames.

A sharp screech rang out from deep within the black flames, following which a black shadow flew out from within, then sped away into the distance, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as blue light flashed within his pupils, and he was able to catch a glimpse of the black shadow.

It was a humanoid creature with a disproportionately large head, and it was wielding the very same trident that Han Li had previously been attacked by.

Unfortunately, the black shadow had fled too quickly for Han Li to get a good look at it.

Han Li withdrew his gaze as he turned his attention to the ball of yellow light. At the same time, he flew back in retreat while making a hand seal, and the Seven Bright Star Rings immediately emerged from his body.

The seven rings hovered around him, forming an orderly star array, and all of the rings were releasing dazzling starlight that connected together to form a starlight restriction.

Even though the ball of yellow light had helped him force the ghostly head into retreat, he was not so naive to believe that this was an ally, so he had to take the necessary safety precautions.

Meanwhile, the ball of yellow light swiveled around slightly, then faded to reveal a yellow flying boat that was around 40 to 50 in length.

It resembled a flying dragon, and it seemed to have been constructed from some type of yellow spirit wood.

At the front of the boat were embedded a pair of bright yellow egg-sized ovular crystals that were giving off a special type of law fluctuation, but Han Li wasn't able to identify the crystals.

There were two people standing next to each other on the flying boat, one of which was none other than Daoist Hu Yan!

There was a rectangular object on his back that was enveloped within a yellow cloth. The object was around a foot in length, and the yellow cloth seemed to be able to keep out spiritual sense, making it impossible for Han Li to see what was beneath it.

Standing beside Daoist Hu Yan was none other than Yun Ni, and a stunned look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

"Elder Hu Yan! Elder Yun Ni!"

"I sensed from afar that a battle was taking place here, so I decided to come and take a look, but I certainly wasn't expecting to see you here," Daoist Hu Yan chuckled.

Meanwhile, Yun Ni merely nodded at Han Li without saying anything.

"I was also not expecting to meet the two of you here," Han Li said with a smile as he made a hand seal to withdraw the starlight restriction around him.

Daoist Hu Yan was his closest acquaintance back in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and the two of them had been quite close.

Ever since the incident back in the Blaze Dragon Dao, Han Li had been keeping tabs on news pertaining to Daoist Hu Yan, but he certainly wasn't expecting to run into him here.

"Looks like we really are connected by fate," Daoist Hu Yan mused with a smile.

"Thank you for stepping in and forcing that black shadow into retreat, Elder Hu Yan," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

"Don't worry about it, I just so happened to be passing through anyway. Speaking of which, how did you end up being pursued by that Yin Wraith? That thing is not easy to deal with, and you're extremely fortunate not to have been devoured by it," Daoist Hu Yan said with a serious expression.

"So that's what it's called. That thing was indeed quite formidable. Do you know its origins, Elder Hu Yan?" Han Li asked.

"Yin Wraiths are a type of creature unique to this area. It's impossible to ascertain their exact cultivation base, but even the average Golden Immortal would struggle to escape the fate of being devoured by one. However, these creatures generally only appear in the deepest parts of the Soul Stirring Winds, so it's very rare to see one so far on the outskirts," Daoist Hu Yan mused with a befuddled expression.

"In any case, these Yin Wraiths are quite powerful, but they're not very intelligent, so now that this one's fled in retreat, it won't come back," Daoist Hu Yan continued.

"That's good to hear. If I hadn't run into the two of you here, I would've most likely met my demise," Han Li replied as he extended a grateful nod.

"Now that we're no longer in the Blaze Dragon Dao, I think it would be best to do away with the 'elder' title," Daoist Hu Yan said with a meaningful expression.

Han Li nodded in agreement.

He had joined the Reincarnation Palace, while Daoist Hu Yan was most likely already a member of the Reincarnation Palace, so they were once again part of the same organization, but Han Li chose not to reveal this information.

"I saw a while back that you've also become a wanted fugitive of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, Fellow Daoist Li. I must say, I feel a little guilty about this. If we hadn't been so close back in the Blaze Dragon Dao, you wouldn't have been implicated by connection," Daoist Hu Yan said in an apologetic voice.

"The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace isn't actually after me because of my connection to you. Instead, I have other differences with the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace," Han Li explained in an ambiguous manner.

"I see. Hold on a minute, have you already reached the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage? No wonder you were able to ward off that Yin Wraith," Daoist Hu Yan said with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

Yun Ni had been standing beside Daoist Hu Yan in silence this entire time, and she was clearly also quite taken back to hear this.

"I was simply very fortunate to have made some progress in my cultivation since we last met," Han Li replied in a humble manner.

"Back when you first joined the Blaze Dragon Dao, you were still only at the early-True Immortal Stage, yet you've reached the pinnacle of the late-True Immortal Stage in just a few centuries since then. I've never heard of anyone in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region making such rapid progress!" Daoist Hu Yan exclaimed with an incredulous expression.

"You're far too kind, Senior Hu Yan. I was only able to make such fast progress by obtaining some pills by chance," Han Li explained, once again intentionally keeping things very ambiguous.

"Is that so? I suppose with the right pills, one can indeed significantly enhance their rate of cultivation progress," Daoist Hu Yan mused with a thoughtful expression.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this.

Thanks to the Heaven Controlling Vial, he was able to make rapid progress in his cultivation, but the downside was that this incredible progress could attract much suspicion from those who had known him over any substantial period of time.

With that in mind, Han Li didn't want to linger on this topic, so he quickly changed the subject. "By the way, what are you two doing here?"

"After escaping from the Blaze Dragon Dao, we've constantly been in hiding from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, but on this occasion, we have to made a trip to the Black Wind Sea for an important matter, but the teleportation array is closed indefinitely, so we had no choice but to pass through these Soul Stirring Winds," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a contemplative nod.

"Why are you also here, Fellow Daoist Li? Could it be that you just came from the Black Wind Sea?" Yun Ni suddenly asked.

"That's correct, Senior Yun Ni. The Black Wind Sea is not a very safe place at the moment," Han Li replied.

A hint of elation flashed through both Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni's eyes upon seeing this, and that certainly didn't escape Han Li's attention.

"Why did you come to a place as secluded as the Black Wind Sea in the first place, Fellow Daoist Li?" Yun Ni asked.

"Prior to joining the Blaze Dragon Dao, I actually stayed in the Black Wind Sea for some time. After becoming a wanted fugitive of the Immortal Palace, I decided to lie low for a while, so I came back to the Black Wind Sea, and I've been able to cultivate in relative peace for the past few centuries. However, there's been a great deal of unrest in the Black Wind Sea of late, and it's no longer safe for me to stay there, so I decided to leave. I also decided to cross through the Soul Stirring Winds due to the inaccessibility of the teleportation array, but it seems I was overconfident in my own powers," Han Li said with a self-deprecating expression.

"What's been happening in the Black Wind Sea recently?" Daoist Hu Yan asked.

Chapter 392: Imminent Emergence of the Immortal Manor

Daoist Hu Yan swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of red light as he spoke, and the streak of light flew toward Han Li before hovering in front of him.

Han Li focused his gaze on the streak of red light to discover that it contained a golden jade vial that was giving off a faint medicinal aroma.

"This is a vial of Six Profound Pills that are very effective for both recovery and restorative purposes. It must've been quite a taxing journey for you through these Soul Stirring Winds, so these pills will be perfect for you," Daoist Hu Yan said.

"I appreciate the kind gesture, Senior Hu Yan, but I can't accept these pills. You've already saved me from that Yin Wraith, so I certainly can't ask for compensation just for answering a few simple questions," Han Li said with a shake of his head as he returned the jade vial to Daoist Hu Yan, who stowed it away again without raising any objections.

After a brief pause, Han Li gave Daoist Hu Yan a recount of what he had seen in the Black Wind Sea, as well as revealing that cultivators of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace had appeared on Black Wind Island.

However, he made no mention of the fact that he had joined the Reincarnation Palace. After all, even though he speculated that Daoist Hu Yan was also a member of the Reincarnation Palace, this wasn't something that Daoist Hu Yan had ever openly admitted to.

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni listened to what he had to say with contemplative looks on their faces, and they didn't appear overly surprised, as if they had already anticipated that all of this would happen.

"It seems like the two of you already expected all of this to happen in the Black Wind Sea," Han Li remarked with a smile.

Daoist Hu Yan raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, while Yun Ni took a glance at him, and both of them remained silent.

"If you don't want to answer the question, then just pretend as if I never asked," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"It would be rude of us to keep secrets, given how candid you've been with us, Fellow Daoist Li," Daoist Hu Yan said after a brief moment of contemplation.

"Hu Yan!" Yun Ni's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"It's fine. Fellow Daoist Li is no stranger to us, and perhaps we may need his help for what we're going to do," Daoist Hu Yan said in a meaningful voice.

Yun Ni didn't say anything further upon hearing this.

"What do you mean by that, Senior Hu Yan? If there are some complicated circumstances involved, then I'm happy to be kept in the dark," Han Li said with slightly furrowed brows.

He was trying to stay out of trouble as much as possible at the moment.

"Don't be so quick to jump to conclusions, Fellow Daoist Li. What I'm about to tell you could be a brilliant opportunity," Daoist Hu Yan said with a hint of mystery in his voice.

"Alright, then please go ahead, Senior," Han Li prompted.

"You just mentioned the increased frequency of natural disasters taking place all over the Black Wind Sea just now, and there's actually a reason for that. To put it in simple terms, an immortal manor is about to emerge, and that's causing a disturbance in the spirit veins in the region. The cultivators of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace have also come precisely for this immortal manor, and that is our objective as well," Daoist Hu Yan revealed.

Han Li was quite taken aback to hear this, but at the same time, this answered some of the questions that had been on his mind of late.

This explained all of the strange actions that had been taken by Black Wind Island and Azure Feather Island, as well as the sudden appearance of Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators in the Black Wind Sea.

The Origin Void Pill that he had refined for Wyrm 3 most likely had something to do with this immortal manor as well.

With all these thoughts racing through his mind, Han Li took a deep breath to collect himself, then continued to listen to Daoist Hu Yan had to say.

"This immortal manor is called the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and it's a cave abode that was left behind by an almighty senior referred to as the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord countless years ago. It's impossible to ascertain just how many years it's been, but it was said that this immortal lord had gone to great lengths to seal this immortal manor in a spatial rift before vanishing without a trace.

“After that, once every few tens of thousands of years, the immortal manor would appear somewhere in the Northern Glacial Immortal Realm. Inside the immortal manor are countless precious treasures, pills, cultivation arts, and even immortal treasures. It could be said that it's the number one treasure trove of the Northern Glacial Immortal Realm," Daoist Hu Yan continued, and at the same time, he was observing Han Li's expresion.

However, Han Li's reaction was rather unexpected to him. Aside from the initial surprise that Han Li had displayed, he had remained quite calm thereafter.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then asked, "Could it be that the opportunity you were referring to earlier is the opportunity for me to accompany the two of you into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor?"

"Precisely! Are you not interested, Fellow Daoist Li?" Daoist Hu Yan asked.

Instead of answering Daoist Hu Yan's question, Han Li said, "It sounds like the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor has already existed for countless years, so it must've emerged quite a few times in the past. Even if there were many precious treasures inside, surely they would've already all been taken at this point."

"You don't have to be concerned about that, Fellow Daoist Li. The immortal manor is rife with restrictions, and it's not easy to obtain the treasures inside. There have been many who have bitten off more than they could chew and lost their lives in the immortal manor, and the possessions that they left behind have added to the treasures waiting to be claimed.

“On top of that, it's said that someone discovered an independent area within the immortal manor during its last opening, and no one knows they found in that area," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

Instead of displaying any excitement upon hearing this, Han Li fell silent once again.

Daoist Hu Yan didn't try to rush Han Li into a decision, merely waiting in silence as he pondered the offer.

"Thank you for the invitation, Senior, but as the saying goes, risk and reward always come hand in hand, and I'm not prepared to take such a risk right now, so I'll have to turn down the offer this time," Han Li decided after some deliberation.

His top priority right now was to find a way to reach the Golden Immortal Stage, and accompanying Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni into this Infernal Frost Immortal Manor was only going to lead him astray.

Most importantly, the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace had also sent many cultivators into the Black Wind Sea on this occasion, with no lack of Golden Immortals among them, and if they were to uncover his identity, then the immortal manor would most likely become his final resting place.

Daoist Hu Yan seemed to have gleaned Han Li's thoughts, and he asked, "Are you worried about encountering Immortal Palace cultivators inside the immortal manor?"

Han Li nodded in response. "I am but a mere True Immortal cultivator, and I'll be completely powerless to defend myself if I encounter any Immortal Palace cultivators."

Furthermore, both Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni were also wanted fugitives of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, so accompanying them into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor would only further increase his chances of exposure.

"There's no need to be concerned about that. I know that you've also joined the Transient Guild, and the disguises that can be adopted using Transient Guild masks are so profound that even Golden Immortal won't be able to see through them easily. If we disguise ourselves as a trio of itinerant cultivators, I'm sure the cultivators of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace wouldn't be able to identify us.

“On top of that, there are always many powers that send cultivators into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor whenever it emerges, and that includes the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect. The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace may be formidable, but they'll have their hands full dealing with their competitors, so they won't be able to target itinerant cultivators like the ones we'll be posing as," Daoist Hu Yan said.

"Are you saying that the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect have also sent people to the Black Wind Sea?" Han Li asked as a hint of surprise appeared on his face.

"The top three sects of our Northern Glacial Immortal Region have never been absent from such an occasion. Even though the Blaze Dragon Dao is no longer the force it once was, the other two sects are relatively unaffected, and I'm sure they've already sent people to the Black Wind Sea upon receiving wind of the immortal manor's imminent emergence.

“Additionally, due to what happened to the Blaze Dragon Dao, the other two sects are harboring more enmity toward the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace than ever before, and there's a decent chance that they'll join forces to target the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace in the immortal manor," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

"So essentially, the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace will be too busy dealing with them to focus on us, is that correct?" Han Li asked.

"That's right," Daoist Hu Yan replied with a nod.

Han Li fell into deep thought upon hearing this.

Daoist Hu Yan did have a point. After all, not only was the Immortal Palace at odds with the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect, it also had the Reincarnation Palace to worry about.

It was very likely that Wyrm 3 was also planning to venture into the immortal manor, and with so many enemies at every turn, it was very likely that the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace would be completely preoccupied.

Daoist Hu Yan could tell that Han Li was beginning to warm to the idea, so he continued, "On top of that, there are many treasures in the immortal manor, and at your current cultivation base, perhaps you'll be able to find an opportunity in there that can help you break through to the Golden Immortal Stage."

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and he asked, "Are there really treasures in the immortal manor that can help one make progress to the Golden Immortal Stage?"

"I've only heard rumors that they exist, but I'm inclined to believe those rumors. After all, there has been a past instance of someone in the immortal manor finding a cauldron full of premium pills that can enhance the cultivation base of Golden Immortals," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

"It sounds like you don't know too much about the immortal manor yourself, Senior. Perhaps there are some precious treasures in there, but I really don't want to risk my life for what could possibly be nothing more than a pipe dream," Han Li said after some contemplation.

"That's a reasonable viewpoint. Cultivators like us do everything in our power to mitigate risk as much as possible. Having said that, you're currently cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture, right?" Daoist Hu Yan asked.

Han Li didn't know why this question was being raised, but he still nodded in response. "That's correct."

"I presume you're not familiar with the origins of this cultivation art, right?" Daoist Hu Yan asked with a mysterious smile.

"Please enlighten me, Senior Hu Yan," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"The Mantra Axis Scripture may be the premier cultivation art of the Blaze Dragon Dao, but it doesn't come from the Blaze Dragon Dao. Instead, it was taken by Dao Lord Baili from a sect called the True Mantra Sect many years ago," Daoist Hu Yan revealed.

Chapter 393: Return

Han Li nodded in response to this revelation, and he wasn't overly surprised.

Even though this was the True Immortal Realm, it wasn't much different in nature from lower realms in that there were still conflicts constantly taking place between cultivators, and every single day, there were countless sects being destroyed, with their treasures and cultivation arts being plundered.

With that in mind, Han Li chose to remain silent. Daoist Hu Yan had clearly mentioned this topic for a reason, and there had to have been a follow-up.

Sure enough, after a brief pause, Daoist Hu Yan continued, "What I want to tell you is that there are more than just three levels of the Mantra Treasured Axis. Instead, the full cultivation art has nine levels."

Han Li's expression instantly changed drastically upon hearing this.

After reaching the pinnacle of the late-True Immortal Stage, he had begun planning for this future cultivation once he reached the Golden Immortal Stage, and he had tried to search for cultivation arts related to the laws of time that were beyond the True Immortal Stage, but to no avail. Hence, he was naturally extremely excited to hear that there were more parts of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

Han Li took a deep breath to suppress his own excitement, then asked, "In that case, why did Senior Baili declare that there were only three levels to the Mantra Axis Scripture?"

"Even in the context of the entire True Immortal Realm, cultivation arts related to the laws of time are exceedingly rare, and those that can support one's cultivation to the Golden Immortal Stage are already extremely sought-after. If it were revealed that the Mantra Axis Scripture had more than three levels, then endless troubles would've most likely awaited the sect," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

"That does make sense," Han Li mused with a contemplative nod.

"On top of that, Dao Lord Baili only obtained the first six levels of the cultivation art, and at the moment, I have all six levels in my possession," Daoist Hu Yan revealed.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was growing rather excited as he asked, "What do you need me to do, Senior Hu Yan?"

"All you need to do is accompany us into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor and help me obtain a certain item. After that, I'll give you the latter three levels of the cultivation art," Daoist Hu Yan replied with a smile.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, Daoist Hu Yan stood calmly with his hands clasped behind his back, seemingly completely unconcerned by the possibility that Han Li could reject him.

A long while later, Han Li raised his head as he said, "If what you're telling me is true, then I'm certainly open to considering the offer. However, I have to make sure that you really do have the latter three levels of Mantra Axis Scripture in your possession."

Daoist Hu Yan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response as he flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip. After that, he cast a few incantation seals into the jade slip before tossing it at Han Li.

Han Li caught the jade slip before briefly inspecting its contents with his spiritual sense, then nodded as he declared, "This indeed a continuation of the Mantra Axis Scripture."

Only the first few lines of the jade slip were revealed to him, but having already mastered the first three levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture, he was naturally able to identify from those few lines whether this was the fourth level of the cultivation art.

"In that case, do we have ourselves an agreement?" Daoist Hu Yan asked with a smile.

"Before I answer that, I have a question that I'd like to ask you," Han Li replied.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Li," Daoist Hu Yan prompted.

"I am just a True Immortal cultivator, and my powers are far inferior to yours, so even if I accompany you into the immortal manor, I struggle to see how I can offer you any meaningful assistance. I'm sure there must be a reason why you're willing to offer me such substantial compensation for my participation, and I want to know that reason," Han Li said.

"Even if you hadn't asked me this question, I would've explained it to you. I've already told you just now that I'm entering the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor in order to obtain a certain item. During this process, my chances of success will be significantly increased if I can benefit from the assistance of your Mantra Treasured Axis," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

"If it's a precious treasure that you're going after, then there will surely be people fighting over it. Will that not put us in a dangerous situation?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"There will definitely be some danger, but the Mantra Axis Scripture is an extremely precious cultivation art, so you can't expect to obtain it without taking any risk. Of course, we'll do everything in our power to keep you safe, but I can't make any promises beyond that," Daiost Hu Yan replied.

Han Li still seemed to be rather hesitant upon hearing this.

"How about this? As a show of sincerity, as long as you're willing to enter the immortal manor with us, I can give you the fourth level of the Mantra Axis Scripture right away, and after we obtain the item that I'm searching for, I'll give you the subsequent two levels," Daoist Hu Yan said.

Han Li contemplated the matter for a moment longer upon hearing this, then nodded in agreement to the offer.

"Alright, in that case, we have ourselves an agreement. Rest assured, you can count on me to follow through on my promises," Daoist Hu Yan said with a smile.

"That was never a concern for me, Senior Hu Yan. We've known each other for many years, and I'm well aware of your integrity and character," Han Li replied with a smile of his own.

"Come and board our flying boat, Fellow Daoist Li. We're still inside the Soul Stirring Winds right now, and this is not a place anyone should stay in for an extended period of time," Daoist Hu Yan said as he made an inviting hand gesture.

Han Li duly obliged, flying onto the yellow flying boat, and Daoist Hu Yan made a hand seal, upon which the entire flying boat began to radiate dazzling yellow light, forming a ball of yellow radiance that encompassed the entire boat.

Immediately thereafter, the ball of yellow light set off at a remarkable speed, and it was giving offtype of special energy fluctuations that seemed to be capable of suppressing Soul Stirring Winds, as evidenced by the face that all of the Soul Stirring Winds in the path of the ball of yellow light instantly parted to grant it free passage.

Sitting on the flying boat, Han Li was surprised to discover that he was unable to hear the sounds of the Soul Stirring Winds at all.

It seemed that this flying boat had similar properties to his Wind Shelter Bead, except those properties were significantly more enhanced in the former.

With that in mind, he began to carefully inspect the flying boat, particularly the three yellow crystals embedded into the boat.

Yun Ni noticed what Han Li was looking at, and she explained, "Those crystals come from the remains of Evil Warding Beasts."

"Evil Warding Beasts? The same beasts that are said to be able to bring luck and ward off misfortune?" Han Li asked with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

He had seen records of this type of beast in some ancient scriptures in the past. It was said that these beasts possessed the innate ability to suppress all evil entities, thereby earning itself a resounding reputation in the True Immortal Realm.

It was also said that those who had such a beast by their side would always be blessed with good fortune, and for this reason, Evil Warding Beasts had been hunted to near extinction many years ago.

"I don't know if Evil Warding Beasts can bring good fortune or not, but Hu Yan used their remains to refine this flying boat, and quite evidently, it's very effective at warding off Soul Stirring Winds," Yun Ni replied with a faint smile.

"I see, as expected of a man of Senior Hu Yan's talents. By the way, where is Bai Suyuan right now?" Han Li asked.

"Yuan'er had already left the Blaze Dragon Dao prior to the preaching ceremony, and she's currently cultivating in a safe place," Yun Ni replied.

"That's good to hear," Han Li replied with a nod.

At the mention of Bai Suyuan, Han Li couldn't help but think of Meng Qianqian and the others. In order to avoid exposing his own identity, he hadn't contacted them at all since last parting ways with them.

However, everyone had to forge rely on themselves in life, and perhaps Meng Qianqian and the others could carve out their own paths without his protection.

Han Li shook his head to rid himself of this train of thought, then closed his eyes and began to cultivate.

Three days passed by in the blink of an eye.

It only took the flying boat three days to cover the same distance that had taken Han Li about half a month to travel.

The three of them were standing in mid-air, looking at the sea up ahead, and Daoist Hu Yan mused, "So this is the Black Wind Sea..."

"The Black Wind Sea is on the outskirts of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so the world's origin qi here is naturally far sparser than elsewhere. At the moment, we're on the northwestern border of the Black Wind Sea. Here are some maps of the entire region," Han Li said as he pulled out a pair of jade slips before handing them to Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

Daoist Hu Yan accepted the jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it, upon which he raised an eyebrow as he remarked, "It looks like the Black Wind Sea is quite a massive region."

"The Black Wind Sea may be secluded, but it's no smaller than the average continent," Han Li agreed with a nod.

Daoist Hu Yan's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing, and he stowed the jade slip away before flipping a hand over to summon a blue scroll, upon which was a piece of scenic artwork.

"That's an Infernal Frost Scenic Painting!" Han Li exclaimed as his gaze fell upon the blue scroll.

"Oh? How do you know that, Fellow Daoist Li?" Daoist Hu Yan asked with a surprised expression.

"I once saw this item being sold in a secret auction held before the preaching ceremony, but that one had been an incomplete artwork, yet even so, it had still been purchased for a very high price. Could it be that you were the one who purchased the item?" Han Li asked.

"An Infernal Frost Scenic Painting was sold at an auction before the preaching ceremony? This is the first time I've heard about this. However, I obtained this artwork from elsewhere, so it's definitely not the same as the one that you saw," Daoist Hu Yan said with a surprised expression.

"Does that mean there are two of these Infernal Frost Scenic Paintings? Also, judging from its name, it seems to have something to do with the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, is that right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. In order to enter the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, you must have an Infernal Frost Scenic Painting, so it acts as a key of sorts. According to my knowledge, there are a total of eight of these paintings.

“The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, the Dawn Fall Sect, the Vast Flow Palace, and the Blaze Dragon Dao all have one each, while the remaining four are missing. The one that you saw during that auction must've been one of those four," Daoist Hu Yan mused.

Chapter 394: Temporary Separation

Han Li was enlightened upon hearing this.

It was no wonder that the mysterious red-robed female cultivator had been willing to pay such a high price for an incomplete Infernal Frost Scenic Painting. With that in mind, Han Li couldn't help but wonder which organization she was affiliated with.

"You just mentioned that the Blaze Dragon Dao also has one such painting. Could it be..."

"That's right, the Blaze Dragon Dao currently no longer has an Infernal Frost Scenic Painting. The painting has always been in the possession of Dao Lord Baili, but now that Dao Lord Baili and I have both left the sect, we naturally took the painting with us," Daoist Hu Yan replied with a smile.

Han Li shook his head as he heaved a faint sigh. "At the height of its powers, our Blaze Dragon Dao was ranked alongside the likes of the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect, with 13 Golden Immortal dao lords and thousands of True Immortals among its ranks, as well as countless subsidiary powers.

“If Dao Lord Ouyang and the others hadn't colluded with the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, there was no way that the Immortal Palace would've been able to do anything to our Blaze Dragon Dao."

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni's expressions both darkened slightly upon hearing this, and it was clear that this was still something that weighed on their mind.

"To be honest, what you saw was only a surface-level picture. In reality, deep-rooted conflicts had already been raging between the 13 dao lords for a very long time, and if it wasn't for Dao Lord Baili, the Blaze Dragon Dao would've been left in the dust by the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect long ago. There's no point in mentioning this now, let's focus on the matter at hand," Daoist Hu Yan sighed.

With that, he began to chant an incantation while making a rapid string of hand seals, and streaks of blue light flew out of his hands to form a circular array projection that was radiating dazzling blue light.

After that, Daoist Hu Yan swept a hand through the air, and the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting that he was holding flew through the air as a streak of blue light before landing at the center of the array in a flash.

Wisps of blue light that resembled clouds and mist instantly began to rise up from the artwork, and a glacial aura also began to spread through the surrounding area, causing the nearby air temperature to plummet.

In the blink of an eye, the surface of the sea within a radius of several dozen kilometers down below had frozen solid, while snowflakes were drifting through the air.

The Infernal Frost Scenic Painting was hovering at the center of the array, and the latter was revolving around the former.

The two were resonating with one another, and the blue light that they were radiating intertwined together before flashing in a rhythmic fashion, as if they were detecting for something.

A hint of curiosity appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, but he didn't ask any questions as he didn't want to distract Daoist Hu Yan.

As for Yun Ni, he wasn't very familiar with her, so he naturally wasn't going to ask her any questions, either.

Moments later, Daoist Hu Yan swept a sleeve through the air, and the entire blue array projection instantly disintegrated into specks of blue light that were then scattered in the wind.

The light radiating from the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting also faded before it returned to Daoist Hu Yan's grasp.

At the same time, the glacial aura in the air also receded, but the surface of the sea down below remained frozen solid.

"How are things looking?" Yun Ni asked.

"Judging from the current signs, there should be roughly three or four years left until the immortal manor emerges," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

Han Li took a glance at the blue scroll that Daoist Hu Yan was holding upon hearing this. It seemed that this painting wasn't just a key.

"What about the exact location?" Yun Ni asked.

"I'm unable to detect it from here, so we must be too far away. Thankfully, we still have time. We can decide on a few locations on the map, then try again from those places," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

Yun Ni nodded in response.

Daoist Hu Yan turned to Han Li as he asked, "Do you have any plans, Fellow Daoist Li? We still have some time left, would you like to stay with us or make some preparations on your own?"

Han Li considered his options for a moment, then replied, "If I'm going to be accompanying the two of you into the immortal manor, then it would be best for me to make some preparations, so I think I'll go off on my own for now."

"That's probably a good idea. The immortal manor is fraught with peril, so it would be in your best interests to make some preparations," Daoist Hu Yan replied with a nod.

He then flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized red array plate before handing it to Han Li as he continued, "Find a safe place, and if you need anything from me, contact me using this Bonfire Plate."

Han Li accepted the array plate to find that there was a flame design emblazoned on its surface, and he nodded in response before stowing it away.

After that, Daoist Hu Yan cautioned Han Li not to be discovered by cultivators from the Immortal Palace, then promptly departed with Yun Ni.

Han Li lingered in the area for a moment longer, then flew away in a different direction as a streak of azure light.

Half a month later.

Han Li emerged near Dark Veil Island amid a flash of azure light.

He took a glance at the island to find that all of the restrictions were still in place, indicating that the island remained in lockdown.

He then withdrew his gaze before flying away into the distance.

On the surface of the sea not far away from Dark Veil Island was an enormous vortex that was rumbling like thunder. All of the seawater within a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers were converging toward the vortex before being sucked into it.

Han Li flew straight into the sea, and before long, he arrived on the seabed.

Within a blue restriction sat his Earthly Deity Avatar with its eyes closed and its legs crossed, and there was a water law thread hovering above its head, slowly revolving in the same direction as the vortex up above.

The surrounding seawater was constantly converging toward the vortex before being rapidly converted into drops of heavy water, and at this point, there was already a ball of heavy water the size of a human head between the Earthly Deity Avatar's palms.

The ball of heavy water didn't appear to be remarkable in any way upon first glance, but Han Li could clearly sense that it was different.

In particular, its density far exceeded that of heavy water of the first level.

Han Li flew into the blue restriction as an azure shadow, then sat down with his legs crossed.

With only three or four years left, he couldn't be bothered to search for another place to go into seclusion, so he decided to return to Dark Veil Island.

He made a beckoning motion, and the ball of second level heavy water flew out of his avatar's grasp before landing in front of him.

Just this small ball of second level heavy water was already as heavy as a mountain that was several thousand feet tall.

Han Li closed his eyes as he released his spiritual sense, and he could sense tremendous water-attribute spiritual power surging out of the ball of second level heavy water, striking him with the false impression that he was currently standing in front of a vast lake.

He opened his eyes, and a pleased look appeared on his face.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly, and he began considering refining all of his first level heavy water into second level heavy water.

However, he then shook his head to dismiss the thought.

He didn't have much time on his hands at the moment, and it was best to leave such a time-intensive task until after he returned from the immortal manor.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li returned the ball of heavy water to his Earthly Deity Avatar, following which a contemplative look appeared on his face.

With only several years left before the emergence of the immortal manor, there wasn't enough time for him to make any substantial progress in any of his cultivation arts. Hence, the only way that he could maximize his powers in a short time would be to work on his spirit treasures and immortal treasures.

Immortal treasures that he had taken from others like the Seven Bright Star Rings weren't going to be easy to refine, so it seemed that his only options were the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and the Heavy Water True Axis.

With that in mind, Han Li raised a hand, and a series of streaks of azure light flew out of his sleeve, transforming into 72 small azure swords with thin arcs of golden lightning flashing over them.

These were none other than his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and they were giving off a tremendous and peerlessly sharp aura, causing the nearby seawater to quiver and shudder.

The swords had been slightly damaged during his battle against that Yin Wraith, but after being nurtured in his body over the past few days, they were close to making a full recovery.

Han Li lifted his other hand, and his Heavy Water True Axis also flew out of his body.

He looked back and forth between the two treasures for a moment, then ultimately decided on the Heavy Water True Axis and stowed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords away.

While his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were his bonded treasure, it was not going to be easy to enhance their powers in a short time, and doing so without a proper plan could have a detrimental effect.

As for his Heavy Water True Axis, this was a faux immortal treasure that he had created using a cultivation art, and it still had much room for improvement. On top of that, even if it were damaged from a failed refinement attempt, the consequences would be far from catastrophic.

After making up his mind, Han Li took a deep breath, then made a hand seal, and the Water Dao Rune on the Heavy Water True Axis instantly lit up, releasing waves of blue ripples.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

As he had progressed in his cultivation through the years, he had developed a deeper understanding of how to use the Heavy Water True Axis in battle. It wasn't going to be very difficult to enhance its power, and he had even considered refining the treasure again on multiple past occasions.

He flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip, which contained the refinement method of the faux axis.

After that, he pressed the jade slip to his own forehead and closed his eyes.

Only after sitting completely still for three days did he reopen his eyes, then rose to his feet before pulling out some materials and beginning to make some inscriptions on the ground.

A day and a night later, an extremely complex array had appeared on the ground.

Within the array were eight ring designs that were giving off bursts of blue light, and Han Li was seated at the center of the array.

His Earthly Deity Avatar had also stopped manifesting heavy water and was seated across from him.

Han Li made a hand seal while opening his mouth to release a ball of azure nascent flames, and at the same time, his Earthly Deity Avatar also opened its mouth to release a ball of blue flames that mixed together with the azure nascent flames.

The two flames came together to form a blue and azure fireball that was several feet in size, and it enveloped the Heavy Water True Axis to scorch it with intense heat.

All of the runes on the Heavy Water True Axis instantly lit up as it began to tremble and buzz.

Chapter 395: Remodeling

Han Li began to chant an incantation while casting a series of incantation seals forward, and the array immediately began to operate.

The eight ring designs within the array blurred momentarily, following which a series of profound golden runes appeared within them, intertwining with one another to form numerous spherical projections in mid-air.

As Han Li continued to cast more incantation seals into the array, the spherical projections exploded into balls of blue flames, making it appear as if the entire array had been set alight.

Right at this moment, he switched to a different hand seal, and all of the balls of fire drifted out of the array before converging toward the Heavy Water True Axis.

The fireball around the Heavy Water True Axis rapidly swelled to the size of a millstone, and the heat that it was radiating was rapidly elevating, causing the surrounding air temperature to spike drastically.

In the face of these scorching blue flames, the spirit patterns on the surface of the axis gradually began to turn transparent.

A month flew by in a flash.

At this point, the Heavy Water True Axis had already turned completely transparent, resembling a translucent blue crystal that was radiating dazzling blue light.

However, this blue light was constantly pulsating, and it was as if the Heavy Water True Axis could succumb to the heat and melt into a liquid form at any moment.

At the same time, the Water Dao Rune on the axis had become even brighter and was giving off formidable water law fluctuations.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, and seven or eight different materials appeared in front of him.

All of these materials were different shades of blue and contained water law powers.

He made a hand seal while sweeping a sleeve through the air, and all of the blue flames in the entire array gradually converged into the eight ring designs in the array.

A few seconds later, all of the blue flames in the array had completely gathered in the eight rings, forming eight pillars of blue fire.

With a wave of Han Li's hand, the eight materials each flew into one of the eight fiery pillars.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li began to chant an incantation, and the eight pillars of blue fire began to rapidly revolve, transforming into eight fiery tornadoes that were radiating scorching heat.

The eight materials within the fiery tornadoes melted into balls of blue liquid one after another, and within each ball of blue liquid was a blue rune that symbolized the law powers that the materials contained.

Han Li gave a slight nod upon seeing this, then switched to a different hand seal once again, upon which the blue liquid within the eight pillars of fire flew out in unison before vanishing into the ball of fire around the Heavy Water True Axis.

Han Li then took a deep breath as a look of concentration appeared on his face, and he began to make a rapid string of hand seals.

Meanwhile, the ball of fire around the Heavy Water True Axis began to revolve, quickly forming a fiery vortex.

The eight pillars of fire within the array also converged and fused into the fiery vortex, causing it to rapidly expand while also increasing in heat.

Large beads of sweat were beginning to appear on Han Li's forehead as he continued to make a rapid string of hand seals, and the eight balls of liquid gradually fused into the Heavenly Water True Axis while the fiery vortex continued to revolve.

With each ball of liquid that was infused, the blue light radiating from the axis would brighten slightly, and countless blue runes could be seen dancing within the light.

The blue light appeared very chaotic, while all of the blue runes inside were also jumping around in a completely haphazard fashion, causing the entire axis to tremble in an unstable fashion.

Right at this moment, the Earthly Deity Avatar's eyes abruptly sprang open, and it made a hand seal as a thick blue translucent thread appeared above its head.

Immediately thereafter, the blue thread shot forth and infused itself into the Heavy Water True Axis.

A burst of blinding blue light erupted out of the Heavy Water True Axis, illuminating the entire seabed within a radius of several hundred kilometers.

A burst of formidable water law fluctuations were emanating from the blue light, sending visible ripples spreading through the surrounding air.

All of a sudden, all of the blue runes around the Heavy Water True Axis were abruptly stabilized before vanishing into the axis in a flash.

Han Li immediately began casting incantation seals into the axis upon seeing this, and the axis began to buzz and tremble, as was the case with the blue light that it was emitting.

In the next instant, the surface of the sea within a radius of hundreds of kilometers began to churn violently, and countless vortexes appeared beneath the surface.

All of a sudden, countless blades and arrows of water began to sweep through the seawater, shredding everything in their path.

All of the living marine creatures within a radius of several hundred kilometers were instantly slaughtered, while a thick layer of the seabed had also been stripped away.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which an elated look appeared in his eyes.

He then took a deep breath, and the elation in his eyes faded. At the same time, the flow of azure nascent flames surging out of his mouth ceased, and the array on the ground instantly stopped functioning as well.

The Earthly Deity Avatar also withdrew the blue nascent flame that was streaming out of its mouth. With all of the flames out of the way, all that was left was the semi-transparent Heavy Water True Axis hovering in mid-air.

Han Li opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence, fused into the Heavy Water True Axis in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, the semi-transparent axis quickly began to take on an opaque black color, and at the same time, it was rapidly cooling down.

Blue light flashed over the axis's surface, and nine specks of gentle blue light emerged before transforming into nine Water Dao Runes.

A burst of water law fluctuations that were several times more formidable than before surged out of the Heavy Water True Axis, and a hint of elation appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

After toiling away for over a month, he had finally succeeded.

He was looking a little weary, and only after taking a recovery pill did his complexion gradually improve.

Han Li exhaled as he examined the Heavy Water True Axis, and the satisfaction in his eyes grew even more pronounced.

The refinement had been unexpectedly successful, and the axis's power had been significantly enhanced. Even though he hadn't tested it in battle yet, he estimated that it was at least four to five times more powerful than before.

The primary reason for this was the substantial investment that Han Li had made, infusing eight materials that contained water law powers into the Heavy Water True Axis at once. Many of these materials had been obtained from Han Li's past enemies, and they could've been used to refine an immortal treasure or two of comparable power to the Heavy Water True Axis.

Now that all of them had been infused into the Heavy Water True Axis, it only made sense that there was such a significant enhancement in power.

Aside from that, there was another important factor, which was that the water law thread that the Earthly Deity Avatar had manifested from the power of faith had also been infused into the Heavy Water True Axis.

A water law thread manifested by an Earthly Immortal wasn't going to be as pure as one manifested by a True Immortal who had truly mastered the laws of water, but it was still nothing to be scoffed at.

Han Li made a beckoning motion to draw the Heavy Water True Axis into his grasp, and he felt as if he were holding a vast sea, allowing him to control all of the water-attribute spiritual power within a radius of thousands of kilometers.

Han Li tossed the Heavy Water True Axis before making a hand seal, and the axis began to emit dazzling blue light as all nine of the Water Dao Runes on its surface lit up, forming a blue ring of light.

He closed his eyes as he carefully sensed the change taking place within the blue ring of light, trying to glean the laws of water.

Even though he was currently cultivating the laws of time, it naturally couldn't hurt to master more laws.

Having just remodeled the Heavy Water True Axis, he had developed a deeper understanding of the laws of water, and he was certainly going to take full advantage of this opportunity.

A burst of water-attribute law powers began to spread through the area, and the nearby seawater began to churn violently once again, sending enormous waves sweeping over the surface.

Right at this moment, a burst of black light flashed from the Heavenly Water Pouch strapped to the Earthly Deity Avatar's waist, and a ball of second level heavy water flew out from within.

As soon as the ball of heavy water emerged, it immediately flew toward the Heavy Water True Axis before fusing into it.

The light radiating from the Heavy Water True Axis rippled slightly, then became a little brighter.

Han Li's eyes sprang open as a hint of surprise appeared on his face, but he made no effort to stop what was happening.

The Heavy Water True Axis continued to revolve as one ball of heavy water after another flew out of the Heavenly Water Pouch before fusing into the axis.

Due to the time constraints, the Earthly Deity Avatar hadn't manifested much second level heavy water, and before long, the Heavenly Water Pouch was completely emptied.

After absorbing all of this heavy water, the blue light radiating from the axis had become brighter, while the axis itself had also become significantly heavier.

This was a very pleasant surprise to Han Li.

Back when the Heavy Water True Axis was first refined, it hadn't been all that powerful, and only after it had absorbed a huge quantity of first level heavy water did it become one of his trump cards.

Unfortunately, it was unable to absorb more heavy water beyond a certain point, thereby stunting its growth, but now, following its remodeling, it had regained the ability to absorb heavy water.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, and a ball of first level heavy water flew out of one of his Heavenly Water Pouches before enveloping the Heavy Water True Axis.

However, the Heavy Water True Axis seemed to be rather resistant to level one heavy water and refused to absorb it.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he quickly realized why this was happening.

Not only had the Heavy Water True Axis become far more powerful following the refinement process, the energy that it contained had also become far purer.

In comparison, the energy imbued within the first level heavy water was of an inferior level, so it would've actually only been detrimental for the axis to absorb first level heavy water.

"It looks like I'll have to refine all of my first level heavy water, after all," he murmured to himself as he flipped a hand over to produce a Heavenly Water Pouch, then handed it to his Earthly Deity Avatar.

At this point, there were only roughly three years left until the emergence of the immortal manor, so time was very tight, and the more second level heavy water that he could refine, the more powerful the Heavy Water True Axis would become.

The Earthly Deity Avatar accepted the Heavenly Water Pouch, then drew out a large ball of first level heavy water.

At the same time, dazzling blue light began to radiate from its body as bursts of power of faith were transmitted to it from afar, while a tiny blue thread of light appeared above his head.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of the thin blue thread.

All of the water law powers that the Earthly Deity Avatar had manifested from the power of faith had been infused into the Heavy Water True Axis, thereby leaving the avatar's cultivation base severely impaired, and now, it had to start all over again in its manifestation of law powers.

Chapter 396: Preparations

The Earthly Deity Avatar made a hand seal as it channeled is Black Sea Heavy Water Tome, and the thread of light above its head began to emit beams of blue light with countless tiny blue runes within them, shining upon the first level heavy water in its hands.

The heavy water instantly began to condense, slowly evolving into second level heavy water.

However, this process was extremely slow, and Han Li could only heave a faint sigh upon seeing this.

The rate of heavy water manifestation was extremely slow to begin with, and now that the avatar's water law powers had been significantly impaired, this process was only going to be even slower.

At this rate, it wasn't going to be able to manifest much second level heavy water at all in three years.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li flipped a hand over to summon his Heaven Controlling Vial, inside of which was a drop of green spirit liquid.

He then cast an incantation into the vial, and all of a sudden, countless dark clouds began to gather in the sky, while the world's origin qi began to churn violently.

Several days later, Han Li was holding a time crystal in his hand.

With his immense late-True Immortal Stage immortal spiritual power, manifesting these time crystals was no longer very taxing on him at all.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the time crystal flew over to his Earthly Deity Avatar, following which the translucent golden thread inside fused into the thread of blue light.

The thread of blue light instantly brightened significantly as a layer of golden light appeared on its surface, while the rate at which the ball of first level heavy water in its hands was being converted into second level heavy water was sped up significantly.

Before long, the entire ball of first level heavy water had been converted into second level heavy water.

The Earthly Deity Avatar stowed the ball of heavy water away, then produced another ball of first level heavy water to continue the conversion process.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this.

Thankfully, the time crystals were capable of accelerating this process. Otherwise, he would've been at a loss for what to do.

After lingering on the seabed for a while longer, he rose up through the water and quickly broke through the surface.

From there, he inspected his surroundings briefly before descending onto a small coral island near Dark Veil Island.

The seabed was quite peaceful and safe, but the moonlight wasn't able to reach the seabed, so he wouldn't be able to manifest more spirit liquid.

With a sweep of his sleeve, a series of array flags flew out before landing near the island.

This was a very secluded place, so Han Li didn't bother to be too meticulous with his security measures, only setting up a few arrays before sitting down with his legs crossed and setting down his Heaven Controlling Vial beside him.

After that, he swept his sleeve through the air once again to summon the ingredients required to refine the Golden Soul Pill.

He had already gathered all of the required materials, but he had been too busy to refine the pill prior to this.

Now that he had nothing to do anyway, he decided to take advantage of this opportunity to refine this pill in preparation for a future breakthrough.

After meditating for some time to prime himself into the best condition, he flipped a hand over to produce his silver cauldron, then opened his mouth to release his Flame of Essence onto the underside of the cauldron.

After doing all of that, he summoned the jade box that contained Tao Yu's nascent soul, then removed all of the restrictions around the nascent soul before transferring it into the cauldron.

Once that was done, he opened his mouth to release a stream of azure nascent flames that mixed together with the Flame of Essence, and the temperature within the cauldron was instantly significantly elevated.

Enveloped within the two flames, the nascent soul was being subjected to scorching heat while Han Li observed the changes taking place within the nascent soul with rapt focus.

At the same time, he was constantly making hand seals to control the two-colored flames within the cauldron.

Close to a month flew by in the blink of an eye.

At this point, the nascent soul within the cauldron had shrunk down into a fist-sized golden bead with streaks of translucent light surging over its surface.

Han Li picked up another ingredient before transferring it into the cauldron, and close to another month flew by in a flash.

On this day, the world's origin qi in the area suddenly began to rumble and churn, while beams of golden light emerged to form a series of golden flowers.

At the same time, heavenly music was ringing out across the heavens, and an ecstatic look appeared on Han Li's face as he stared at the cauldron in front of him.

Hovering in the air above the cauldron was a longan-sized golden pill that was giving off dazzling golden radiance, and it was none other than a Golden Soul Pill.

The refinement process for the Golden Soul Pill wasn't actually all that complicated, and with Han Li's current level of pill refinement proficiency, he was able to successfully refine the pill in less than two months.

There was a projection of a miniature humanoid figure around the pill, and it was as if the pill possessed a soul.

At the same time, it was giving off a peculiar medicinal aroma, and as soon as Han Li breathed in this aroma, he could feel his own soul beginning to display signs of making a breakthrough.

"As expected of a pill that can elevate one's soul," Han Li praised as he carefully stored the Golden Soul Pill into a jade box, then adhered a few talismans to the box before stowing it away into his storage bracelet.

After that, he made a beckoning motion to draw his Heaven Controlling Vial to himself, then cast an incantation seal into it, and all of the world's origin qi around the coral island instantly began to converge toward the Heaven Controlling Vial in a frenzy.

Several days later, the surging world's origin qi around the coral island gradually subsided, while the Heaven Controlling Vial slowly descended, and the drop of spirit liquid inside had been converted into a time crystal.

He stowed the vial away, then took a recovery pill before sweeping a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which enveloped the time crystal before transporting it to the seabed.

Moments later, the streak of azure light returned from the seabed, carrying a Heavenly Water Pouch.

It was flying in a rather sluggish manner, as if it were carrying a huge mountain.

Han Li reached out to grab the Heavenly Water Pouch, and his arm instantly sank down a little.

He released his spiritual sense to inspect the contents of the pouch, and to his elation, he discovered that it already contained enough second level heavy water to fill a pond.

It seemed that with the time crystal speeding up the process, the Earthly Deity Avatar was able to manifest second level heavy water quite quickly, even though the avatar's water law powers were severely hampered.

With that in mind, he summoned his Heavy Water True Axis, then drew a ball of second level heavy water around the size of a human head out of the Heavenly Water Pouch.

The ball of heavy water then spread over the axis at Han Li's behest, and blue light began to radiate from the nine Water Dao Runes on the Heavy Water True Axis, illuminating the entire nearby area a bright blue color.

The nine Water Dao Runes began to rapidly devour the second level heavy water like nine mouths, and it didn't take long before all of the heavy water had been absorbed, following which the light radiating from the axis became slightly brighter once again.

Han Li continued this process without pause, infusing another ball of heavy water into the axis.

One ball of second level heavy water after another flew out of the Heavenly Water Pouch before fusing into the Heavy Water True Axis, and after a day and a night, the Heavenly Water Pouch was finally emptied.

The axis was glowing with dazzling blue radiance, and as it revolved, it was giving off astonishing power that was causing the nearby space to tremble incessantly.

It was clear that the axis had become noticeably more powerful after absorbing the heavy water.

Furthermore, unlike before, when the axis's spiritual connection with Han Li had been severed after it had absorbed too much first level heavy water, even though the axis had absorbed close to a pond's worth of second level heavy water, its spiritual connection with Han Li still remained completely unaffected.

Han Li's gaze fell upon the nine Water Dao Runes on the axis as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

The axis's improved tolerance capacity for heavy water was most likely due to the increase in the number of Water Dao Runes.

This was certainly good news as he wouldn't have to refine the axis with his nascent flame like before.

……

Three years later.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on the coral island, and it was as if he had never moved from that spot in the past three years.

At this moment, a ball of radiant blue light was hovering in front of him, and beside it was a ball of heavy water.

Within the ball of blue light was the Heavy Water True Axis, and even though it was merely hovering in mid-air, it was still giving off an incredibly heavy aura that was causing the nearby space to tremble and ripple, as if even the space itself were unable to bear its enormous weight.

Han Li made a hand seal, and the Heavy Water True Axis began to slowly revolve.

The trembling of the surrounding space instantly became even more violent, while enormous waves were swept up over the nearby sea and gusts of ferocious wind were howling through the air. Thankfully, the coral island remained unaffected thanks to the restrictions that had been set up in advance.

The blue light radiating from the Heavy Water True Axis enveloped the surrounding heavy water before rapidly absorbing it.

Once all of the heavy water was gone, Han Li made a beckoning motion, and the Heavy Water True Axis instantly stopped revolving. The blue light that it was radiating also faded as it fell into Han Li's grasp.

As soon as the axis ceased in its rotation, all of the unrest in the surrounding area also subsided, and it was as if nothing had ever happened here.

The Heavy Water True Axis looked no different from before aside from the fact that the nine Water Dao Runes on its surface had become noticeably larger, and they resembled nine blue swirling vortexes.

Furthermore, they were giving off far more formidable water law fluctuations than before.

The nine bursts of law fluctuations came together to form a formidable stream, and in terms of sheer volume of law power, the axis possessed far more than any of Han Li's other immortal treasures.

With this significantly enhanced Heavy Water True Axis, Han Li's chances of survival in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor would undoubtedly be increased.

A hint of excitement appeared on his face as he examined the axis. Even though it had been absorbing second level heavy water for the past three years, it showed no signs of slowing down, so it was clear that it could still absorb far more.

Chapter 397: Well-prepared

With that in mind, Han Li patted the Heavenly Water Pouch strapped to his waist.

He still had quite a large quantity of first level heavy water left. Up to this point, only around a third of the heavy water in the pouch had been converted into second level heavy water before being absorbed by the Heavy Water True Axis, and he couldn't help but wonder how much more the axis would be able to absorb.

He promptly stowed the axis away before flipping a hand over to summon the crimson communication array plate that had been given to him by Daoist Hu Yan.

Three years had already passed by, and according to what Daoist Hu Yan had said, the emergence of the immortal manor was imminent, yet Han Li hadn't been contacted at all.

Has there been a change of plans?

Initially, he hadn't actually been all that eager to go to this immortal manor. After all, there were many powers involved, including the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and with so many Golden Immortals in the mix, it was going to be a very perilous trip. Even if there were many precious treasures inside the immortal manor, they were simply not worth risking his life over.

However, after learning that Daoist Hu Yan possessed three more levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture, he had no choice but to take this matter seriously, particularly after already having witnessed the tip of the iceberg when it came to the unfathomable power of the laws of time.

With these thoughts running through his mind, he was considering whether he should be the one to contact Daoist Hu Yan, but he quickly abandoned the idea after some contemplation.

Regardless of whether Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni had found the entrance to the immortal manor, he wasn't going to be able to help them, so the best thing for him to do was to remain patient and not disturb them.

Even though the Black Wind Sea wasn't very safe at the moment, with their combined powers, they should be safe unless they encountered an opponent of Xiao Jinhan's caliber.

With that in mind, Han Li stowed the array plate away as a contemplative look appeared in his eyes.

All of a sudden, he flipped a hand over to produce a storage pouch, which contained the remaining batches of Origin Void Pill ingredients.

After that, he stowed his Heaven Controlling Vial, then flew toward a certain direction, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Only after flying for several days without pause did Han Li stop on a deserted island countless kilometers away from Dark Veil Island.

This place was already quite close to the Soul Stirring Winds, so there was a great deal of disturbance in the world's origin qi, coupled with howling winds and enormous waves.

He paid no heed to the terrible environment as he released his spiritual sense throughout the surrounding area, and only after confirming that there were no potential hazards around did he withdraw his spiritual sense.

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a thick stack of array tools.

He then began to chant an incantation, and all of the array tools flew to various parts of the island before vanishing out of sight.

Moments later, a yellow cloud restriction emerged to encompass the entire island.

In the blink of an eye, the island was completely isolated from the outside world, and it was as if it had become an independent space.

Before long, a thick azure restriction had also been set up outside of the yellow cloud restriction, following which a white mist restriction appeared outside of the azure one.

In the blink of an eye, seven or eight restrictions had taken shape to encompass the entire island, and the outermost one was a blue restriction with countless ripples surging over its surface. As soon as this restriction appeared, the entire island instantly vanished, blending in with the sea around it.

These were the exact same restrictions that Han Li had used to protect his temporary cave abode, so he was able to set them up in a very well-rehearsed fashion.

Han Li took a glance at his surroundings, then sat down with his legs crossed onto a plot of flat ground at the center of the island.

He then raised a hand to release a burst of silver light, which transformed into a silver cauldron that landed in front of him.

Immediately thereafter came another streak of silver light. This time, it was the Flame of Essence, and it landed on the underside of the cauldron.

After preparing everything, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce the storage pouch from before, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a batch of Origin Void Pill ingredients.

After taking some time to compose himself, he immediately picked up one of the ingredients beside him before transferring it into the cauldron.

He was planning to use the remaining time before the emergence of the immortal manor to try and refine another Origin Void Pill. He didn't know what the pill could be used for, but he speculated that Wyrm 3 was most likely planning to use it in the immortal manor for some purpose.

Initially, he was only a little curious about this pill, but seeing as he was also going to venture into the immortal manor, he may as well refine one for himself. It certainly couldn't hurt to be well-prepared, and perhaps the pill could come in useful.

He had chosen to come all the way here to refine the pill instead of refining it near Dark Veil Island in light of the pill tribulation that had descended the last time he had refined this pill.

Thanks to his prior experience, he was already quite proficient in the refinement of the Origin Void Pill, and he was flying through the steps with efficiency and precision.

While Han Li was refining the Origin Void Pill, a blue-robed middle-aged man was standing in mid-air above a nameless island countless kilometers away.

The man was none other than Luo Qinghai, and at this moment, his brows were tightly furrowed in agitation, in stark contrast with his normal composed and measured demeanor.

Standing behind Luo Qinghai was the effeminate young man by the name of Nan Kemeng, and at this moment, his brows were also tightly furrowed.

Neither of them were saying anything, and the atmosphere was a little heavy.

Right at this moment, a streak of blue light appeared on the distant horizon, and both of them immediately turned to that direction.

The streak of blue light quickly arrived in front of Luo Qinghai and Nan Kemeng, then faded to reveal a middle-aged man with a coarse beard.

As soon as the man appeared, he cupped his fist to extend a salute, only for Luo Qinghai to raise a hand to stop him as he asked in an urgent voice, "No need for formalities. Have you discovered anything?"

The bearded man was silent for a moment, then shook his head in response. "The seven of us have scoured the areas that we're responsible for several times, but none of us have been able to find anything."

Luo Qinghai's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but Nan Kemeng could clearly detect that the air temperature had dropped slightly.

"Should we continue, Palace Master?" the bearded man asked in a hesitant voice.

"Yes. Expand the scope of the search, and make sure no detail is missed," Luo Qinghai instructed in a grim voice.

"Yes, Palace Master," the bearded man replied, then flew away as a streak of light.

"Master, is it possible that the information we've received is inaccurate, and the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor isn't actually going to be emerging in the Black Wind Sea?" Nan Kemeng asked.

"No. The signs of the immortal manor's imminent emergence have become more and more apparent in the Black Wind Sea in recent years, and the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting is also reacting here, so there's no mistaking it," Luo Qinghai replied with a shake of his head.

"In that case, why are we unable to find the entrance? According to past records, as long as one has the painting, it shouldn't be difficult to find the entrance of the immortal manor," Nan Kemeng said.

"There's only one possibility..." Luo Qinghai mused as his eyes narrowed slightly.

"What is it?" Nan Kemeng asked.

Luo Qinghai offered on reply as he flipped a hand over to produce a small blue mirror, then cast an incantation seal into it, and immediately swelled to several times its original size while radiating dazzling blue light.

A series of images rapidly flashed over the mirror, and only after a long while did the image stabilize, revealing a middle-aged man with a purplish-red face.

"How are things going on your end, Junior Martial Brother Fan?" Luo Qinghai asked, and he was speaking in a much warmer tone than when he was speaking with the bearded man from before.

"Not well, I'm afraid. The people from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace suddenly disappeared some time ago along with some important figures from Black Wind Island, and we've been unable to track them down up to this point," the man in the mirror replied with a shake of his head.

Luo Qinghai's expression darkened even further upon hearing this.

After hearing this exchange, Nan Kemeng also realized what Luo Qinghai had been alluding to earlier, and he asked, "Master, are you speculating that the people from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace have done something to prevent us from finding the entrance?"

"It's most likely the case that Xiao Jinhan has sealed the entrance using some type of secret technique. Otherwise, it would've definitely already appeared by now, given that there's less than a year left before the emergence of the immortal manor," Luo Qinghai replied.

"I don't know much about the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, but I do know that the entrance of the immortal manor is a connective point between two realms, so there's no way it could be sealed discreetly in a short time," Nan Kemeng said with furrowed brows.

"He was most likely somehow able to ascertain the location of the entrance in advance, then set up some restrictions there beforehand," Luo Qinghai harrumphed coldly.

An incredulous look appeared on Nan Kemeng's face upon hearing this.

"There's not much time left until the emergence of the immortal manor. What should we do, Palace Master?" the man in the mirror asked.

"We have to find the entrance of the immortal manor no matter what. Keep searching for leads on the people from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace and the master of Black Wind Island. There are so many of them, there's no way that they could've simply disappeared into thin air without leaving any traces behind. Employ some extreme measures if necessary," Luo Qinghai said in a meaningful voice.

"Yes, Palace Master," the man in the mirror replied, then quickly vanished from the mirror.

Luo Qinghai made a hand seal, and the blue mirror rapidly shrank down before flying back up his sleeve.

After that, he remained standing on the spot for a moment longer, then abruptly swept a sleeve through the air to envelop both himself and Nan Kemeng before flying away into the distance.

Chapter 398: Time Running Out

Meanwhile

There were around a dozen figures standing in mid-air above a certain area in the Black Wind Sea.

All of them were dressed in black robes, they were members of the Dawn Fall Sect.

They were led by none other than the zombie-like Feng Tiandu and the master of the Dawn Fall Sect.

Aside from those two, three of the other Dawn Fall Sect cultivators present were also Golden Immortals.

One of them was extremely tall and rotund, resembling a mountain of flesh from afar.

The other two had much more normal figures, but the coloration of their skin was very peculiar.

One of them had skin that was as black as ink, and in dim light, it would've been difficult to even discern his facial features from one another. In contrast, the other man was as pale as a sheet, and even his hair and eyebrows were completely white and devoid of color.

As for the rest of the Dawn Fall Sect cultivators, all of them were at the mid or late-True Immortal Stage.

The portly Golden Immortal turned to Feng Tiandu and the Dawn Fall Sect Master as he reported, "According to our search, not only have the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators disappeared from Black Wind Island, Island Master Lu Jun and several of his most important subordinates have also gone missing.

“After performing a soul search technique on one of the administrators, I learned that they had suddenly disappeared several days ago."

"It's just as you say, Senior Martial Brother. Xiao Jinhan has most likely somehow concealed the entrance of the immortal manor," the Dawn Fall Sect Master said with a grim expression.

"Looks like we were too careless. This emergence of the immortal palace is more significant than previous ones, so I should've predicted that Xiao Jinhan would take some measures to prevent others from getting in," Feng Tiandu sighed.

"I also discovered that aside from our Dawn Fall Sect, there are several other powers that are also searching for the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators," the portly Golden Immortal continued.

"Oh? How many are there?" Feng Tiandu asked.

"Around two or three, but all of them are very alert, so I didn't dare to get too close, and I wasn't able to find out too much. However, I'm certain that I spotted Western Extreme Palace Master Cui Can of the Vast Flow Palace's Five Extreme Palaces among them," the rotund Golden Immortal replied.

"Seeing as we were able to determine that the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace had to have concealed the entrance of the immortal manor, the other powers must've been able to arrive at the same conclusion as well," Feng Tiandu said.

"How could Xiao Jinhan do something so deplorable? He's trying to keep everyone out of the immortal manor! What do we do now, Senior Martial Brother?" the Dawn Fall Sect Master asked as he turned to Feng Tiandu with tightly furrowed brows.

"There's still some time left until the immortal manor emerges, and we have to find the entrance before then no matter what. Otherwise, if Xiao Jinhan obtains what he's searching for, then our Dawn Fall Sect will be at risk for suffering the same fate as the Blaze Dragon Dao," Feng Tiandu said in a cold voice.

……

In Black Wind City.

In a room in an inn at the center of the city sat a man and a woman.

They were none other than Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni in disguise, and there was a lavish feast laid out before them, but neither of them showed any interest in it, and both appeared quite agitated.

"I didn't think Xiao Jinhan would have a trick like this up his sleeve. We don't have much time left, Hu Yan. What should we do?" Yun Ni asked with a hint of anxiety in her voice.

"It looks like continuing to wait in Black Wind City isn't going to do us any good, so let's go search elsewhere. In any case, we have to find the entrance of the immortal manor no matter what!" Daoist Hu Yan said with a determined expression.

"But we're only two people, and the Black Wind Sea is so vast. How are we supposed to find the entrance on our own? Should we call upon Li Feiyu to help us? It most likely won't make a difference, but I suppose we can always give that a try as a last resort," Yun Ni proposed.

"There's no need for that. This region isn't very safe at the moment, so we should avoid contact with others as much as possible. As for how we're going to find the entrance, I have some ideas," Daoist Hu Yan said as he rose to his feet, then made his way out of the room.

Yun Ni knew that once Daoist Hu Yan made up his mind, there was no dissuading him, so she could only heave a faint sigh before following him out of the room.

……

On a rather desolate-looking island elsewhere in the Black Wind Sea, a group of white-robed cultivators were gathered.

The group consisted of around a dozen people, all of whom were standing in small groups of two or three in silence.

Judging from the way that they were arranged, their leader appeared to be a square-faced elderly man standing at the center of the group, and his aura indicated that he was a Golden Immortal, while everyone else around him were True Immortals.

At this moment, all of them were looking around with anticipation in their eyes, seemingly waiting for someone or something.

Some time later, a streak of silver light appeared on the distant horizon, and it was traveling at a rapid speed, arriving near the island in the blink of an eye.

The streak of silver light contained a silver-robed woman, and the square-faced elderly man immediately approached her with a fawning smile on his face as he greeted, "Welcome, Fellow Daoist Qu."

A faint smile appeared on the silver-robed woman's face as she asked, "Have you made any discoveries?"

"Not at the moment, but even though our Xue Clan moved out of the Black Wind Sea many years ago, we still have many contacts here, and I've already sent out people to get in touch with these contacts while also helping out in the search, so I'm sure we'll find something soon," the square-faced elderly man replied.

The silver-robed woman's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and she said, "There's not much time left before the emergence of the immortal manor, so we have to do everything in our power to find the entrance. Otherwise, all of us will have come here for nought."

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Qu, we're doing everything in our power," the square-faced elderly man immediately replied.

The silver-robed woman nodded in response, then spoke to the elderly man for a while longer before flying away as a streak of silver light.

A long-faced man swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a white light barrier around everyone, then approached the square-faced elderly man as he said, "Esteemed patriarch, that woman's cultivation base is far superior to ours, and she claims that she wants to work with our Xue Clan to venture into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor together, but is she really being earnest and forthcoming with us?

“She tries to hide her malice behind that smile of hers, but I can tell she's not a kind person."

"I'm sure she won't turn on us. Her cultivation base is indeed far superior to ours, but she's on her own, while all of the other powers that have come to the Black Wind Sea have superior numbers on their side, so it makes sense that she would want to secure some allies," the square-faced elderly man replied.

The long-faced man didn't say anything, but the concern on his face didn't diminish at all.

"Rest assured, with the Snow Silkworm Array from the 10 of you and myself, we'll be able to ensure at least self-preservation. Even if she wants to use us, it's not like she can interfere with what we do once we enter the immortal manor," the square-faced elderly man said with a faint smile, seemingly quite pleased with himself.

The long-faced man's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he smiled as he said, "You're right, esteemed patriarch. It seems I was just excessively cautious."

Meanwhile, the silver-robed woman was racing over the sea, and there was a longhorn beetle perched on her shoulder. Its body was a pristine white color, as if it had been carved out of jade, and at this moment, the voice of the square-faced elderly man was coming out of its mouth.

"... it's not like she can interfere with what we do once we enter the immortal manor..."

"Pathetic little bugs," the silver-robed woman scoffed to herself with a cold sneer. "I suppose I'll spare you for now, seeing as you're still useful to me."

The silver-robed woman stowed the white longhorn beetle away, then began making a string of hand seals, and a cloud of white mist flew out of her sleeve.

The mist then quickly dispersed in all directions, revealing itself to be a swarm of tiny semi-transparent white insects.

A Core Formation Stage eel demon beast was swimming through the sea when it came into contact with a few of these white insects, and the insects immediately vanished into its body like water droplets into cotton, but the eel demon beast remained completely oblivious as it continued to swim through the water.

Similar scenes were unfolding across the entire nearby area at the moment, with these white insects entering the bodies of all types of marine demon beasts and even ordinary fish as they spread far and wide at a rapid speed.

……

Meanwhile, a group of around a dozen cultivators were seated in a circular formation on a calm area of the sea.

There were three bald men hovering in front of the group, all three of whom were at the Golden Immortal Stage, while the others were all True Immortals.

Each of these cultivators had a small blue flag hovering in front of them, with countless runes visible on each flag.

All of the flags were giving off water law fluctuations, indicating that they were immortal treasures, and they appeared to be part of the same set.

These cultivators were collectively chanting an incantation while making a constant string of hand seals, and dazzling blue light was radiating from the flags before coming together to form an enormous blue light barrier that resembled a huge mirror.

Each of the three bald Golden Immortals had a palm outstretched, sending a pillar of blue light surging into the giant mirror, and all of a sudden, the mirror shattered into several dozen smaller mirrors amid an audibel crack.

Each mirror depicted a different setting, varying from under the sea, or in the sky, or on an island.

Different images were constantly flashing over these mirrors, and all of the cultivators present were scrutinizing the mirrors intently to see what was happening in all of those places.

……

All of the major powers that had come to the Black Wind Sea were naturally feeling extremely agitated by their inability to track down the immortal manor's location, and all of them were searching frantically.

Initially, they tried to cover their tracks as much as possible, but as time passed and they became more desperate, they gradually began to throw caution to the wind, not bothering to keep their search secretive any longer.

With so many formidable foreign cultivators suddenly appearing in the Black Wind Sea, all of the local powers were left feeling quite uneasy, and more and more islands were going into lockdown.

Chapter 399: Another Piece of News

Half a year flew by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, the world's origin qi in a certain area on the outskirts of the Black Wind Sea suddenly began to churn violently, and countless dark clouds appeared in the sky before forming a massive vortex.

Immense law fluctuations were emanating from the dark clouds, raising turbulent waves of the nearby sea and sweeping up ferocious gusts of wind.

Thankfully, this area was quite close to the Soul Stirring Winds, so the disturbance wasn't all that apparent.

The black cloud churned and rumbled for a while before a thick pillar of black light shot down from the vortex amid a resounding boom.

There seemed to be nothing but empty sea down below, but all of a sudden, multiple layers of restrictions appeared in the path of the pillar of black light.

In the blink of an eye, the pillar of black light pierced through these light barriers before continuing onward, only to be stopped cold in its tracks by a gray mountain projection.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the surrounding space shuddered, as did the nearby sea, and a series of massive rifts appeared on the seabed.

After releasing that pillar of black light, the black cloud up above quickly dispersed, and the restrictions above the surface of the sea also faded to reveal Han Li.

His complexion was looking a little pale, but there was an elated look on his face.

He exhaled as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a ball of bright azure light that revolved rapidly around the island, gathering all of the array tools distributed throughout the island before returning them up his sleeve.

In the next instant, Han Li began to make a rapid string of hand seals, and arcs of golden lighting appeared over his body before spreading outward to form a golden lightning array.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li vanished from the array amid a rumbling thunderclap.

……

A tall and imposing figure was seated in a dim space somewhere in the Black Wind Sea.

Their entire body was enshrouded within a layer of black mist, making it impossible to catch a clear glimpse of them, and there was a menacing aura emanating out of the black mist.

There were several other figures seated around the tall figure, but none of them dared to get too close.

Right at this moment, all of the black mist around the tall figure surged into their body, revealing none other than Xiao Jinhan.

A peculiar look appeared on his face as he cast his gaze toward a certain direction while rising to his feet, and everyone else around him hurriedly stood up as well.

These were none other than the Golden Immortal Stage elders of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and Deputy Palace Master Xue Ying was also among them.

"What is it, Palace Master?" Xue Ying asked in a respectful voice.

Xiao Jinhan paid no heed to her as he flipped a hand over to produce a white jade plate that was around the size of a washbasin.

The entire plate seemed to have been crafted from some type of white jade material, and there were many antiquated designs etched onto the edge of the plate, while a series of white jade grids were present on the plate, slowly revolving around the plate's center.

Gentle white light was radiating from the plate, while a streak of black light had emerged in one of the grids on the edge of the plate, presenting a stark contrast.

However, the black light only flashed a few times before quickly fading away, but a hint of law fluctuations could still be detected from the black light before it vanished.

"Has someone refined a dao pill?" Xiao Jinhan murmured to himself.

A hint of surprise appeared on Xue Ying's face as she said, "There's no way that there would be a Dao Pill Master in a place as secluded as the Black Wind Sea. Could it be someone from the Vast Flow Palace or the Dawn Fall Sect? But why would they refine a dao pill at a time like this?"

"I don't have an answer to that. Perhaps they're trying to use some type of alternative method to find the entrance of the immortal manor," Xiao Jinhan speculated.

He then flipped a hand over to stow the white jade plate away before making his way toward a giant blue gate of light not far in front of him.

The gate was over 1,000 feet in size with countless antiquated patterns engraved onto its frame, and it was radiating dazzling blue light.

The light at the center of the gate was even brighter, and it resembled flowing water, forming a blue vortex.

Occasionally, the blue light at the center of the gate would abruptly brighten before spreading outward, and there were nine giant white jade pillars standing around the gate of light, with each one riddled with profound engravings.

The ground surrounding the nine pillars were also covered in complex patterns, forming an enormous array, and at the top of each pillar sat a cultivator with their legs crossed.

The three dao lords led by Ouyang Kuishan were among them, and they were chanting a collective incantation.

Radiant white light was surging out of the jade pillars and the array, forming a thick white light barrier that encompassed the entire gate of light.

With each eruption of blue light, the white light barrier would shudder violently, as would the nine surrounding jade pillars and the cultivators seated atop them.

"The closer we get to the emergence of the immortal manor, the more powerful the tremors will become, so make sure to be on your guard and don't slip up at this crucial juncture," Xiao Jinhan instructed.

"Rest assured, Palace Master, we've made extensive preparations for this, and we'll make sure that nothing goes wrong," Xue Ying replied in a confident manner.

"On top of that, keep a closer eye on Ouyang Kuishan and the other dao lords. Make sure that they're not slacking off," Xiao Jinhan said.

"They wouldn't dare," Xue Ying replied with a cold smile. "Besides, now that we're already here, they have no choice but to comply."

Xiao Jinhan nodded in response, then asked, "How are things going outside?"

"The people of the Dawn Fall Sect and the Vast Flow Palace are still searching frantically for us like headless chickens, but they haven't made any progress," Xue Ying reported with immense schadenfreude in her voice.

A pleased smile appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face upon hearing this, following which he said, "They're not a major concern of ours. What are the people of the Reincarnation Palace up to?"

"The people of the Reincarnation Palace remain as secretive as ever, but even if they discover the outermost restrictions, if they try to break through those restrictions by force, the trap that we set up would be activated.

“It may not be able to wipe them all out, but it'll be sure to pose them a great deal of trouble, and even if they can break through, it'll take them at least a year or so, by which time the entrance of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor would've already closed long ago," Xue Ying replied with a smile.

Xiao Jinhan gave a pleased nod in response, then cast his gaze toward the blue gate of light with a look of yearning in his eyes.

Right at this moment, a burst of white light suddenly emerged on the body of a nearby white-robed cultivator.

This was none other than the man with the Feng surname who had arrived in the Black Wind Sea in advance, and a hint of surprise appeared on his face as he flipped a hand over to summon a white array plate.

A small line of text appeared on the array plate, and his expression instantly changed drastically after taking a glance.

He hurriedly made his way toward Xiao Jinhan as he declared, "We have bad news, Palace Master!"

……

Arcs of golden lightning sprang out of thin air in the sky near Dark Veil Island, following which a golden lightning array took shape.

Han Li appeared within the array before inspecting his surroundings while also releasing his spiritual sense, and only after confirming that the nearby area was safe did he flip a hand over to produce a jade box, which contained the Origin Void Pill.

Even though he had previously successfully refined this pill, he was still only able to refine a single one after using up all of the remaining batches of ingredients.

A thoughtful look appeared in his eyes as he inspected the Origin Void Pill in his hand.

Through this pill refinement, Han Li had gained a deeper understanding of the pill. It was very similar to a dao pill, but its intended purpose seemed to be different.

However, he had no idea what its exact purpose was supposed to be.

He inspected the pill for a while longer before stowing it away, then cast his gaze forward with slightly furrowed brows.

Another half a year had passed by without any updates from Daoist Hu Yan, and he couldn't help but wonder if something had gone wrong.

Han Li was silent for a moment before flipping a hand over to produce the crimson communication array plate, then cast an incantation seal into it, and a crimson array immediately emerged.

He communicated a message into the array, but even after a long wait, there was still no response from Daoist Hu Yan.

Han Li's brows became tightly furrowed upon seeing this.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flew into the sea while putting on his Transient Guild mask.

If something really had gone wrong with the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, there should be some information on the subject being exchanged in the Transient Guild.

As soon as he put on his Transient Guild, Han Li was immediately rooted to the spot.

At the moment, the information exchange section of the Transient Guild was in a state of complete pandemonium, and he hurriedly began to read through the pieces of information being released..

During these past few years, he had either been busy refining his Heavy Water True Axis or refining his Origin Void Pill, so he hadn't kept up to date with the latest information on the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor.

It seemed that the entrance of the immortal manor still hadn't appeared during the past three years, and all of the powers were searching frantically for it.

However, the reason why the Transient Guild had been stirred up into such a frenzy was due to the release of a certain piece of information.

"The entrance of the immortal manor is under Red Moon Island."

It was unclear whether this information was actually accurate, but it had created a massive stir in the Transient Guild, nonetheless.

"Red Moon Island..." Han Li murmured to himself.

This was a very familiar place to him. Was the entrance of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor really situated under that island?

A contemplative look appeared on his face as he flipped a hand over to summon the Hard Ink Crystal that had been given to him by the Pig Dolphin Beast.

It had found the crystal near Red Moon Island, and Wyrm 3 seemed to have been quite interested in it.

It seemed that all of the signs were pointing to Red Moon Island.

Perhaps it really is true...

Chapter 400: Assembly

Right at this moment, the communication array beside Han Li suddenly lit up, following which a crimson projection of Daoist Hu Yan appeared, and it declared, "Fellow Daoist Li, come meet us at Sea Fig Island right away."

This was the exact same island that all of the Transient Guild members had been instructed to assemble at prior to carrying out the mission on Red Moon Island.

"Sea Fig Island... Could it be that the entrance of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor really is beneath Red Moon Island?"

"It sounds like you've also seen that piece of information circulating in the guild. The news is most likely true, so come and meet up with us right now," Daoist Hu Yan urged.

"Alright, I'll set off right away," Han Li replied with a nod, then concluded the communication and stowed the communication array plate away before flying toward the surface of the sea.

Moments later, a streak of azure light emerged from the sea, then flew away into the distance.

……

Elsewhere in the Black Wind Sea, all of the Vast Flow Palace's cultivators were traveling on a large blue flying boat.

"Red Moon Island... Its location isn't very secluded, nor is it close to the center of the Black Wind Sea, so it can be easily missed," Luo Qinghai murmured to himself with a contemplative expression as he stood at the bow of the boat.

Hovering in front of him was a small blue light screen that depicted all of the islands littered throughout the Black Wind Sea.

At this moment, there were four people standing behind him, consisting of a middlea-ged man wearing a feathered hat, a young scholar with a fair complexion holding a blue feather fan, a quiet and serious-looking elderly man with a black beard, and a man wearing a conical bamboo hat that was positioned very low to conceal his facial features.

What was particularly noteworthy was that the man in the conical bamboo hat was missing both of his arms.

As for the other Vast Flow Palace cultivators, including Nan Kemeng, they were all standing a bit further away.

"I did previously conduct a search on Red Moon Island, but at the time, I wasn't able to find anything. Perhaps I was too negligent," the young scholar said slightly furrowed brows.

"If the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace really did set up concealment restrictions well in advance, then it would be impossible to uncover the location of the entrance through conventional means, so don't blame yourself. I don't know who leaked this piece of information, but my intuition tells me that it's true," Luo Qinghai said.

A hint of excitement appeared on the young scholar's face upon hearing this, and the serious-looking elderly man also raised his head with a faint gleam in his eyes.

Even the conical bamboo hat of the armless man shifted ever so slightly, and all of the other Vast Flow Palace cultivators that were further away were also displaying reactions of excitement.

Luo Qinghai didn't say anything further as he made a hand seal, and the blue flying boat instantly sped up, flying onward as a giant blue shadow.

……

In the sky above another area of the Black Wind Sea, all of the Dawn Fall Sect cultivators were gathered together.

"Do you think this piece of information is true or not, Senior Martial Brother?" the Dawn Fall Sect Master asked as he turned to Feng Tiandu.

"There must be some truth to it. In any case, none of you have been able to find any leads thus far, so we may as well pursue this one," Feng Tiandu replied in an expressionless manner.

A slightly awkward look appeared on the Dawn Fall Sect Master's face as he said, "In our defense, the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace is clearly somehow concealing the entrance of the immortal manor, so..."

Before he had a chance to finish, Feng Tiandu swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a large black cloud that enveloped everyone before surging away into the distance, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

……

Hovering in mid-air above a lush island was the silver-robed woman by the name of Qu Ling.

She was wearing an azure mask that was projecting an azure light screen, and she was inspecting the light screen with a hint of a smile in her eyes.

Right at this moment, a ball of white light appeared on the distant horizon before rapidly approaching her, and Qu Ling took a glance in that direction, then removed the mask on her face before stowing it away.

Upon arriving above the island, the ball of white light faded to reveal the Xue Clan cultivators, and there were even more of them than last time.

"Fellow Daoist Qu, have you heard the rumor that the entrance of the immortal manor is located beneath Red Moon Island?" the square-faced elderly man asked with an excited expression.

"I have. That piece of news has caused quite a stir in the Transient Guild," Qu Ling replied with a nod.

"Do you think the news is reliable?" the square-faced elderly man asked.

"There are many people in the Transient Guild doubting the validity of this news, but no one has been able to present any concrete evidence against it, so there's a chance that it could be real. Regardless, we'll have to make a trip to Red Moon Island and take a look for ourselves," Qu Ling replied.

The square-faced elderly man nodded in response with a contemplative expression.

"I don't know much about this Red Moon Island," Qu Ling continued. "Your Xue Clan was once a local power of the Black Wind Sea, so I'm assuming you must know more than me about this island, Fellow Daoist Xue Shan."

"In the past, Red Moon Island wasn't all that renowned in the Black Wind Sea, and our Xue Clan left the Black Wind Sea tens of thousands of years ago, so I'm afraid I don't know much about the island, either. All I've heard is that the island master was quite a renowned and formidable Earthly Immortal, but for some reason, he was killed, and Red Moon Island has been left abandoned since then."

"I see..." Qu Ling mused as her eyes narrowed slightly in contemplation.

"Seeing as we've already decided to go to Red Moon Island, we should set off right away. If the entrance of the immortal manor really is there, then we have to strive to get there before anyone else," Xue Shan urged.

"Alright, let's go," Qu Ling replied with a nod.

Xue Shan immediately swept a sleeve through the air upon hearing this, releasing a burst of white light that enveloped all of the Xue Clan's cultivators, but before he had a chance to do anything else, a gentle breeze suddenly blew over his back, following which a burst of sharp pain speared through his lower abdomen.

He looked down to find a white snake head protruding out of his lower abdomen, and locked in the mouth of the snake was none other than his nascent soul.

Xue Shan's eyes immediately widened with incredulity.

Even though there wasn't much spiritual light radiating from his body, he was wearing a compact suit of spirit armor that he had refined over the course of hundreds of thousands of years, yet it wasn't able to pose any resistance against the white snake.

A burst of white flames shot out of the snake's mouth before striking the nascent soul, instantly freezing it solid.

Immediately thereafter, the white snake opened its mouth up wide to devour the frozen nascent soul before shooting back toward Qu Ling.

Xue Shan gave a muffled groan, and his body was turned around by the force of the white snake's withdrawal.

Standing behind him was Qu Ling with a cold look on her face and a large white snake wrapped around her body, flicking its forked tongue out in a menacing fashion.

"What the hell are you doing, you insane woman!"

"Patriarch..."

All of this had taken place so abruptly that only now did the Xue Clan cultivators realize that their patriarch had been attacked, and all of them immediately flared up with rage, releasing a vast array of spirit treasures in the blink of an eye, as if they were already prepared for something like this.

A cold sneer appeared on Qu Ling's face as she swept a sleeve through the air to release a ball of golden light, which transformed into a giant golden beetle that was several hundred feet in size to keep the barrage of oncoming spirit treasures at bay.

"Why..." Xue Shan asked with great difficulty as the vitality rapidly seeped out of his body.

"I only approached your Xue Clan as I wasn't familiar with the Black Wind Sea and required a guide. Now that the location of the immortal manor's entrance has been revealed, I no longer require your services," Qu Ling explained in a cold voice, then flicked a finger through the air, and a hole was instantly punched through Xue Shan's glabella.

The light in his eyes faded, and his lifeless body crumpled to the ground.

Qu Ling then cast her gaze toward the giant golden beetle, which was standing firm against the barrage of spirit treasures with ease, completely unscathed by the attacks.

However, it certainly didn't enjoy being attacked, and a furious look appeared in its eyes as it swept its two front legs through the air, releasing two translucent streaks of light that severed a pair of spirit treasures like a hot knife through butter.

All of the Xue Clan cultivators were astonished to see this.

"There's no way we can defeat her! We have to split up and run!" the long-faced man roared, then flew away as a streak of white light, doing so in such a hurry that he was even leaving his spirit treasures behind.

Everyone else immediately snapped back to their senses upon hearing this before also fleeing in different directions.

"None of you are getting away!" Qu Ling sneered as she flicked a finger through the air, and the golden beetle instantly lashed out with its two front legs once again, releasing two thick streaks of translucent light that were each over 100 feet in length.

The two streaks of light shuddered slightly, then split up into around a dozen smaller streaks of light that swept toward the Xue Clan cultivators at an astonishing speed, reaching them in the blink of an eye before slicing through their protective treasures and the protective spiritual light around their bodies with ease.

A string of agonized wails rang out as all of the Xue Clan cultivators were sliced to shreds along with their spirit treasures, and a faint smile appeared on Qu Ling's face as she swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of silver light, which swept up Xue Shan's body before dragging it toward her.

She inspected the body briefly, then stowed it away as she turned to the golden beetle with a smile and said, "Golden Immortals make for good sources of sustenance, but there's no need to hurry, the best delicacies are still yet to come."

After that, she withdrew the giant golden beetle as well before flying away as a streak of silver light.

Chapter 401: True Flame Sect

Several days later, on Sea Fig Island.

A streak of azure light approached the island from afar, then faded to reveal a burly male figure.

The man was none other than Han Li, but he had disguised himself as an unremarkable-looking middle-aged man with a dark complexion.

He hovered in mid-air in a still manner as he inspected his surroundings with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and right at this moment, an egg-shaped blue light barrier appeared over the island down below.

Immediately thereafter, an opening appeared in the light barrier, and before Han Li had a chance to do anything, a voice rang out from within the light barrier.

"Come in, Tianyu."

Han Li raised an eyebrow, then descended into the blue light barrier, following which the opening was instantly sealed, and the light barrier itself also vanished shortly thereafter.

There was a hemispherical space that was no more than 1,000 feet in size beneath the light barrier, and the air temperature was quite high.

Upon entering the space, Han Li was surprised to find a group of cultivators that were completely unfamiliar to him.

However, there was a black-robed elderly man who was looking at him with a smile, and standing beside him was a woman in a yellow dress.

It didn't take long for Han Li to figure out that these two were none other than Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, and just like him, they had also adopted disguises.

"Sorry to keep you waiting, Martial Uncle. I was delayed a little on the way here," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute while taking a glance at the other people present.

Standing behind Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni were nine cultivators dressed in fiery red Daoist robes, each with an extremely lifelike fire raven embroidered onto the sleeve, and it seemed that they were all from the same sect.

There was an unnatural flush on the faces of all nine cultivators, and they were also giving off formidable fire-attribute spiritual power fluctuations, indicating that they were all using fire-attribute cultivation arts.

The nine cultivators were led by a trio that consisted of an elderly man with red hair and a red beard, a physically-imposing, bare-chested man, and a middle-aged woman who appeared to be in her forties.

Their auras weren't as formidable as Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni's, but the three of them were clearly all Golden Immortals, and the elderly man's cultivation base was slightly more advanced than the other two.

"Come here, Tianyu. These are all fellow daoists from the Ancient Cloud Continent's True Flame Sect, and they'll be accompanying us into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor. This is Sect Master Xu Yangzi, and these two are Elder Zhen Yun and Elder Lu Lan. Fellow daoists, Tianyu is my nephew, and he's a very alert young man with a decent cultivation base, so he should be of some help to us in the immortal manor," Daoist Hu Yan introduced with a smile.

"Gu Tianyu pays his respects to the seniors of the True Flame Sect," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

He had heard of the True Flame Sect before.

On the Ancient Cloud Continent, it was considered to only be below the top three sects, and its members were particularly renowned for their mastery of fire-attribute cultivation arts. However, for some reason, its members very rarely left the sect, and they kept a rather low profile, so the sect wasn't as renowned as it should've been.

Xu Yangzi gave Han Li a slight nod, then turned back to Daoist Hu Yan as he asked, "Isn't it a little premature to be discussing what happens after we enter the immortal manor when we don't even know where the entrance is right now, Fellow Daoist Gu?"

As for the two elders, Zhen Yun and Lu Lan, both of them merely took a glance at Han Li before looking away.

Han Li wasn't bothered by this, and he made his way over to Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni before standing behind them.

"I'm sure the three of you must've already heard about that piece of news that was released in the Transient Guild. Perhaps the entrance of the immortal manor may not actually be there, but at the very least, we have a lead to pursue," Daoist Hu Yan replied with a faint smile.

"It's a great sign of trust that you approached us with the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting and offered to let us accompany you into the immortal manor. For that, we should be extremely grateful, but at this point, we've already searched through the entire Black Wind Sea without being able to find any leads, and there's no evidence to back up this piece of news, so I'm afraid I'm not very optimistic about its validity."

"While it's true that this piece of news is unsubstantiated up to this point, regardless of whether its true or not, we should still go and take a look on Red Moon Island," Yun Ni said.

"Pardon me for being blunt, but just like you said, no one knows if this piece of news is true or not, and there's a chance that someone intentionally spread this rumor and set up a trap on Red Moon Island for people to fall into. If that's the case, then we'd be making a grave error by going to the island," Zhen Yun said with a shake of his head.

Lu Lan's brows were tightly furrowed as she chimed in, "Exactly. There's a chance that this could be a trap set by none other than the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, so it's best to proceed with caution."

"The Infernal Frost Immortal Manor only emerges once every several tens of thousands of years, and in particular, someone discovered an entirely new area within it last time. There's a very good chance that this area holds High Zenith Pills, which are immensely beneficial to anyone attempting to reach the High Zenith Stage.

“Otherwise, the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace wouldn't have gone to such great lengths to conceal the entrance. This is an opportunity that'll perhaps never come around again. Are you really willing to just back down like this?" Daoist Hu Yan asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

Xu Yangzi's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he replied, "Well... I haven't made any concrete decisions yet, I'm just saying that we should proceed with caution and take our time to make a decision."

Zhen Yun and Lu Lan didn't say anything further, but it was clear that they were still rather doubtful about the situation.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

These Golden Immortals from the True Flame Sect were clearly tempted by the allure of the treasures in the immortal manor, but they weren't displaying any courage or decisiveness in this situation. If this was the personality of their sect master and elders, then it was no wonder that the sect had always kept such a low profile.

"I understand that you're concerned about the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace. It's true that if we run into them in the immortal palace, we'll be no match for them. However, ever since the Blaze Dragon Dao incident, there's been a great deal of discontent building against the Immortal Palace.

“According to my knowledge, many powers, including the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect, have been very displeased with the Immortal Palace's handling of the Blaze Dragon Dao situation and in particular, their concealment of the immortal manor's entrance.

“Essentially, they've made themselves public enemy number one, and I predict that all of those powers will definitely be sending people to Red Moon Island," Daoist Hu Yan said.

"If the entrance of the immortal manor really is below Red Moon Island, with everyone joining forces against the Immortal Palace, there's no way they'll be able to contend with all of us. Even if this is a trap, it'll be impossible for them to trap us all, so what do we have to fear?" Yun Ni added.

"What you're saying does make a lot of sense," Xu Yangzi mused as he stroked his own beard, seemingly tempted by what he was hearing, and the same applied to Zhen Yun and Lu Lan as well.

Even if they were to disregard the rumor that there were High Zenith Pills in the immortal manor, all of the other precious treasures inside were already extremely alluring to them.

"We don't have much time left, so you'll have to make a decision fast, fellow daoists. Are you really willing to just let this opportunity slip through your fingers?" Daoist Hu Yan asked.

A slightly conflicted look appeared in Xu Yangzi's eyes.

"Of course, we can't just go there recklessly. Instead, we have to establish a plan in advance," Daoist Hu Yan continued.

Han Li took a glance at the True Flame Sect cultivators, then smiled as he asked, "I'm sure you already have a plan prepared, right, Martial Uncle?"

Daoist Hu Yan merely smiled in response, then swept a sleeve through the air to remove the surrounding restriction.

After that, a ball of blue light flew out of his sleeve, then transformed into a blue flying carriage with a rather peculiar appearance. There was a cross-shaped windmill on both the front and the back of the carriage, and it was radiating dazzling light while also giving off formidable spiritual power fluctuations.

"This carriage is something that I obtained from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor many years ago, and it has an exceptional concealment effect, so we should be a lot safer if we take this carriage to Red Moon Island," Daoist Hu Yan said.

Han Li examined the carriage closely to find that it was refined from some special spirit materials, and there were countless complex and profound spirit patterns engraved onto its surface, giving off faint water law fluctuations.

Thanks to his Heavy Water True Axis, he was quite sensitive to water law fluctuations, and he could sense that the law fluctuations emanating from the carriage were more geared toward concealment.

Han Li decided to lead by example, flying onto the carriage before everyone else, while Xu Yangzi hesitated for a while longer before also doing the same.

The two elders and the other six True Immortal cultivators of the True Flame Sect quickly followed suit, flying onto the carriage as well.

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni exchanged a smile before also flying onto the carriage.

After landing on the carriage, Daoist Hu Yan made a hand seal, and a burst of misty blue light emerged to envelop the entire carriage, instantly concealing both its physical form and its aura, making it completely undetectable.

Chapter 402: Entrance

Immediately thereafter, the flying carriage descended into the sea down below at Daoist Hu Yan's behest.

Upon entering the sea, the blue light emanating from the carriage instantly completely fused as one with the surrounding seawater, and it was as if the carriage had become a part of the sea.

The carriage then shot forth through the water as a streak of light, while Xu Yangzi praised, "This flying carriage of yours is indeed extremely profound, Fellow Daoist Gu. It looks like the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor really does contain some exceptional treasures."

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist. If we can enter the immortal manor, I'm sure all of you will be able to reap some exceptional spoils," Daoist Hu Yan replied with a smile.

"I'm looking forward to it," Elder Zhen Yun said with a smile.

"Hopefully, the entrance of the immortal manor really is beneath Red Moon Island, and we manage to enter the immortal manor without any incident," Lu Lan said.

A faint smile appeared on Daoist Hu Yan's face, and he didn't speak any further as he gently stomped a foot down onto the flying carriage, upon which it accelerated even further.

The carriage was traveling rapidly through the water in a wraith-like manner, and it wasn't causing any physical disturbance or displacement of water.

The fish and the demon beasts in the sea continued to swim around and forage for food, completely oblivious to the carriage's passing.

Han Li was inspecting his surroundings, and he was also quite impressed with the carriage.

The craftsmanship of this carriage was exceptional, and the person who had refined it clearly had outstanding mastery over the laws of water as well, so it was indeed very safe taking this carriage through the sea.

However, judging from the immortal spiritual power fluctuations that it was giving off, it was most likely quite taxing on Immortal Origin Stones as well. It seemed that Daoist Hu Yan was making an investment here so that the True Flame Sect cultivators would be willing to accompany them.

Han Li looked around momentarily before sitting down with his legs crossed in a corner of the carriage, then closed his eyes to meditate.

As for the other True Immortals of the True Flame Sect, all of them also did the same after the excitement and novelty of the carriage wore off.

Sea Fig Island wasn't far away from Red Moon Island, and this carriage was extremely fast, so it only took them around two days to arrive at their destination.

Instead of directly reaching the island, the carriage stopped in the sea several hundred kilometers away.

Everyone on the carriage had already risen to their feet, and they were observing the enormous island up ahead in silence.

"I didn't think this island would be so massive. Even if that rumor is true, it won't be easy to find the entrance of the immortal manor on such a huge island," Daoist Hu Yan said as his brows furrowed slightly.

The Infernal Frost Scenic Painting wasn't going to help them in this situation, and in order to remain covert, they couldn't use their spiritual sense to search for the entrance, either.

Given those circumstances, searching such a huge island was indeed going to be quite a difficult task.

Xu Yangzi and the others were all looking at one another, and it was clear that they were also at a loss for how to proceed.

"Let's go around the island and search its border. Perhaps we'll be able to make some discoveries," Yun Ni suggested.

"I suppose that's better than nothing."

Daoist Hu Yan couldn't think of any better strategies, so he decided to adopt this idea, and the carriage set off once again at his behest.

Meanwhile, everyone was using their own covert abilities to scour the surrounding area.

Two beams of blue light that were several feet in length emerged from Han Li's eyes as he inspected his surroundings, and Xu Yangzi's brows instantly furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"Don't use your abilities recklesslessly! If you expose us, we'll all be in grave danger! Besides, with your paltry cultivation base, it's not like you'll be able to contribute anything anyway."

"I understand your concerns, Senior Xu Yangzi, but this is a spirit eye ability of mine that doesn't give off any aura, so you can rest assured," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Don't worry, Fellow Daoist Xu Yangzi. If Tianyu wants to help, then why don't we give him the opportunity?" Daoist Hu Yan said with a smile.

Xu Yangzi didn't say anything further upon hearing this, and Daoist Hu Yan gave Han Li a slight nod, indicating for him to continue.

With the speed of the blue flying carriage, they were quickly able to make it halfway around Red Moon Island, but no one had discovered anything.

Xu Yangzi's expression had darkened once again, and Zhen Yun and Lu Lan were also beginning to look rather uneasy.

Right at this moment, Han Li's expression changed slightly as he hurriedly said, "Please stop here for a moment, Martial Uncle."

Daoist Hu Yan raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and the flying carriage instantly drew to a halt at his behest.

At the same time, a layer of rippling blue light appeared over its surface, and it was once again indistinguishable from the seawater around it.

Mere moments later, a streak of light shot forth from afar from the left, then continued toward the seabed without pause, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

"That spirit eye ability of yours is quite impressive, Tianyu," Daoist Hu Yan praised.

"You're far too kind, Martial Uncle, I was only lucky to have been looking in the right direction," Han Li replied in a humble manner.

Xu Yangzi's eyelid twitched slightly, clearly feeling a little embarrassed to have been proven wrong like this, but he still cast his gaze toward the streak of light like everyone else.

"Perhaps the entrance is down there... Tianyu, can you see a little further?" Yun Ni asked.

Han Li took a deep breath as he channeled his Brightsight Spirit Eyes with all his might, but unfortunately, the sea here was too deep for him to see the bottom, and he could only turn to Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni with a resigned shake of his head.

"We've already come here, so some degree of risk is unavoidable. I think we should go down and have a look," Daoist Hu Yan suggested after some contemplation.

Yun Ni nodded in agreement, and Han Li naturally offered no objections, either.

"What do you think, Fellow Daoist Xu Yangzi?" Daoist Hu Yan asked as he turned to Xu Yangzi's trio.

The three of them exchanged a glance, following which Xu Yangzi also nodded in agreement with this proposed course of action.

With that, Daoist Hu Yan made a hand seal, and the blue flying carriage swiveled around before descending toward the seabed.

The sea here was extremely deep, and even after flying for a long while, the flying carriage still hadn't reached the seabed.

Furthermore, there were countless deep rifts and trenches on the seabed here, presenting a very complex terrain that resembled a mountain range.

A hesitant look appeared on Daoist Hu Yan's face, and he was no longer able to sense where the streak of light had gone.

He exchanged a glance with Yun Ni, in response to which she gave a shake of her head.

He then turned to Xu Yangzi's trio with an inquisitive expression, but it was clear that they were just as lost as he was.

"He went down that trench, Martial Uncle," Han Li said as he pointed at a giant trench not far away.

An elated look immediately appeared on Daoist Hu Yan's face and he asked, "What is this spirit eye ability of yours? How is it able to allow you to see so far?"

At the same time, he was making a string of hand seals, and the blue flying carriage immediately flew toward the trench that Han Li was pointing at.

"You think far too highly of me, Martial Uncle. There's no way my spirit eyes can see that far, it's just that the ability allows me to see spiritual power fluctuations, and I was able to see some of the traces that person left behind," Han Li explained with a smile.

At his current cultivation base, he was able to see faint spiritual power traces even without combining his Brightsight Spirit Eyes with his Law Destruction Eye.

"Even so, it's quite remarkable that your spirit eye ability was able to detect such faint spiritual power traces," Yun Ni praised.

Xu Yangzi's trio was also forced to re-evaluate Han Li upon hearing this, and Han Li merely gave them a modest smile in response.

At this point, the flying carriage had already flown deep into the trench.

The terrain here was also extremely complex, without countless tunnels and passageways that led to unknown places.

These passageways seemed to have been formed naturally, but it was unclear how they had arisen.

A peculiar look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

During the Gongshu Hong assassination mission, he had remained on the island the entire time, so he was unaware of the complexities present beneath the island.

Han Li continued to work with Daoist Hu Yan, with the former using his spirit eye ability to follow the spiritual power traces, while the latter controlled the flying carriage.

Some places that they had to pass through were quite narrow, only several feet wide, but the carriage was able to expand or shrink at will, and all of the cultivators onboard were also able to manipulate their own bodies through various means, so this was no obstacle for them.

Close to an hour passed by in the blink of an eye, and the blue flying carriage continued to traverse slowly through the water.

The rock tunnels on the seabed were blue in color, resembling ice crystals, and they were giving off wisps of spiritual qi, indicating that they were similar in constitution to some spirit materials.

It was extremely dark this deep in the sea, and the only source of light came from the faint blue radiance emanating from the rock tunnels.

Han Li continued to inspect his surroundings with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and at this point, he could detect many spiritual power traces, as if many people had come here before.

He immediately revealed this observation to Daoist Hu Yan and the others, and everyone was elated to hear this.

The fact that so many people had recently passed through this area indicated there was a very good chance that the entrance of the immortal manor was up ahead.

Daoist Hu Yan remained patient as he continued to slowly advance the flying carriage through the water, and after traveling for a while longer, bursts of rumbling suddenly began to ring out up ahead, as if there were a battle taking place.

Everyone was even more encouraged upon seeing this.

"It should be just up ahead!"

"Looks like that piece of news was true, after all."

"Don't let your guard down, everyone. We still can't be sure yet, so let's not get complacent," Daoist Hu Yan cautioned as he made a hand seal, and the flying carriage accelerated slightly.

Chapter 403: Seal

As the flying carriage continued onward, the rumbling up ahead grew louder and louder, and all of the nearby seawater was also churning incessantly.

At the same time, the rock tunnels were beginning to tremble, and chunks of rocks of different sizes were occasionally clattering down from above.

Lights of different colors were flashing through the space up ahead, and at the same time, bursts of spiritual sense were sweeping forth from all directions in a blatant fashion, making no attempt at subtlety and secrecy.

This was certainly not something that Han Li and the others had expected to see.

The flying carriage continued onward, reaching the end of the rock tunnel in the blink of an eye.

Up ahead was an enormous underground cave, the roof of which was riddled with countless blue stalactites, and it seemed that this was a naturally forming karst cave that was several dozen kilometers in size.

At this moment, there were also dozens of cultivators gathered in the cave, all of whom were viciously bombarding a certain part of the cave with attacks.

They were collectively attacking a dense black light barrier, beyond which one could just barely make out the entrance of a cave. There were some cultivators standing deep within the opening of the cave, but it was impossible to see them clearly due to the black light barrier in the way.

One spirit treasure after another crashed into the black light barrier, causing it to shudder incessantly, and it was unclear whether this cave had been artificially fortified or if it was this resilient to begin with, but it remained completely unscathed despite the powerful shockwaves released by the barrage of attacks.

"How dare you seal the entrance of the immortal manor!"

"The Infernal Frost Immortal Manor doesn't belong to your Northern Glacial Immortal Palace! Remove these restrictions right now!"

Some of the cultivators were yelling to vent their fury as they continued to rain down attacks upon the black light barrier.

Han Li and the others were ecstatic to see this, and Daoist Hu Yan flipped a hand over to produce the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting.

As soon as the painting was summoned, the blue light radiating from it instantly brightened before pointing in the direction of the black light barrier. Due to the restrictions, it seemed that the painting was only able to detect the entrance of the immortal manor from very close proximity.

"It looks like the entrance of the immortal manor really is here!" Daoist Hu Yan said as he stowed his Infernal Frost Scenic Painting away, then cast a fervent gaze toward the black light barrier, and Xu Yangzi and the others were also looking very excited.

Han Li was also quite elated, but not as much as the others, and he quickly calmed down before turning his attention to the other cultivators in the cave.

There were 34 cultivators present, all of whom were at or above the True Immortal Stage.

They were dressed in different attire and split up into three factions, the most eye-catching one of which was situated at the edge of the cave.

The group consisted of around a dozen blue-robed cultivators, led by a benevolent-looking middle-aged man.

This man was none other than the master of the Vast Flow Palace, Luo Qinghai.

As for the people standing beside Luo Qinghai, Han Li had no recollection of any of them aside from an effeminate young man.

The Vast Flow Palace cultivators were the most formidable faction of the three, with four mid-Golden Immortal cultivators alongside Luo Qinghai, who was at the late-Golden Immortal Stage.

In the face of such a formidable lineup, Han Li's group was completely outmatched.

On top of that, the majority of the rest of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators were at the late-True Immortal Stage.

After taking a brief glance at the Vast Flow Palace cultivators, Han Li turned his attention to the other two factions, one of which was dressed in black robes, each of which had a skull design embroidered onto the chest.

This group also consisted of around a dozen cultivators, led by an elderly man with pockmarks all over his face, a petite young woman whose features were concealed behind a veil, and two other men, one tall and one short.

The pockmark-faced elderly man wore a vicious expression as he glowered at his surroundings, while the veiled young woman's entire body was enveloped within rings of translucent azure light.

As for the other two men, the taller one was over 20 feet in height and had an extremely imposing physique, giving him the appearance of an impregnable fortress on legs.

The shorter of the two was less than five feet tall with stubby arms and legs that gave him a rather comical appearance, but he possessed an extremely solid physique, much like an iron weight.

Despite the enormous disparity in the statures of the two men, their facial features were very similar in appearance, and it seemed that they were brothers.

All four of them were Golden Immortals, with the pockmark-faced elderly man at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, while the other three were at the early-Golden Immortal Stage, and the rest of the group were naturally all True Immortals.

The final group had a similar number of people to the other two factions, and they were all dressed in very strange attire. Regardless of whether they were male or female, all of them were wearing short vests with black bandanas around their heads. Furthermore, it seemed that they were not of the human race.

There were four Golden Immortals among them as well, namely an elderly man with a dark complexion, an elderly woman with freckled skin, and a pair of physically-imposing men with blank and wooden expressions, as if they were puppets.

The four of them were holding a golden cane each, all of which were riddled with peculiar golden patterns while also giving off formidable auras that were resonating with one another.

At this moment, the latter two factions in the cave were attacking the black light barrier, while the Vast Flow Palace cultivators were merely observing as bystanders.

Meanwhile, Luo Qinghai was occasionally glancing down into the underground space beneath the cave entrance, seemingly waiting for something.

After their initial excitement, Daoist Hu Yan and the others gradually calmed down after assessing the situation.

Xu Yangzi hesitated momentarily, then asked in a quiet voice, "Should we reveal ourselves now or continue observing like this?"

"Seeing as there aren't any traps here, I think we should reveal ourselves. Otherwise, if we're somehow discovered, that would put us in a bad light. Having said that, this is not the right place to be revealing ourselves," Daoist Hu Yan replied, following which the blue flying carriage beneath his feet flew back a little through the rock tunnel at his behest.

Immediately thereafter, he made a hand seal, and the carriage rapidly shrank down before flying back up his sleeve, thereby revealing everyone.

"Let's go."

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni led the way forward, and Xu Yangzi and the others immediately followed along.

As soon as they re-entered the cave, everyone's attention was immediately drawn to them, including several pairs of eyes in the underground space beneath the black light barrier.

Luo Qinghai took a glance at Han Li's group, following which a hint of disappointment flashed through his eyes, and he quickly averted his gaze.

The other two factions temporarily ceased in their attacks before turning to Han Li's group as well.

Meanwhile, Daoist Hu Yan and the others feigned surprised expressions and stopped not far away from everyone else.

The pockmark-faced man put on a hideous smile as he approached Han Li's group, and after taking a glance at Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, he greeted, "I didn't expect to see you here, Fellow Daoist Xu Yangzi. Who are these two fellow daoists? I don't recall ever meeting them before."

As for Han Li, he was just a True Immortal, so he naturally didn't attract much attention from the elderly man.

All of the other black-robed cultivators also approached Han Li and the others behind the pockmark-faced elderly man.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Chen. These two are good friends of our True Flame Sect, and they've come to explore this Infernal Frost Immortal Manor with us. Fellow Daoist Gu, this is Sect Master Chen Pi of the Ghost Wail Sect," Xu Yangzi introduced.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this. The Ghost Wail Sect was a sect on the Ancient Cloud Continent that was comparable in power to the True Flame Sect.

Its members were proficient in all types of ghostly and devilish cultivation arts, and they had a notorious reputation, often killing others to take their souls for the sake of cultivating certain ghostly abilities and even going as far as to completely slaughter some smaller sects, for which they had always been frowned upon by the Blaze Dragon Dao.

However, the sect was situated very far away from the Blaze Dragon Dao, so as long as they didn't do anything to harm the Blaze Dragon Dao's interests, there was naturally no incentive for the Blaze Dragon Dao to target them.

"I've heard much about the Ghost Wail Sect. My name is Gu Yan, and this is my Junior Martial Sister, Gu Ni. Both of us are itinerant cultivators," Daoist Hu Yan said with a smile, while Yun Ni merely nodded at the Ghost Wail Sect cultivators in silence.

"It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, fellow daoists," Chen Pi said.

He seemed to be eager to recruit Xu Yangzi, Daoist Hu Yan, and the others as allies, and the feeling was very much mutual, so the two sides quickly struck up a pleasant conversation.

As for the group of foreign race cultivators, they remained standing on the spot in silence, displaying no intention of approaching Han Li's group.

"Could it be that the entrance of the immortal manor is in there?" Xu Yangzi asked as he cast his gaze toward the cave beneath the black light barrier.

"That's right. The people from the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace are all in there, and they've set up a restriction to seal the entrance so that they can keep it to themselves! Other people may be scared of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, but I'm certainly not scared!

“You came at just the right time, Fellow Daoist Xu Yangzi. Our three factions should work together to blow this restriction open and give the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace what they deserve!" Chen Pi said with a cold smile.

"Three factions? Are you counting in those people over there?" Daoist Hu Yan asked as he cast his gaze toward the foreign race cultivators.

"Precisely. They're cultivators of the Southern Dawn Race from the westernmost border of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. They don't mean any disrespect, they simply don't like to interact with people outside of their own race," Chen Pi explained.

Daoist Hu Yan wasn't bothered at all.

All races were generally quite apprehensive toward those of other races.

However, as long as there wasn't any animosity beyond that, Daoist Hu Yan certainly wasn't opposed to working with those Southern Dawn beings.

Chapter 404: Impasse

"Truth be told, I've already communicated with them earlier, and they're also very unhappy with what the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace has done here, so they'll definitely be receptive to the idea of forming a temporary alliance with us. The restriction set up by the Immortal Palace is very resilient, but if we can get 10 Golden Immortals attacking the same spot on it at once, we'll surely be able to break through it," Chen Pi said.

Xu Yangzi's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to Daoist Hu Yan for a verdict.

A hint of surprise flashed through Chen Pi's eyes upon seeing this, and he was forced to reassess the status of Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni in the group.

"The Vast Flow Palace cultivators are also here, why haven't you joined forces with them to break this restriction?" Daoist Hu Yan asked.

"They're a major sect that has no eyes for other sects and races beneath them, so they're naturally unwilling to work with us," Chen Pi replied with a resigned expression.

Daoist Hu Yan was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of gentle light that instantly formed a light barrier, encompassing the surrounding area within a radius of over 100 feet.

After setting up the light barrier, Daoist Hu Yan said, "Sect Master Chen, in my opinion, it's best for us not to break this restriction for now."

Chen Pi's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. "Oh? Why do you say that, Fellow Daoist Gu?"

"The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace's actions have already incurred widespread outrage from all of the powers that have gathered in the Black Wind Sea in search for the immortal manor. If our three factions join forces to break the restriction now, that'll be sure to pit us in a direct conflict against the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and even if we can keep them at bay, we'll only be benefiting others," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

A contemplative look appeared on Chen Pi's face upon hearing this.

"I think that we should take a more patient approach. There's still some time until the opening of the immortal manor, and the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators won't be able to simultaneously enter the immortal manor while also defending the restriction here.

“The location of the immortal manor's entrance was leaked quite some time ago, so it's only a matter of time before all of the powers assemble. Once that happens, surely the Immortal Palace wouldn't dare to continue to oppose everyone," Daoist Hu Yan continued.

"Fellow Daoist Gu is right. This is not the right time to be breaking the restriction, and the Vast Flow Palace cultivators are most likely hanging back precisely for this reason. They would be ecstatic to see us engage in a direct battle against the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators while they look on from the sidelines. Luo Qinghai is a sly old fox, and this is what he likes to do best," Xu Yangzi chimed in with a nod.

Chen Pi's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this. "That's a good plan, Fellow Daoist Gu. It seems I was too eager to strike. I was so infuriated by the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace's actions that I was determined to foil their plans, even if it meant that I lost the chance to enter the immortal manor myself, but it appears there's no reason to make such a sacrifice."

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Chen," Daoist Hu Yan replied in a modest manner.

Chen Pi and Daoist Hu Yan chatted for a while longer before the former departed and flew back to the group of Southern Dawn beings, where he began communicating with the four Golden Immortals.

The pair of imposing men displayed no reaction to what they were being told, but the elderly man and the elderly woman's expressions changed slightly upon hearing what Chen Pi had to say.

The two of them then nodded in agreement with Daoist Hu Yan's proposed course of action, and they refrained from continuing in their assault on the black light barrier.

All of a sudden, it had become very peaceful in the cave.

Luo Qinghai took a glance at Daoist Hu Yan as a peculiar look flashed through his eyes.

"It looks like someone with an ounce of intelligence has finally arrived, Palace Master," the fair-skinned scholar remarked as he approached Luo Qinghai.

Even though Daoist Hu Yan had just set up a restriction to prevent others from eavesdropping on their conversation, it was very apparent what had just transpired.

"This is not a bad development. It may not necessarily benefit us for them to recklessly break the restriction, so let's just continue waiting and observing," Luo Qinghai said in a contemplative manner.

"Indeed, Palace Master. It would be best to wait for everyone to arrive and force Xiao Jinhan to remove the restriction," the fair-skinned scholar said.

Luo Qinghai merely smiled in response.

……

Behind the black light barrier was a cave, which led into a spacious area, one in which all of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators were situated.

At this point, the cultivators on the stone pillars had already stopped what they were doing and flown down from the pillars.

However, the array was still functioning to encompass the gate of light.

Aside from them, there were also some cultivators dressed in Black Wind Island attire, including Lu Jun, Lu Yuqing, and several of the Black Wind Island elders.

At this moment, everyone was standing with their heads lowered, not daring to make even the slightest sound. Meanwhile, Xiao Jinhan was glowering at everyone with a furious expression, and there was a cloud of black mist swirling around his body, giving off a fearsome aura of malice.

"Who can explain to me what's happened here? How was the location of the immortal manor suddenly leaked without any explanation?" Xiao Jinhan asked in a cold voice.

None of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators could offer a response.

Xiao Jinhan turned his gaze to Deputy Palace Master Xue Ying.

Xue Ying hesitated momentarily, then said, "All of the people who are aware of the entrance's location are gathered here right now, and the restriction set up cuts off all communication with the outside world, so there shouldn't be any way for the information to have been leaked."

"Then why don't you explain to me how those people have shown up outside?" Xiao Jinhan demanded as he turned to Xue Ying with a sharp gaze.

Xue Ying's complexion instantly paled slightly, and she was at a loss for how to respond.

"This is the one task that I assigned to all of you, yet you've still managed to make a complete mess of things!" Xiao Jinhan spat in a cold voice.

After a tense silence, Lu Yue said in a feeble voice, "I believe that there are only two possible explanations, Palace Master."

"Go ahead," Xiao Jinhan prompted.

"The first possibility is that one of us leaked this information," Lu Yue said.

A cold gleam flashed through Xiao Jinhan's eyes upon hearing this.

"That's impossible! All of the cultivators of our Northern Glacial Immortal Palace that were sent here are absolutely loyal and trustworthy. On top of that, even Golden Immortals like you and I are unable to send any information to the outside world through the restrictions here," Xue Ying immediately objected with furrowed brows.

"I'm also certain that everyone here is reliable and trustworthy, so there's only a very slim chance of this being the case," Lu Yue said.

"What's the other possibility?" Xiao Jinhan asked.

"The second possible explanation is that the Reincarnation Palace already discovered the entrance of the immortal manor well in advance, and they were the ones who leaked this information," Lu Yue replied.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon hearing this, while Xiao Jinhan's brows furrowed slightly in contemplation.

The black mist swirling around his body slowly dissipated, and the menacing aura in the air also faded, much to the relief of everyone else.

"We've been able to lead the Reincarnation Palace on one wild goose chase after another, pursuing a series of false entrances, but now that I think about it, things may have gone a little smoothly. The Reincarnation Palace has been able to contend with our Immortal Palace for many years, so they shouldn't be this incapable.

“I think they must've already seen through our intentions, and they've only been pretending to fall for our ploys in order to lure us into a false sense of security," Lu Yue continued.

Everyone immediately began to discuss this theory.

"Be quiet!" Xiao Jinhan yelled, and everyone instantly fell silent again.

"Regardless of exactly what happened, there's no use in speculating now. Keep doing what you need to do, and I'll deal with the rest," Xiao Jinhan said in an indifferent voice, having calmed down again.

With that, everyone returned to their original posts, including Ouyang Kuishan and the dao lords, who returned to the tops of their respective stone pillars.

A few people also made their way over to the black restriction at the entrance of the cave before sitting down with their legs crossed.

Meanwhile, Xiao Jinhan cast his gaze outward with a cold look in his eyes, and it was unclear what he was contemplating.

……

Meanwhile, the cave outside was completely silent.

Han Li was observing everyone as he stood behind Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

Wyrm 3's objective was also the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, so perhaps they had already arrived here. However, it was impossible to tell as all of the Reincarnation Palace cultivators also had Transient Guild masks that could conceal their appearances and auras.

He was inspecting everyone in the cave closely, trying to spot some telltale signs, but his efforts proved to be futile.

Right at this moment, Han Li's expression suddenly changed slightly as he cast his gaze outside, and a hint of foreboding suddenly welled up in his heart.

Daoist Hu Yan noticed the change in Han Li's expression, and he asked through voice transmission, "What is it?"

"I think someone else is coming," Han Li replied.

Daoist Hu Yan cast his gaze toward the entrance of the cave upon hearing this, just in time to see a silver-robed woman appear amid a flash of silver light.

The woman took an expressionless glance at everyone else in the cave, then slowly made his way inside.

Her arrival created a small stir among everyone in the cave, and even Luo Qinghai's eyes narrowed ever so slightly at the sight of her arrival.

Chapter 405: Assembled

A hint of wariness flashed through Han Li's eyes as he observed the woman.

Even with his tremendous spiritual sense, he was unable to detect her cultivation base, and he had only ever experienced this with Xiao Jinhan and Baili Yan. Not even Luo Qinghai had been so unfathomable in his eyes.

He observed the woman for a while longer, then closed his eyes to meditate.

The woman was none other than Qu Ling, and there was a small golden pouch hanging from her waist.

The pouch was glowing with spiritual light, and there were several peculiar patterns on its surface, giving off a burst of law fluctuations.

Right at this moment, the pouch twitched ever so slightly, and Qu Ling's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this as she brushed a hand over the pouch in a subtle fashion.

A ball of silver light appeared over the palm of her hand before quickly vanishing into the pouch, upon which it fell still again.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes sprang open as a hint of shock flashed across his face, and he hurriedly lowered his head to conceal his expression.

Right at this moment, Qu Ling raised her head as she swept her gaze across everyone in the cave.

At this moment, everyone was also observing her, and as soon as anyone's gaze met hers, they immediately felt a sharp pain in their eyes, as if they had been pricked by a needle.

Most of the people present hurriedly withdrew their gaze, and some with lesser cultivation bases couldn't help but give muffled groans, as if they had suffered some internal injuries.

Some of the Golden Immortals present were rather displeased to see this, but they didn't say anything.

Luo Qinghai's brows furrowed slightly, and he said, "I wasn't expecting to see you here, Fellow Daoist Qu Ling."

Just now, two of the Vast Flow Palace's True Immortals had suffered some internal injuries from their brief eye contact with Qu Ling, and this was not good news for their imminent venture into the immortal manor.

"You're constantly in seclusion, yet even you've come here, so why can't I be here?" Qu Ling countered as she took an indifferent glance at Luo Qinghai.

"The Infernal Frost Immortal Manor doesn't belong to our Vast Flow Palace, so of course you're free to come her as you please, but isn't it rather unbefitting for someone of your status to be intimidating these juniors?" Luo Qinghai asked with a faint smile.

"If you keep these juniors in check so that they don't go around gawking at others like idiots, perhaps I wouldn't have to discipline them in your stead," Qu Ling replied with a cold sneer.

The other Golden Immortals of the Vast Flow Palace immediately flared up with rage, yet Luo Qinghai raised a hand to stop them before they could say anything.

"You're right, Fellow Daoist Qu, these juniors were indeed at fault for being so rude. It seems like you've advanced even further in your cultivation since we last met. I must admit that I'm very impressed," Luo Qinghai said with a faint smile.

Qu Ling offered no response, taking a glance at the black restriction before finding a place to stand in the cave.

Luo Qinghai was completely unbothered by this, and his smile remained unchanged as he averted his gaze in a calm manner.

"Who is this woman, Senior Hu Yan? It seems like even Luo Qinghai doesn't dare to provoke her," Han Li inquired through voice transmission.

"Her name is Qu Ling, and she’s quite an enigmatic figure, but she's also very renowned in this immortal region. She already reached the late-Golden Immortal Stage over 100,000 years ago, and it seems that her cultivation base has advanced even further since then," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon hearing this.

"Despite her lofty cultivation base, what's actually most fearsome about her is the vast array of spirit beasts and spirit insects in her possession. On top of that, she has a very cruel and unpredictable personality, and even the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace wouldn't want to make an enemy out of her. If you run into her in the immortal manor, then make sure to stay away, and do not provoke her no matter what you do," Daoist Hu Yan continued.

"I'll be sure to keep that in mind," Han Li replied.

Half a day passed by in the blink of an eye, and some of the people in the hall were beginning to grow rather agitated again, particularly the cultivators of the Ghost Wail Sect.

Chen Pi's gaze was flashing back and forth between the entrance of the cave and the black light barrier, and right at this moment, an ecstatic look appeared on Chen Pi's faces as another group of cultivators arrived.

They were none other than the cultivators of the Dawn Fall Sect, led by their sect master and Feng Tiandu.

"Welcome, Elder Feng, Sect Master Qi. I've already been waiting here for you for quite some time," Luo Qinghai greeted with a warm smile.

"You arrived quite early, Palace Luo, and you've brought with you quite a formidable entourage. It looks like you're determined to get your hands on some precious treasures in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor," the Dawn Fall Sect Master remarked.

"I wouldn't even dare to consider competing against the two of you. I've only brought these juniors with me on this occasion to broaden their horizons, so rest assured, you won't be facing any competition from me," Luo Qinghai replied with a smile.

"You're still as modest as ever, Grand Palace Master Luo," the Dawn Fall Sect Master chuckled, clearly completely unconvinced by Luo Qinghai's words.

Meanwhile, Feng Tiandu remained silent as he swept his gaze across everyone else in the hall. He had changed into a clean gray robe, and he was still zombie-like in appearance, but he already appeared far more normal than before, and the chains around his body had also disappeared.

All of a sudden, his gaze fell upon none other than Qu Ling.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Qu," Feng Tiandu said with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

Qu Ling merely nodded in response.

Han Li was quite taken aback to see this.

Qu Ling had displayed a great deal of arrogance to everyone else in the cave, including even Luo Qinghai, yet she was far more restrained in the face of Feng Tiandu.

Having said that, it seemed that this was for good reason as Feng Tiandu's cultivation base felt just as unfathomable as Qu Ling's to Han Li.

"Senior Hu Yan, are these people from the Dawn Fall Sect?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"That's right. The man with the scar on his face is the sect master, Qi Tianxiao. He's always kept a low profile, so he's not all that renowned. The one standing beside him is Feng Tiandu, the grand elder of the Dawn Fall Sect, and he's a much more renowned figure in our Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

“Feng Tiandu, Dao Lord Baili, and Xiao Jinhan are considered to be the three most formidable Golden Immortals of our Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but for some reason, he went into seclusion tens of thousands of years ago and hasn't come out since then, but it seems that he's finally come out of seclusion for this occasion," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

He was carefully observing Feng Tiandu, and for some reason, he felt a sense of familiarity in Feng Tiandu, as if he had seen him somewhere before.

Right at this moment, Feng Tiandu seemed to have sensed Han Li's gaze, and he turned to look at Han Li.

Their eyes met, and Han Li instantly felt a chill run down his spine. He felt as if Feng Tiandu were seeing right through him, laying him completely bare and exposed.

Han Li hurriedly averted his gaze, while Feng Tiandu observed Han Li for a while longer with a peculiar look in his eyes before also looking away, turning his attention to the black restriction in the cave.

"Are the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators in there right now, Grand Palace Master Luo?" Feng Tiandu asked.

"That's right," Luo Qinghai replied with a nod.

Feng Tiandu observed the black light barrier for a moment, then raised a hand, and a streak of black light shot out of the palm of his hand like an arrow before striking the black light barrier in a flash.

The streak of light wasn't remarkable in appearance at all, and it wasn't even all that bright, but the impact caused the black light barrier to shudder violently, sending ripples surging over its surface.

Countless specks of black light appeared on the light barrier to form a nine-grid array, and a burst of peculiar force emerged, quickly settling the ripples on the light barrier.

"This is the Nine Heavens Profound Array. Looks like Xiao Jinhan is indeed responsible for this," Feng Tiandu remarked as he turned to Luo Qinghai.

"Indeed, Elder Feng," Luo Qinghai replied with a smile.

"This restriction is certainly not easy to break, but given the combined powers of yourself and the other elders of your Vast Flow Palace, you're definitely capable of breaking this restriction, so why have you still not done so, Grand Palace Master Luo?" Feng Tiandu asked.

"You think far too highly of me, Elder Feng. Besides, seeing as all of us want to enter the immortal manor, we should all contribute our efforts to breaking the restriction," Luo Qinghai replied with a smile.

"I suppose you're right, Grand Palace Master Luo. What do you think, Fellow Daoist Qu?" Feng Tiandu asked as he turned to Qu Ling, in response to which she only gave a silent nod.

"Alright, in that case, let's not waste any more time with idle chatter. Everyone, let's all join forces for now and force the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace to remove the restriction so we can all enter the immortal manor. After that, we all go our separate ways. What do you all say?" Feng Tiandu declared as he swept his gaze over everyone else in the cave.

Everyone immediately expressed their agreement to this proposal, and with that, Feng Tiandu rose up into the air before descending in front of the black restriction.

All of the other Dawn Fall Sect cultivators hurriedly followed along, as did the cultivators from the other powers gathered in the cave.

Han Li was naturally among them, but he intentionally lagged behind a little, situating himself in a discreet corner near the back of the crowd.

An immense collective aura was emanating out of everyone's bodies, placing tremendous pressure upon the black restriction.

The very space was trembling in the wake of the enormous spiritual pressure, and even the entire cave was beginning to rumble.

The black restriction was rippling incessantly as Feng Tiandu declared in a cold voice, "Xiao Jinhan, your plan to keep the immortal manor to yourself has been foiled. Remove this restriction right now. Otherwise, we certainly wouldn't mind doing so by force!"

The black restriction continued to ripple, but remained in place.

Chapter 406: Come In

"Fellow daoists, it seems that the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace is determined to defy us to the end, so there's no need for us to hold back any longer. Let's combine our powers and break this restriction by force!" Qi Tianxiao declared in a cold voice.

Everyone in the cave had been frantically searching for the entrance of the immortal manor over the past few years, and as a result, they had developed a great deal of resentment toward the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace. Hence, they were more than happy to heed Q Tianxiao's rallying call.

"Are we just going to leave it at that, fellow daoists? The Immortal Palace needs to suffer the consequences for what they've done! Not only are we going to break this restriction, we should kick them out of here and relegate them to the fate of not being able to enter the immortal manor, just like what they tried to inflict upon us!" Chen Pi yelled.

Everyone immediately fell silent upon hearing this, while contemplative looks appeared on the faces of all of the most formidable Golden Immortals present.

Generally, everyone tried to get along with the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and it was often referred to as the leading power of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but that was only due to how formidable the Immortal Palace was and the fact that there were generally no conflicts of interest between the Immortal Palace and other sects.

However, the Immortal Palace had put its ambition on full display in the wake of the Blaze Dragon Dao incident, and their sealing of the immortal manor entrance was a move that encroached upon the rights of everyone, so it was no wonder that they had become widely condemned.

Luo Qinghai, Feng Tiandu, and all of the other Golden Immortals were clearly moved by the idea.

They didn't know how many people the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace had sent to the Black Wind Sea, but there was no way that they would be a match for all of these formidable powers combined, so kicking the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace out was certainly a possibility.

Luo Qinghai and Feng Tiandu exchanged a glance with one another, and right as they were about to say something, the black restriction suddenly began to ripple and quiver.

Immediately thereafter, the nine grids reappeared on its surface one after another, while the ripples became more and more pronounced.

A few moments later, all of the nine grids abruptly lit up with dazzling radiance, but the light faded just as abruptly as it appeared, following which the entire black restriction was also lifted, revealing the dim cave beyond.

Everyone was already prepared to lash out, but all of a sudden, it was as if they had punched into a wall of cotton, and they began to exchange bewildered glances at one another, at a slight loss for what to do.

Immediately thereafter, a voice rang out from within the cave.

"Come in, fellow daoists."

Having seen Xiao Jinhan in person back in the Blaze Dragon Dao, Han Li could tell that this was Xiao Jinhan's voice.

Luo Qinghai, Feng Tiandu, and the other prominent Golden Immortals present exchanged a few glances, then made their way into the cave.

Even Qu Ling decided to follow behind Luo Qinghai and the others after a brief moment of contemplation.

All of the True Immortals present immediately followed along, and that naturally included Han Li, who was trailing along behind Daoist Hu Yan.

Before long, everyone had entered the cave.

Not only had the black restriction at the entrance of the cave been lifted, the entire array around the blue gate of light had also disappeared, but the nine stone pillars were still standing.

Without the seal in place, the blue light radiating from the gate had become several times brighter than before, and it was also giving off a glacial aura interspersed with formidable bursts of spatial power.

The glacial aura and the spatial power intertwined while the blue light within the gate surged violently, looking as if it were about to erupt out of the gate altogether.

At the same time, the world's origin qi above Red Moon Island was also churning violently, forming a series of balls of dazzling radiance before exploding amid bursts of dull rumbling.

The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators were situated near the gate of light, observing the cultivators making their way into the cave, and they were led by Xiao Jinhan, who was standing with a warm smile on his face, as if he were a hospitable host welcoming his guests.

Han Li was standing in an obscure corner, and after a quick count, he discovered that there were around two or three dozen Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators present, close to half of whom were Golden Immortals.

What was rather surprising to him was the three dao lords, including Ouyang Kuishan, were also present.

As for the rest of the Immortal Palace cultivators, they were either at the late-True Immortal Stage or at the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage.

The Northern Glacial Immortal Region was clearly far more formidable than any single other power present, and it was certainly worthy of its title as the premier power of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

However, with so many power joining forces, the collective lineup of cultivators was significantly more formidable than that of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace.

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed a group of black-robed figures standing beside the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators, among which were Lu Jun and Lu Yuqing.

He hurriedly ducked behind a physically-imposing man standing in front of him upon seeing this.

The disguise that he had adopted using his Transient Guild mask could fool others, but Lu Yuqing had shown that she was able to identify him through her innate ocular ability.

"Please pardon our intrusion, Palace Master Xiao," Qi Tianxiao said with a hint of a mocking sneer on his face.

Meanwhile, Feng Tiandu, Qu Ling, Luo Qinghai, and the others were all scrutinizing Xiao Jinhan in silence.

"It's so good to see so many of my old friends here. My sincerest apologies for not coming out to greet you sooner," Xiao Jinhan said with a faint smile.

Feng Tiandu clearly wasn't in the mood for small talk, and he said in a cold voice, "Let's not waste any time here, Palace Master Xiao. I'm sure you heard the discussion that we had outside, right?"

"I take responsibility for all of my actions, so all of you can do anything that you please. Our Northern Glacial Immortal Palace is fully prepared to bear the consequences," Xiao Jinhan replied in a calm manner.

Meanwhile, all of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators had placed their hand on their storage tools, and they weren't displaying any fear at all.

"Do you think that we wouldn't dare to go through with our plan, Palace Master Xiao?" Qu Ling asked as a cold gleam appeared in her eyes.

"Your combined powers do indeed exceed that of our Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, but I suggest you think before you act. These stone pillars form an array that can be detonated at any moment that I please.

“The resulting explosion won't be able to destroy the entrance, but it'll certainly be sufficiently powerful to destroy the space near the entrance. As for what'll happen to the entrance itself, you're free to speculate on that," Xiao Jinhan said in an indifferent voice.

Qu Ling's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, and everyone else also became rather hesitant about how to proceed.

Before anyone had a chance to say anything, Qi Tianxiao yelled, "You think an empty threat like that is enough to stop us?"

"If you don't believe me, then you're free to give it a try," Xiao Jinhan replied in a calm and composed manner.

Meanwhile, Feng Tiandu and the others were communicating to one another through voice transmission.

"Fellow Daoist Feng, you're one of the top array masters of our Northern Glacial Immortal Region. Can you tell if those stone pillars really are capable of doing what he claims?" Luo Qinghai asked.

"Even I don't recognize all of the runes on these pillars, but my experience tells me that this is indeed an extremely formidable array, and if it were to be detonated, the consequences would be catastrophic," Feng Tiandu replied.

"What a sly bastard that Xiao Jinhan is. Are we just going to let them off the hook?" Qi Tianxiao asked in a disgruntled voice.

"It'll take a very long time to unravel this restriction, and if a battle breaks out, we definitely won't be able to prevent him from detonating those stone pillars. Our top priority is to enter the immortal palace, so it looks like we have no choice but to adopt a more peaceful approach. Let's see what he says first," Feng Tiandu said.

Luo Qinghai, Qi Tianxiao, Qu Ling, and the others were silent for a moment, then nodded in agreement.

"You've gotten the better of us this time, Palace Master Xiao. We'll settle for a peaceful resolution," Feng Tianxiao said.

None of the other Golden Immortals said anything, but it was clear that Feng Tiandu had the authority to speak on their behalf.

Qu Ling began to make her way off to the side, and all of the True Immortals gathered in that direction hurriedly dispersed to give her a wide berth.

The other powers were feeling rather indignant, but seeing as the Vast Flow Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect had already given up on pursuing this matter, they naturally weren't so foolish as to oppose the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace on their own. Even Chen Pi and the group of Southern Dawn beings had fallen silent at this point.

A subtle hint of relief flashed through Xiao Jinhan's eyes upon seeing this, and he said with a faint smile, "The Infernal Frost Immortal Manor is enormous and filled with countless treasures. Even though it's emerged many times in the past, the treasures in it still show no signs of running out. All of us have come here for the immortal manor, so why ruin the peace with a pointless conflict?"

"You've been here for the longest out of all of us, when do you think the immortal manor will descend, Palace Master Xiao?" Feng Tiandu asked.

"It'll definitely descend in two more days at most. However..."

"What is it?" Feng Tiandu asked.

"In order to reassure everyone, I've already withdrawn the restrictions at the entrance of the cave, but it would be best to keep the entrance of the immortal manor somewhat sealed. Otherwise, we'll be faced with a difficult predicament if the profound glacial qi within erupts outward," Xiao Jinhan replied.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the blue light within the gate abruptly began to churn and rumble, following which a thick pillar of blue light erupted out from within, rising up directly toward the heavens.

The air temperature in the entire cave instantly plummeted drastically, and a layer of blue ice crystals quickly spread over the entire area.

Everyone hurriedly conjured up layers of protective spiritual light upon seeing this while flying away from the gate of light as quickly as they could, and the ice crystals spreading over the cave were also promptly shattered under everyone's collective efforts.

However, the glacial qi within the pillar of light was so formidable that some of the weaker True Immortal cultivators present still suffered some internal injuries from the infiltration of glacial qi into their bodies.

All of the Golden Immortals present hurriedly unleashed secret techniques or released spirit treasures to protect their entourages, and the entire cave erupted into a chaotic frenzy.

Chapter 407: A Request

The pillar of blue light continued to erupt outward for close to 20 seconds before slowly fading, and only then did the disturbance in the gate of light subside.

"It seems like the entrance really does need to be somewhat sealed. I think each of the powers present should send out a representative and have them join forces to seal the entrance. That way, everyone can rest assured that there won't be any foul play afoot," Feng Tiandu suggested.

"I concur," Luo Qinghai immediately chimed in.

No one else raised any objections to this proposal, and each of the factions sent out a Golden Immortal representative, with the exception of Qu Ling, who was on her own.

Han Li's faction sent out Xu Yangzi, and in total, there were six Golden Immortals surrounding the blue gate of light as they chanted an incantation while hovering in mid-air.

Lights of different colors erupted out of their bodies, then intertwined to form a rainbow-like cage of light that encompassed the blue gate.

The light on the surface of the gate instantly began to shudder erratically while releasing shockwaves that were invisible to the naked eye in all directions. The cage of light still hadn't fully taken shape yet, and it began to tremble violently in the face of the shockwaves, looking as if it could shatter at any moment.

However, it was ultimately stabilized as everyone sped up their incantation, but a burst of residual shockwaves was still able to sneak through before spreading outward in all directions.

The weaker True Immortals in the cave were unable to stand their ground in the face of these shockwaves, and they were forced all the way back to the cave wall before finally steadying themselves.

As a result, the originally orderly formation of cultivators in the cave had become a little chaotic.

Han Li was able to withstand the shockwaves, but in order to blend in and not draw any attention to himself, he pretended to stumble back to the cave wall as well.

From there, he observed the six Golden Immortals around the gate of light, and a thought suddenly sprang into his mind.

According to Daoist Hu Yan, there were a total of eight Infernal Frost Scenic Paintings, yet there were only seven powers present, so was there one missing?

All of the Golden Immortals present were sly old foxes who had lived for countless years, so there was no way that they hadn't noticed this. Hence, they must've simply refrained from mentioning this matter for some reason.

While Han Li was deep in thought, a familiar voice rang out beside him.

"Brother Liu!"

Han Li was immediately snapped out of his train of thought, and he turned to discover none other than Lu Yuqing standing not far away from him, sneaking glances at him with a hint of a smile in her eyes.

It seemed that in the wake of the orderly formation of cultivators being broken up by that burst of shockwaves, Lu Yuqing had taken the opportunity to sneak over to his side.

A resigned look appeared on Han Li's face as he sighed through voice transmission, "I should've known I wouldn't be able to hide from you."

"I wasn't expecting to see you here, Brother Liu. Are you also interested in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor?" Lu Yuqing asked.

"Of course I am, given the abundance of precious treasures in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor. However, we belong to different factions at the moment. It looks like Black Wind Island is currently a subsidiary power to the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, so surely it's inappropriate for you to be approaching me like this," Han Li replied.

"It's fine, Brother Liu. We've only been brought here to prevent us from leaking the location of the immortal manor's entrance. Now that the news has already been leaked, our presence here is completely superfluous. On top of that, the situation is a bit chaotic right now, so no one will be paying any attention to us," Lu Yuqing said.

Han Li offered no response to this.

Lu Yuqing hesitated momentarily, then continued, "Brother Liu, there's something I wanted to ask you. Time is of the essence, so I'll keep things brief."

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, but his expression remained unchanged as he prompted, "Go ahead."

"I also want to enter the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and I'm hoping that the faction that you belong to can bring me along," Lu Yuqing declared in a direct and straightforward manner.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "Isn't your Black Wind Island a subsidiary power of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace? Why don't you ask them to take you with them?"

"Are you not aware that each Infernal Frost Scenic Painting can only grant 12 people access into the immortal manor? With such a limited number of spots, there's no way that the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace would be willing to take me with them," Lu Yuqing said in a slightly self-deprecating voice.

"I was indeed unaware of that," Han Li replied.

Having said that, prior to this, he had already noticed that all of the each of the factions present seemed to have consisted of 12 people, but he hadn't thought much of this as there had been other things on his mind.

"You and I are acquaintances, and I really want to help you, but as you can see, all 12 of our spots are already occupied, so I'm afraid I won't be able to help you," Han Li replied.

He was already taking quite a significant risk on this trip, and after seeing so many Golden Immortals here, he was even more determined to keep a low profile. He had decided that he was just going to play it safe and help Daoist Hu Yan obtain what he wanted in exchange for the next three levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

Han Li was confident that he would be able to secure a spot from Daoist Hu Yan, but in doing so, he would have to offend the True Flame Sect, and that was not a desirable outcome for him.

"Don't be in such a hurry to refuse, Brother Liu, I can be more of a valuable asset than you think. Our Lu Clan actually discovered the entrance of the immortal manor even earlier than the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and at the time, we obtained a stone plaque from here that contains a part of the immortal manor's map and some other information.

“As I'm sure you're aware, the immortal palace is fraught with peril. If you bring me along, I'm willing to share my knowledge with you," Lu Yuqing said.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up slightly upon hearing this.

They were venturing into the immortal manor completely blind, so it would indeed be a lot safer if Lu Yuqing could act as a guide for them.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then asked, "Are you telling the truth?"

"I'm willing to swear a vow. If I'm lying to you here, then let me be racked with inner demons and suffer a terrible death," Lu Yuqing vowed in a solemn voice.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li nodded in response. "Alright, in that case, I can relay your request to the leader of our group, but I can't guarantee whether he'll agree or not."

"I knew I could count on you, Brother Liu!" Lu Yuqing said with a faint smile, seemingly completely unconcerned.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he still approached Daoist Hu Yan before relaying what Lu Yuqing had told him through voice transmission.

An ecstatic look instantly appeared in Daoist Hu Yan's eyes after he heard what Han Li had to say. "What? She has a map of the immortal manor?"

"I've met her on several past occasions, so I know her decently well, and I think she's telling the truth," Han Li replied.

Daoist Hu Yan was silent for a moment, then nodded in response. "In that case, let's bring her along."

"What about the True Flame Sect?" Han Li asked in a hesitant voice.

"Leave them to me," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then turned to Lu Yuqing and informed her of what had just transpired through voice transmission.

An elated look appeared in Lu Yuqing's eyes, and she gave Han Li a slight nod from afar before returning to the group of Black Wind Island cultivators.

At this point, the restriction set up by the six Golden Immortals around the gate of light had already been fully established, and a thick rainbow light barrier had appeared over the blue gate.

Glacial qi was surging violently within the gate of light, but the light barrier remained firm and resolute, standing against the waves of glacial qi without any trouble. It seemed that his restriction was even more formidable than the one that the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace had set up here earlier.

"As expected of a master of arrays like yourself, Fellow Daoist Feng, this restriction of yours is quite profound," Xiao Jinhan praised as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"You're far too kind, Palace Master Xiao," Feng Tiandu replied in an indifferent voice, then sat down with his legs crossed somewhere in the cave.

All of the other Dawn Fall Sect cultivators immediately sat down around him.

Meanwhile, Xiao Jinhan glanced at Feng Tiandu for a moment longer before returning to the group of Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators.

The other factions in the cave were also waiting for the immortal manor to descend, and with so many people present, the cave was virtually entirely filled.

Xu Yangzi had also returned to the group, and Daoist Hu Yan approached him to exchange a few words.

After hearing what Daoist Hu Yan had to say, Xu Yangzi was initially quite disgruntled, glowering at Han Li with a furious expression, but as Daoist Hu Yan continued, the fury on Xu Yangzi's face gradually faded, and in the end, he gave a reluctant nod.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this, then closed his eyes to meditate.

Two days passed by in the blink of an eye.

The gate of light in the cave had swelled to over twice its original size, and the patterns on its surface had become extremely clear, making it seem as if it really were a spatial gate that led to another world.

Hovering within the gate of light was a ball of blue light that was churning violently and giving off radiant blue light.

A spatial passageway could be seen within the ball of light, but it was unclear where it led to.

At this point, everyone in the cave had already risen to their feet and were intently scrutinizing the gate of light, which was trembling incessantly.

The nearby space was also buzzing and trembling, causing the entire cave to shudder and sway.

The rainbow cage of light around the gate was still standing, but it was clearly being overwhelmed.

The six Golden Immortals rose up into the air once again at Feng Tiandu's instruction before attempting to fortify the cage of light, but their efforts proved to be futile as the light radiating out of the blue gate was becoming brighter and brighter, slowly forcing the rainbow cage outward.

All of a sudden, the ball of blue light within the gate abruptly swelled to several times its original size, virtually filling the entire blue gate while fluctuating in size in an unstable fashion.

At the same time, waves of rippling blue light erupted out of the gate, and all of the space in the wake of the rippling immediately blurred and warped.

Before long, the rainbow cage was completely shattered, and the six Golden Immortals around it were instantly sent flying back, but they were already prepared for this outcome, and they were able to escape injury by activating some protective secret techniques.

"There's not much time left, so there's no need to continue," Feng Tiandu said as he stared intently at the gate of light.

Right at this moment, the entire gate of light exploded violently amid a resounding boom, transforming into a ball of radiant blue light.

A projection of a series of mountains, rivers, palaces, and pavilions appeared deep within the ball of light, but it was unclear what location the projection was depicting.

Chapter 408: Entering the Immortal Manor

The ball of blue light was slowly revolving while hovering in mid-air, and rays of translucent blue light were emanating from within alongside a cloud of faint white mist. The scene within the ball of light was already rather indistinct, and it was made even more obscure by the layer of faint mist.

After a brief silence, someone yelled in an excited voice, "There it is!"

Their excitement was contagious, and everyone else's eyes immediately lit up.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense toward the ball of blue light, and his soul immediately shuddered violently. It was as if a rumbling thunderclap had rung out directly beside his ears, and his expression remained unchanged, but he hurriedly withdrew his spiritual sense in alarm.

At the same time, he could see that the complexions of many of the people present had also paled slightly, clearly indicating that they had also suffered some backlash after extending their spiritual sense toward the ball of blue light.

Han Li's spiritual sense was comparable to a Golden Immortal, yet even he had suffered some minor degree of backlash, so the other True Immortals were naturally only going to fare worse. As for the Golden Immortals present, they were able to avoid substantial backlash, but it seemed that they weren't able to make much inroads with their spiritual sense, either.

"'Fellow Daoist Luo, Fellow Daoist Feng, why don't you two go on ahead?" Xiao Jinhan offered with a smile.

"We couldn't do that, Fellow Daoist Xiao. Your Immortal Palace has done such a good job of protecting the entrance up to this point, the right to enter the immortal manor first should be reserved for you. Wouldn't you agree, Fellow Daoist Feng?" Luo Qinghai jibed.

Feng Tiandu's expression remained unchanged, and he merely gave a cold harrumph in response.

Before Xiao Jinhan had a chance to respond, Qu Ling interjected, "If the three of you are unable to reach a consensus, then I'll go first."

She then pulled out her Infernal Frost Scenic Painting and gave a gentle shake, upon which a vast expanse of light surged out from within to envelop her entire body before carrying her into the ball of blue light.

Everyone faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which a hint of agitation began to spread through the crowd.

Han Li looked on with a contemplative expression as Qu Ling vanished into the ball of blue light.

Xiao Jinhan turned to Xue Ying and the others, then instructed, "All of you, come with me. The rest will stay here."

He then summoned his Infernal Frost Scenic Painting, and a burst of blue light surged forth to envelop himself, as well as eight Immortal Palace cultivators and the three dao lords of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Immediately thereafter, the group flew into the ball of blue light, vanishing in the blink of an eye.

Meanwhile, the rest of the Immortal Palace cultivators and the Black Wind Island cultivators remained outside.

After all of the Immortal Palace cultivators had entered the immortal manor, Luo Qinghai offered for Feng Tiandu to go ahead, but the latter remained unmoved. Hence, Luo Qinghai called upon the cultivators of the Vast Flow Palace before summoning his Infernal Frost Scenic Painting, and before long, they had also flown into the ball of blue light.

Only then did Feng Tiandu take a glance at Qi Tianxiao, and the latter instructed the Dawn Fall Sect's cultivators to assemble before flying into the ball of blue light as well.

At this point, the number of cultivators present had been reduced by around half, and the remaining factions were naturally all raring to go.

Chen Pi spoke briefly with the Southern Dawn beings, then made his way toward Han Li's group again.

"Fellow Daoist Gu, I think we should let the Southern Dawn beings go in first, and our Ghost Wail Sect will go in after them. Once we're in there, we'll wait for your group to come in so all of us can explore the immortal manor together," Chen Pi said.

"That sounds like a good plan, Fellow Daoist Chen," Daoist Hu Yan replied with a smile.

Chen Pi could see that the Southern Dawn beings had already entered the ball of blue light, and he hurriedly said, "Alright, then we'll be going ahead."

Following the departure of the Ghost Wail Sect cultivators, Daoist Hu Yan said to Han Li and the others, "Looks like it's our turn."

Xu Yangzi gestured for everyone to gather together, and there was still a hint of displeasure in his eyes as his gaze swept over Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

"The immortal manor is filled with treasures, but also fraught with peril, so after we get in there, let's do our best to stay together and not get separated," Daoist Hu Yan cautioned.

He then pulled out an Infernal Frost Scenic Painting of his own, and it released a burst of blue light that swept up everyone before flying into the blue entrance.

In the instant that they entered the ball of blue light, Han Li felt a burst of buzzing ring out beside his ears, immediately following which all of his senses virtually completely faded, leaving only a hazy consciousness behind.

It was an indescribable sensation that was very disconcerting, but thankfully, everything returned to normal after less than 20 seconds.

As Han Li's senses gradually recovered, he heard the sound of howling wind blowing past his ears.

He was greeted by the sight of a pristine white world that was covered in snow, and the entire surrounding area was filled with glacial qi. On the distant horizon were countless giant tornadoes that stood like pillars between heaven and earth, presenting an awe-inspiring sight to behold.

A layer of azure light appeared over his body to keep the wind and snow at bay, but he could still feel a bone-chilling sensation seeping into his body.

He looked around to find that the factions that had previously entered the immortal manor were already nowhere to be seen.

Lu Yuqing had conjured up a layer of protective spiritual light as well, but a layer of frost had already appeared over her eyelashes, and she exclaimed, "It's so cold..."

The crimson robes being worn by the True Flame Sect cultivators were glowing brightly, and waves of heat were surging out from within, but even so, they weren't faring much better.

Xu Yangzi and the other Golden Immortals were doing just fine, but the other True Flame Sect cultivators were all shivering uncontrollably.

"Please use your scenic painting to shelter everyone, Fellow Daoist Gu," Xu Yangzi said as he turned to Daoist Hu Yan.

Daoist Hu Yan nodded in response, then flipped a hand over to produce his Infernal Frost Scenic Painting, which unfurled in front of him.

Immediately thereafter, a spherical light barrier emerged from the painting to encompass everyone.

As soon as the light barrier appeared, the sound of the howling wind instantly subsided, while the unbearing bone-chilling sensation was also kept at bay.

"The Southern Dawn beings and the Ghost Wail Sect cultivators are nowhere to be seen," Yun Ni remarked.

"There's no integrity or reliability to speak of when it comes to a bunch of ghostly cultivators and foreign race beings. They most likely already departed on their own as they didn't want to fall behind everyone else," Elder Zhen Yun sneered.

"I don't think that's the case. Chen Pi took the initiative to approach us earlier, and I think he was earnest about forging an alliance. Compared with the likes of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, the Vast Flow Palace, and the Dawn Fall Sect, our individual factions are far too vulnerable, so it's necessary for us to band together. Hence, I don't think they would've gone back on their word just to get ahead of us," Xu Yangzi said with a shake of his head.

Han Li turned to Daoist Hu Yan as he said, "I can sense some traces of spatial power in the snowstorm here. Perhaps they were teleported elsewhere against their will."

"I also think that's a possibility," Daoist Hu Yan replied. "Seeing as we can't find them for now, let's leave this area first. In any case, we must proceed with caution. Make sure to stay by my side and do not leave this light barrier from the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting."

Everyone immediately gave affirmative responses to this.

Right as Daoist Hu Yan was about to set off, Han Li's voice suddenly rang out beside his ears through voice transmission.

"Senior Hu Yan, I've already entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor with you, so would you be able to give me the next three levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture now?"

Daoist Hu Yan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then grumbled, "Isn't it too early to be asking for compensation? We've only just entered the immortal manor and haven't even done anything yet!"

"But you promised that you would give me the fourth level of the cultivation art upon entering the immortal manor," Han Li replied with a smile.

Daoist Hu Yan was familiar with Han Li's personality, so he wasn't bothered by this, and he removed a storage pouch strapped to his waist before handing it to Han Li as he said, "The immortal manor is a very dangerous place, so here are some life-saving treasures. Make sure you don't lose them."

Han Li hurriedly accepted the storage pouch, then briefly examined its contents with his spiritual sense before putting on a facade of gratitude and excitement as he said, "Thank you, Uncle."

No one was suspicious of this, thinking that this was just a routine precautionary measure.

"Which direction should we go in? Everything looks the same here," Han Li said as he stowed the storage pouch away.

He had just tried to examine the surrounding area with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, but no matter where he looked, he saw nothing but a vast expanse of snow and ice.

Daoist Hu Yan's brows furrowed slightly as he turned his gaze to his Infernal Frost Scenic Painting, trying to find the right way forward when all of a sudden, Lu Yuqing pointed in a certain direction and said, "There seems to be an exit over there."

Everyone turned to the direction that she was pointing in, and sure enough, there was an indistinct ball of blue light in the extremely far distance, something that would've been impossible to spot unless one were to look very closely.

Han Li knew that Lu Yuqing possessed a special ocular ability, so he wasn't all that surprised. However, he had previously looked in that direction, but hadn't seen any speck of blue light, so it seemed that it had only just appeared.

A hint of bewilderment appeared in Daoist Hu Yan's eyes as he took a glance at Lu Yuqing. After all, even with his eyesight as a Golden Immortal, he had failed to notice the speck of blue light.

Hence, everyone began to travel in that direction under the protection of the spherical light barrier.

Chapter 409: Separated

As they drew closer and closer, the speck of blue light expanded further and further, and Han Li and the others were gradually able to see the entire thing.

It was indeed a blue spatial vortex, and it was releasing very similar energy fluctuations to the vortex that they had just entered through.

All of a sudden, the space up above abruptly shuddered, following which all of the snowflakes in the sky were rendered completely stationary.

Immediately thereafter, the snowflake converged to form a giant snow dragon that was over 1,000 feet thick, swooping down upon everyone with tremendous power.

A resounding boom rang out as the blue light barrier around everyone was struck by the snow dragon and was violently shattered. The wind and snow that surged into the broken light barrier had become extremely violent, and it split up everyone in different directions before hurling them high up into the sky.

The power released by the exploding snow dragon was so fierce that an extremely violent windstorm was swept up, and everyone was frantically trying to steady themselves in mid-air, but they were unable to do so, and the gusts of ferocious wind sent them flying away in different directions.

Bright azure light emerged over Han Li's body as his Thunderstorm Wings appeared on his back, and he flapped them with all his might, doing everything in his power to stabilize himself.

He was just about to search for Daoist Hu Yan when he spotted a black shadow hurtling rapidly toward him, following which he felt a soft body wrap itself around him.

Han Li had only just barely managed to steady himself, but the impact of having someone else crash into him tipped him off balance once again, and he fell involuntarily into a gust of ferocious wind.

The world spun rapidly around him, and he didn't get a chance to see who it was that was clinging to him before he fell unconscious.

……

On a vast and windy snowland.

The space in this area was far more stable than in the previous area, and the landscape was riddled with massive cedar trees that were covered in snow.

There were around a dozen figures standing in front of a cluster of cedar trees, and they were led by none other than Deputy Palace Master Xue Ying of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace.

Even though they were standing together, it was clear that there was some division among them. The Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators were all gathered together, while the three dao lords of the Blaze Dragon Dao were standing a bit further away.

"The immortal manor will only be open for a year, why is it that Palace Master Xiao hasn't come to meet up with us?" Ouyang Kuishan asked as he took a glance at the snowland around him.

"We wouldn't have to act so urgently if the location of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor's entrance hadn't been leaked," Xue Ying said in a cold voice.

It was clear that she was suspecting the three dao lords of leaking the location of the entrance.

Ouyang Kuishan's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, and he gave a cold harrump before falling silent.

"The palace master is taking care of the people entering the immortal manor after us. He's going to send them into the spatial storm to separate them, and that'll make them much easier to deal with. Even if any of them dare to oppose us, we'll be able to divide and conquer them, rather than having to face them all at once," Xue Ying explained.

The three dao lords exchanged a glance with complex looks in their eyes upon hearing this.

……

There was a nameless gray desert that was covered in gray pebbles of different sizes. The desert was completely devoid of vegetation, and there were patches of snow littered across the landscape.

At the center of the desert was a winding channel that had seemingly been bored into the ground over time by flowing streams of melted snow, and there were some ponds of different sizes inside, the surfaces of which had all been frozen solid.

Laying beside the channel on the trunk of a fallen cedar tree were a pair of unconscious figures, one male and one female.

The man was laying face-down on the ground, so it was impossible to glean his appearance, while the woman was extremely beautiful.

At this moment, the woman's arms were wound firmly around the man's waist, while her face was pressed tightly against his side, presenting a rather intimate sight to behold.

Right at this moment, the man suddenly shuddered before regaining consciousness.

He turned over before getting up into a seated position, then began inspecting his surroundings with a slightly disoriented look on his face.

The man was none other than Han Li in disguise, and at this moment, there was no one else with him aside from the young woman that was clinging to his side.

Daoist Hu Yan, Yun Ni, and the others were all nowhere to be seen.

"Fellow Daoist Lu..." Han Li called out as he patted the woman on the shoulder with a layer of azure light over the palm of his hand.

The woman was none other than Lu Yuqing, and she gave a muffled groan before also regaining consciousness.

After taking a glance at Han Li, she inspected her surroundings with a dazed expression while massaging her own temples as she asked, "Where are we, Brother Liu?"

Han Li didn't immediately reply. Instead, he began to inspect his surroundings with his spiritual sense and his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

A short while later, he withdrew his gaze as he said, "We're definitely still in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, but I don't know exactly where we are."

"Where is everyone else? Why are we the only ones here?" Lu Yuqing asked with a puzzled expression.

"It seems like we were attacked earlier and swept up into a spatial storm that separated everyone. It appears we're the only two to have ended up here," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

Only after hearing this did Lu Yuqing recall how she had clung desperately to Han Li in a blind panic during the storm, and a faint blush immediately appeared on her face.

"What do we do now?" she hurriedly asked in order to mask her own embarrassment.

Han Li fell into deep thought upon hearing this. The original plan was for everyone to travel together, so he still didn't get a chance to ask Daoist Hu Yan about the internal layout of the immortal manor.

"I scoured the area with my spiritual sense just now, and there are no clear spiritual power fluctuations nearby. However, the further we go in that direction, the lower the air temperature becomes," Han Li said as he pointed in a certain direction.

"In that case, that's where we should go. That should be the first area of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, the Light Frost Region," Lu Yuqing said.

"How do you know about this, Fellow Daoist Lu?" Han Li asked as he turned to Lu Yuqing with a puzzled expression.

"As I said earlier, our Black Wind Island discovered the entrance of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor even earlier than the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and even though we've been ordered to keep everything about the immortal manor secret, my father still conducted a great deal of research into the immortal manor in advance," Lu Yuqing explained.

A peculiar look appeared on Han Li's face as he asked, "In that case, was it your father that leaked the location of the immortal manor's entrance in secret?"

This was not just a completely baseless theory from Han Li.

Black Wind Island had guarded the entrance of the immortal manor for the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace for many years, yet they had received no reward at all for their efforts, and not even a single one of the Immortal Palace's 12 spots had been granted to them.

As a result, Lu Yuqing had no choice but to implore Han Li to request a spot for her from Daoist Hu Yan, and only then was she able to enter the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor.

Lu Yuqing was terrified to hear this, and she hurriedly waved her hands as she denied, "Please don't make such damning accusations, Brother Liu! We wouldn't dare to do something like that. If the Immortal Palace pins the blame on us, then our entire island runs the risk of being wiped out!"

Han Li had no intention of pursuing this matter, and he smiled as he reassured, "Don't worry, I was just curious. I didn't mean to cause any alarm."

The location of the immortal manor's entrance being leaked was a positive development for Han Li, and he didn't care who it was that had leaked this information. Even though he had joined forces with Daoist Hu Yan and the True Flame Sect, they still couldn't compare with the likes of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace and the Dawn Fall Sect.

In the wake of the location of the entrance being leaked, many powers had been able to get involved, thereby completely muddying the waters, and that could only benefit people like Han Li.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li took a glance into the distance, then swept a hand through the air to summon an azure flying boat with four azure wings on either side.

"Let's go. There's no point in staying here any longer," he said to Lu Yuqing, then flew onto the spirit boat.

Lu Yuqing nodded in response before also springing up into the air and landing on the flying boat behind Han Li.

The flying boat then sped away as a streak of azure light at Han Li's behest.

There was a blanket of dark clouds hanging in the sky at a low altitude, giving the entire area a rather oppressive atmosphere.

It was a very bleak and desolate area with no living creatures in sight, nor any sounds to be heard aside from that of the passing wind.

After flying for a few minutes, snowflakes suddenly began to drift through the air. Initially, the snow was quite sparse, but as they continued onward, the snowfall became heavier and heavier.

At the same time, the environment beneath them gradually began to change. As they left the gray desert behind, they arrived on a vast ice field.

The clouds in the sky had darkened significantly, and the snowflakes drifting through the air also appeared significantly heavier than before, falling from the sky thick and fast.

Thankfully, this area wasn't filled with the same intense cold as the initial area that they had arrived in upon entering the immortal manor, and the layers of protective spiritual light over their bodies were sufficient to keep them warm.